- ( static hissing )
P
Pre
Prese
Presen
Present
Present Da
Present Day
Present Day_
P
Pre
Prese
Presen
Present
Present T
Present Ti
Present Time
Present Time_
- ( static hissing )
- ( distorted speech )
- ♪ AND YOU DON'T SEEM
TO UNDERSTAND ♪
♪ A SHAME YOU SEEMED
AN HONEST MAN ♪
♪ AND ALL THE FEARS
YOU HOLD SO DEAR ♪
♪ WILL TURN TO WHISPER
IN YOUR EAR ♪
♪ AND YOU KNOW WHAT THEY SAY
MIGHT HURT YOU ♪
♪ AND YOU KNOW THAT
IT MEANS SO MUCH ♪
♪ AND YOU DON'T EVEN
FEEL A THING ♪
♪ I AM FALLING ♪
♪ I AM FADING ♪
♪ I HAVE LOST IT ALL ♪
♪ OHH-HH ♪
♪ OH, YEAH ♪
♪ I AM FALLING ♪
♪ I AM FADING ♪
♪ I AM DROWNING ♪
♪ HELP ME TO BREATHE ♪
♪ I AM HURTING ♪
♪ I HAVE LOST IT ALL ♪
♪ I AM LOSING ♪
♪ HELP ME TO BREATHE. ♪
- ( chattering )
- Lain: WHY?
WHY WON'T YOU COME?
YOU REALLY SHOULD COME HERE.
( panting )
- WHAT'S THE MATTER WITH HER?
- OH, MY GOSH.
- ( laughing )
- YOU'RE TOO MUCH!
- I KNOW.
Why you should do that...
...is something you should figure out for yourself.
- ( laughing )
- COME ON, BABY.
- NO.
- COME ON, COME ON.
- HEY, CUT IT OUT.
- DON'T BE LIKE THAT.  COME ON.
- GET OFF.
- NO.  HEY!
- COME HERE.
- COME ON.
- ( laughing )
- ( wind blowing )
- ( mouthing )
I...
...don't need to stay in a place like this.
- HUH?
- Man: WHAT THE HELL?
WHAT'S GOING ON HERE?
- Woman:
OH, NO, THIS IS HORRIBLE!
- Man #2: I DON'T KNOW.
- Man: WHAT'S ALL THAT NOISE?
WHAT HAPPENED?
- Man #2: I DON'T KNOW ANYTHING.
WE GOT NOTHING TO DO WITH THIS.
- Woman #2: SHE JUST CAME OUT
OF NOWHERE.
- ( chattering )
- ( electricity humming )
If you stay in a place like this...
...you might not be able to connect.
- ( chattering )
- IT'S SO NOISY.
CAN YOU JUST SHUT UP?
- Man: HUH?
- Woman: HUH?
- ( chattering stops )
- ( chattering )
- GOOD MORNING!
- YOUR HAIR LOOKS SO GOOD TODAY.
- ( chattering continuing )
- Girl: YOU GOTTA SHOW ME
WHERE HE'S SITTING.
Everybody, hurry...
- ( girl sobbing )
- JULIE, COME ON.  DON'T MAKE
SUCH A BIG DEAL OUT OF IT.
- YEAH, REALLY.
IT'S JUST SOME STUPID PRANK.
- BUT I JUST--
- AWW, JULIE, IT'S OKAY.
- LAIN.
- OH.
- SO DID YOU GET ONE, TOO?
- GET WHAT?
- THE EMAIL.
- EMAIL?
- CHISA YOMODA'S EMAIL.
- I'M NOT UP ON ALL THAT STUFF.
- YOU REALLY OUGHTA CHECK YOUR
EMAIL AT LEAST ONCE A DAY.
IT'S BEST TO, YOU KNOW?
- BABY LAIN
DOESN'T KNOW COMPUTERS.
- HUH?
- ( crying )
- POOR JULIE.
WHY IS SHE CRYING?
- BECAUSE SHE GOT THAT
AWFUL EMAIL FROM CHISA.
CAN'T YOU PUT TWO
AND TWO TOGETHER?
- CHISA?
- IT WAS SUICIDE.
SHE WAS THE ONE
IN D IN OUR SECOND PERIOD.
SHE JUMPED OFF A BUILDING
LAST WEEK.
- THE TEACHER TOLD EVERYONE.
- AND IT'S NOT JUST JULIE.
THERE WERE A WHOLE BUNCH
OF OTHER PEOPLE
WHO HAD GOTTEN EMAIL
FROM HER THIS WEEK ALSO.
- BUT IF SHE'S-- SHE'S--
- DEAD.  THEN WE SHOULDN'T BE
GETTING ANY EMAIL FROM HER.
IT MUST BE A PRANK.
- ( sighs )
What's it like when you die?
It really hurts. :)
Powering up...
- Computer: Log in.
Just a little longer...
Who is the user?
- HUH?
- Lain.
Please state your name.
- LAIN.
- Voice accepted.
Greetings to user Lain.
User Lain has new email.
- WHO'S IT FROM?
- Chisa Yomoda.
Do you wish
to read your email?
Hello, how are you?
Hello.
How are you?
Lain,
I remember walking home
with you once.
Do you remember?
I have only
given up my body.
You see, by sending you email,
I can use this system
to explain to you
that I am still alive.
I wanted to let you
know this, Lain.
I want all the others
to know, too.
So I have sent them
email also.
You may find this hard
to believe.  Do you understand?
It's okay if you don't.
You will all understand soon.
- WHY DID YOU DIE?
- There is a rumor at that
school that this email is
some sort of a prank,
but I want you to know, Lain,
that it is not a prank.
This is real.
- BUT WHY--
WHY DID YOU DIE?
- Here...
...there is a god.
- HUH?
God...
- ( sighs )
I'M FINISHED ALREADY.
IS THAT OKAY, MOM?
I HAD A BIG LUNCH TODAY.
- UH... M-MOM.
- YES.
- I GOT AN EMAIL
FROM A FRIEND TODAY.
IT WAS FROM THIS GIRL I KNOW
WHO KILLED HERSELF LAST WEEK.
- ( car approaching )
- ( door opens and closes )
- WHAT IS IT, LAIN?
YOU USUALLY DON'T COME
TO VISIT ME IN HERE.
WHAT IS IT?
- I--
YOU KNOW THAT NAVI?
IN MY ROOM, IT'S OLD NOW.
DO YOU THINK THAT I--
- SO FINALLY CAUGHT
THE COMPUTER BUG, HAVE YOU?
LAIN, YOU ARE IN JUNIOR
HIGH NOW ALREADY.
YOUR SCHOOL CHUMS
MUST BE LEAVING YOU
IN THE TECHNICAL DUST.
HUH?
WE SHOULD UPGRADE
THAT OLD NAVI.
YOU KNOW, LAIN,
IN THE REAL WORLD,
OR THE WIRED WORLD,
PEOPLE ARE CONNECTED SOMEHOW.
THAT TELLS US HOW THESE
ARE CREATED.
YOU SHOULD BROADEN
YOUR HORIZONS.
MAKE AN EFFORT
TO CREATE FRIENDS.
TAKE THE INITIATIVE.
EVEN A GIRL LIKE YOU
SHOULD BE ABLE TO MAKE FRIENDS
RIGHT OFF THE BAT.
YOU CAN LIVE AND COMMUNICATE
IN BOTH WORLDS.
IT'S NOTHING
TO BE AFRAID OF.
I WISH YOUR MOTHER
COULD UNDERSTAND THAT.
- I'M NOT SCARED.
NOT REALLY.
- SO WHY ARE YOU UP SO LATE
AND TALKING
ABOUT YOUR OLD NAVI?
- I HAVE A FRIEND I WANT TO SEE.
- YEAH!  HA HA!
- ( train clacking )
- ( crash )
- ( screaming )
( brakes squeal )
- Man: WHAT HAPPENED?
- OUCH!
- Man over PA:
Ladies and gentlemen,
we apologize
for the inconvenience.
The train is temporarily
stopped due to an accident.
Please be patient.
- WHAT WAS THAT?
DO YOU THINK WE HIT SOMEONE?
- Man #2: I CAN'T BELIEVE THIS.
- ( crossing alarm blaring )
- ( train horn honking )
- ( plinking )
- Woman: MISS IWAKURA.
- ( panting )
- MISS IWAKURA.
- YES, MA'AM.
- BLACKBOARD.  YOU KNOW
THIS WILL BE ON THE TEST.
Come to the Wired as soon as you can.
- ( electricity humming )
- ( gasps )
CHISA.
SO WHERE ARE YOU?
WAIT.
nan no tsumi mo nai hazu na no ni nanraka no batsu wo uketeru
Although I must be innocent, now I am punished
jibun de maita tane de mo nai no ni
I wasn't the one who sowed those seeds, but nevertheless
sakimidareta hana tsumasareru
I have to pull up the flowers that bloomed from them
shiranai koto to mo ienai ga
I can't say I didn't know about it
katabou katsuida oboe wa nai
but I don't remember taking any part in it
jiyuu wo takaku kawasareta ki mo suru ga
I think my freedom cost me dearly
kokoro made yasuku utta oboe wa nai
but I don't remember selling my soul so cheaply
hey hey kutabatte osaraba suru made
Hey hey, until I die and say farewell...
hey hey dare no te ni mo kakaranai
Hey hey... no one can touch me
tooi yoru wo urotsuiteiru
You probably don't know
shiranai darou eien no narazu monotachi wo
the eternal outlaws prowling in the distant night