"Washing and Drying Complete"
Dad, wake up~!
Oh no! It's noon!
You'll miss the trial! Come on!
Hurry up now!
"6:03"
Hey...
It's 6:00, 6:00
I want to wash the sheets.
You'll bother the neighbors
if you do laundry this early.
Don't worry. I already greeted
the neighbor below us.
You greeted them?
That a problem?
No, ah it's cold, cold.
Anyway!
Hey, hey!
Hands off!
(Start)
(Timer Mode)
What're you doing?
Just ironing.
Send them to the cleaners.
Look, it looks much better
when I do it.
The housekeeper will
do the chores.
She comes twice a week.
If you mean Mita-san,
I canceled...
- No, I fired her.
- Fired?
You paid her ?100,000 a month,
didn't you?
That much, huh?
That's right!
In spite of that, she took advantage
of your indifference.
Plus she's been cutting corners.
She made you take out the trash,
and didn't do laundry other
than sending them to the cleaners.
From now on, I'll be doing all
the housework chores.
That would cut down my expenses.
You'll pay me instead.
That's only fair since it counts
as work as well.
Cleaners fees are included,
of course.
That wouldn't cut my expenses at
all!
I'll give you a discount.
"Operation commenced."
Hey
- Huh? What?
- A moment.
- Come.
- What?
Huh? Hmm.
What about you?
You've been shopping online.
I only bought what's neccessary.
See? See? Is that neccessary?
Do we need that?
Isn't it cute?
That's not what I meant.
Look, it's working really hard.
Wow. I'm getting sick of this.
Huh? That would be nonsense.
I'm not from Shikoku, you know.
I don't eat udon everyday.
Shikoku folks don't, either.
I just like it.
I'm paying you, so make me what I
like.
Oh, right. Before I forget...
I jotted some notes.
Take a look.
What now?
As for lodging,
I pay you ?10,000 a night.
Conversely, you're paying me
?3,000 for breakfast.
But we haven't decided dinner's.
So how about this amount?
?4,000 for dinner?!
For ingredients, and service charge.
Don't you know I can eat
extravagantly for ?4,000?
You do know how well I cook, don't
you?
But you know, I only seldom
eat dinner at home.
Even if you don't eat, I'm still
charging you ?7,000 per day.
Wait a minute, that's unfair.
Dad... and you call yourself a
lawyer?
For example, a train pass.
It's unrefundable no matter what.
So your lodging fee will now be
?3,000 a day?
You paid ?100,000 for housekeeping,
so it evens out.
I understand. I understand.
Whatever.
It's not 'whatever'.
You need to reconsider
your spending habits!
Aren't you wasting money?
Money talk makes me lose my
appetite.
But it's important.
Time to dig in.
No talking during meals.
Didn't your mother teach you?
"Let's talk and enjoy meal time!"
I concur with Mom.
You act as if we're strangers.
You always speak...
Do you understand? Don't
waste your money, Dad.
I'm not wasting my money.
Chaccone.
Why do you have spend that
much just to have a drink?
More than ?30,000 for whiskey!
It's just ?5,000 in stores, and a
mineral water for ?1,000, ?1,000!
The ones being sold ?88
in supermarkets, you know.
It wasn't Chaconne, but tap water
costs 2,000 in clubs.
Some clubs are like that.
That's wasting money!
In any case, don't work
at Chaconne anymore!
Even if I want to, they won't
let me. They sent me home.
Rather than drinking
at a place like this,
shouldn't it be more important to
spend it with your wife?
That's no way to treat a customer.
But why does he have to drink in a
club when he has kids waiting?
Look here, people get stress
from working hard.
They drink to relieve stress.
It gets better drinking with
beautiful women.
That's why men go to clubs like
Chaconne. Generally.
Then generally speaking,
why can't they drink with
their children?
They want to be kids too.
That's why there's a "Mama".
Oh! I see now. They want
to be spoiled, huh.
That's how it is.
You too, Dad?
Generally speaking.
I go for meetings, work related.
But you go alone. That's not a
meeting.
When I go alone, it's to cool down.
To refresh my weary mind and body.
So that's how your relationship
with Haruka-Mama is.
Don't tell me... you lavish
money on her unconditionally?
I don't lavish money!
Really?
There are customers like that.
You're one of them, right?
That's not it. Me and...
- What?
- Anyway, don't go back there.
Because she might find out
that I'm your daughter?
Don't you tell her.
Hmm
Rest assured. I don't feel like
telling her at all. As of now.
"As of now" you say?
By keeping it secret? I might
expose Haruka Mama's real face.
Don't ever tell her!
You got that? Don't ever
tell her! Ever!
Okay, got it.
Thanks.
Bring your plate
to the sink after eating.
There's no self-service if I'm
paying ?3,000, okay?
Don't ever tell her!
You got that?
- You got that?!
- Okay, got it.
(Omotesando Station)
Just give it a try... just a little?
I'm sorry!
What? Come on. It's okay.
Hello there.
You striking out?
I'm scouting. Though it's not
working well.
What a hassle.
It'd save me a lot of trouble
if you came back,
but it's your attitude
that worries me.
What should I do?
Huh? You didn't call for that?
No.
Mama's financial situation?
Why would like to know?
Huh?
I thought it might come in
handy as reference.
Well, she makes a lot of money.
A whole lot more than the others.
Don't lots of customers lavish money
on her?
It's not "lavish," more like a
habit to contributing for her sales.
Like Suzuki-sensei?
Why do you mention his name?
Huh?
Nothing.
Ah, didn't he mention that he
knows your father?
Ah, that's right. Right,
right, that's right!
This please.
- Same for me.
- Yes.
How long has Sensei been
lavishing on Mama?
Who knows? Ask her yourself.
Can I meet her
outside the club?
At this hour, it's physical time.
Uchipanashi(driving range) or detox.
Uchipanashi(bare concrete wall)...
You mean concrete?
I'm so sorry!
Then where does she detox?
I'd never have guessed she'd be
here.
Now, let's flush all the toxins
in your body as we sweat it all out.
The goddess pose.
Enjoy your own body.
Hello there!
Hello.
Thanks for the other day.
Ah, did Ryota-kun...
umm... enjoy his time
with his father?
Very much.
That's good.
You alone today?
Umm... at this time, Dad's...
I don't mean him. Tamagawa-san
was it? That guy.
Ah, he won't be coming
back I think.
He was quite shocked when
he heard you had a child.
Oh, why is that?
Well, I'm not really sure, either.
She doesn't even realize
that he likes her.
Urara-san, work hard.
Will do.
Ah.
I'll be borrowing your father
once in a while, okay?
See you.
Thanks for waiting.
She's quite formidable.
Why, if isn't it Rei-chan.
Hello.
Ah, are you member here also?
Ah, yes. As a family member
of my father's membership.
Your father?
I wonder who he is.
Did I already met him?
I wonder about that.
He works in the day
so he only comes at night.
We have different schedules then.
I guess so.
Do you know the
instructor Okuno-san?
If I see her face, I might recognize
her. Why?
No, nothing.
Is that so? See you then.
I'm truly sorry for
my behavior last time.
Please let me work once again!
Do you mean it?
Yes.
This work isn't a game, you know.
I understand.
I'm counting on you.
FLAT OUT TOKYO GIRL
Thank you very much.
Here you go.
Excuse me.
- Mika!
- I'm here. I'm here.
Welcome!
Daisuke quit the gym?
Wasn't he suppose to court
that gym instructor?
Yes, but...
Is it because she's divorced
and has a kid?
Doesn't he know it's not
the time to be picky?
That's rude to the lady, Joanna.
I guess, Daisuke's friend
is the cause of everything.
He takes rejections hard...
But he keeps coming for more.
You mean Urara?
But he doesn't have
a chance, does he?
Who knows?
I don't think he's out of his
league.
But she doesn't seem to
like him either.
Daisuke, did you catch a cold?
I bet you were talking about me.
We were.
You sure have fun picking on me.
So what's your next plan, Daisuke?
Who're you courting?
But what I liked best was Aki-chan,
the one before you met Urara-chan.
You keep say that,
but she dumped me.
Ask your own heart, who is it
that you really like the most?
When it comes to customers,
it's money, am I right?
Well, of course it's good if they
spend money for the club, but...
That's not all.
Have you seriously
fallen in love with a customer?
I wonder.
For example...
how about Suzuki-sensei?
Rei-chan, we never know
who'll be listening now...
But I have clarify this...
No way.
Anyway, it'll be bad
if other customers hear about it.
You know what I mean.
Yes, but...
Hello.
Ah, hello. It's me.
Huh? I don't know who "me" is.
It's Daisuke.
Huh? Hello?
- Too close.
- Babbling...
You keep babbling there.
Why did you call?
How about dinner today?
I have work.
Work? Where?
A place called Chaconne.
- I'm going ahead.
- A flower shop?
No, it's a club.
Club?
Club!
Club... you mean where
a lot of those women?
Yeah, that's right.
Seriously?
I'm serious. See you then.
Hey, Mama?
Excuse me.
What's the difference
with KUrabu and kuRAbu?
KUrabu is for activities while
kuRAbu is for dancing?
Yeah, that's it.
"Roppongi"
Welcome.
Call Mama for me.
One moment, please.
Mama!
Welcome.
Is Sakurai here?
No.
He'll come here with "that".
Thank you always.
"That"?
Wait, is Rei-chan present?
Right away...
I don't need her.
You don't need to call her.
But isn't she your friend's
daughter?
Rei-chan, right here.
This is Rei-san.
Ah... there's already someone here.
Why didn't you ask for me?
Don't be so cold~ So cold...
Don't get carried away.
Take her away from me.
Yes, as you wish. Sit down.
Risa-chan.
Some champagne?
Thank you.
This is Risa-san.
Welcome.
- Evening.
- This way.
Ah, I'm okay.
Thanks for coming
Any problem?
None.
Have a drink.
No thanks. I have to pick
up Hitomi any moment.
Check if there's 3 million.
I trust you.
Here. That mine?
I'll take it then.
Thanks.
What was that just now?
No comment.
What? Rei-chan! A customer.
Yes.
This is Rei-chan.
Nice to meet you.
Mama will be here soon.
Thank you.
Can you pour me a drink?
Ah, I'm sorry.
You're Haruka-Mama's customer, huh?
Rather than being a customer...
...I'm just happy to here drinking.
Welcome.
Thank you for waiting.
Asking for Urara-san?
Yes.
Please.
Urara-san.
Thank you for requesting me.
I'm Urara.
Where's Urara-san?
She's the only Urara here though.
That's me.
Is there another
Chaconne in Roppongi?
I don't think so.
It's here.
Strange.
Is something wrong?
No thanks.
What?
How do you do?
I'm the Mama here, Haruka.
He came to the wrong
place and was about to leave.
- Oh, that's a shame.
- No, no.
Then, I'll stay a little bit.
I'm glad.
We have a system...
It's okay, Shimo-chan.
I'll explain it to him.
Mama, I'll be going.
Thank you very much.
Thank you.
Oh, good evening.
Good evening.
That person is dating my father.
Here to pick up your kid?
That's right.
I had a late shift today, so
that's why I'm so late.
Must be tough.
Well then.
Umm...
Yes?
Nothing. Have a good night.
I'm home.
Huh?
I'm H-O-M-E!
Welcome home.
- Dad...
- Aren't you early?
I left early.
Feeling sick or something?
You're not even worried about me.
You lavished money on
Mama, after all.
I didn't lavish.
I was just there to drink!
3 million a month!
Hey! Why do you have this?
I took it back.
What did you do? That's theft!
- But that's...
- It's important money!
She needs it tomorrow! Move!
Ah, hello. Mama? The money's
missing, right? It's here with me.
Ah well, Sakurai kinda
messed up the amount.
Yes, right now I can deliver it.
Hey, you can't.
Hey!
Hey! Sakurai!
Stop it Sakurai!
- I'm not Sakurai!
- Stop!
You don't need to come.
I'll come to you, okay?
Hey.
Hey, come on.
Don't butt in!
Acting all frantic.
Hey! Wait up!
Wait!
What?! What should I do?
Just ignore it.
What?
What? She has a spare key?
Sensei? Are you home?
Don't open. Don't open.
- Don't open.
- He's not home, huh.
I'll come back, then.
That's a relief.
Huh?
Good evening.
Hello.
I knew it.
Yes.
So Sensei was the father
you've been looking for, wasn't he?
Thank you for your help
at that time.
You saved me and
brought me to my father, but...
I didn't know how to tell you.
Dad wanted to it
kept as a secret as well.
I see. He wouldn't
let me in recently.
I'm sorry for that.
It's kinda funny thinking
Sensei is being a father.
Busy with life.
So he didn't tell Hanako-san
that he had a kid?
What's "Hanako-san"?
Huh? No, it's nothing.
Hanako-san, how do you
feel about my father?
In what way?
I mean, why are you dating
such an old guy?
An old guy, huh.
Does he have any merits?
Like his work?
I never fall in love thinking...
...about merits or demerits, you
know.
Does he, like, support you?
He does give me psychological
support, though.
The fact that he gave you a spare
key means that Dad too...
I wonder.
Then why do you always
use the intercom?
Huh?
If you have a spare key,
why don't you come in by yourself?
Now that you know about me,
what're you going to do now?
What can I do?
How about marriage?
Have you thought about it?
I guess so.
Is that the extent of it?
Maybe.
Are you really sure about this?
Probably.
Ah, I'm getting annoyed now.
I'm confused on things.
Is that Dad's fault?
I may be at life's crossroad (kiro).
Kilo?
Sensei, where is he now?
Oh, umm... he's off to Roppongi
for some business.
Roppongi?
He'll be coming back right away.
Then, I better get going.
What?
Can you keep this a secret
of us meeting tonight?
Why is that?
Won't that be interesting?
You're right.
Here.
Yes.
Thanks. Ha~ Such a waste of time.
Unbelievable...
- Welcome home~
- ...Not!
Don't meddle ever again!
Then explain it to me.
Why are you lavishing on
Haruka-Mama?
You're annoying.
When you can't answer,
you always yell.
I've had it.
I'm not obliged to answer...
"Don't interfere with my
life," right?
Thanks for the food.
You're welcome.
Thanks for the wait.
I'm Suzuki. Pleasure to meet you.
I'm Suzuki, it's a pleasure.
H-hold on a moment.
Please sit down.
Ah...
Hello.
Well, can you come down to
the parking lot for a moment?
I'm working right now.
I have something important to tell
you. Without my father knowing.
Can you hear me?
- Sakurai-san!
- Sakurai.
Hello?
Listen to me!
Okay.
Sakurai-san! Hello? Saku-
- Come on.
- Sorry...
Turn it off.
I'm turning it off.
Usually... hey!
Hurry, hurry!
Stop calling me!
Why didn't you stop him?
What?
Yesterday's 3 mi-
Yesterday's 3 million.
You withdrew it from my father's
account and brought it over, right?
Isn't that right?
I can't answer that.
Why can't you?
I'm bound to confidentiality.
What do you mean by that?
Lawyers can't disclose information
of his client to a third party.
I'm not a third party.
I'm his daughter. His daughter.
That's not the point.
Then, what is it then?
Like I said, I can't tell you.
- Sakurai-san...
- No way.
Never mind then.
Hey.
It's a dead end for me.
"Accepting Applications"
Sorry! Ah Joanna!
Urara?
I'm sorry. You brought a lot.
These are "manga" materials.
Oh? Is that so? I'll help out.
Thank you! I was on my back.
Oh really now?
Thank you very much!
Food & Drink: 46,000 yen
That was expensive!
I thought you were gonna be
late coming home last night...
Don't mind me!
So that's why you're not helping,
you were looking for a job
...to pay your bill.
Shut up. Don't mind me.
What kind of woman is she this time?
Looks like it.
Again?
"Again"? Hey now!
I don't fall in love for gossip
fodder.
So it's love, after all.
I'm back!
Welcome back!
Hello!
Hello! You helped me.
Thank you.
Careful, it's torn.
- Thanks!
- See you, bye bye!
Urara! Urara!
What did you come here for?
Ah, oh yeah!
Oh yeah. Umm...
Can you listen to me?
Huh? You mean me?
Anyone will do, but...
Hey, hey, hey.
What is it?
I went last night.
- Where?
- Chaconne.
You weren't there.
- I was there.
- You're kidding.
You like that kind of place, huh?
There's something I want to ask you.
You mean Haruka-Mama?
Huh? Well.. that's...
Better forget about her.
This time's a club's Mama, huh.
Dad won't wake up?
Wait. He's breathing?
That's not what I meant.
He doesn't know he's deceived
and giving her money.
What? To whom?
Haruka-Mama.
He spends money there every night,
last night he gave 3 million!
- 3 million?!
If he's being deceived, shouldn't
you report this to the police?
Police?
Do you have proof he's being
deceived?
Proof?
Police is too serious,
you should consult a lawyer.
I can introduce you to a friend of
mine...
Ah, I already know one.
Huh?
Lawyers can also be deceived, right?
Normally they do the
deceiving, don't they?
Like making money by abusing
their knowledge of the law?
No, he won't do such thing!
What?
Huh?
Somehow...
I feel I've been spinning my
wheels again.
I'll try to find some proof.
Sorry for the disturbance!
Oh, okay.
3 million...
Different worlds.
Urara-san's tricky as always.
Hmm... proof, huh.
"Cafe Tamariba; This Way"
Welcome.
Focus. Aim for the ball. Shuu~
There. Try hitting.
Okay.
Listen,
Lift your head.
- Like this?
- Right.
Spread this a bit.
I see.
Your back form.
- Good.
- I see.
There.
You're facing the wrong way.
Ah, okay.
Okay.
One more time.
Thank you very much.
Safekeeping please.
- Certainly.
- Thank you.
I'll drop you off.
Oh, I have an appointment
after this.
Pro-Kikuchi, please come
by the club again, okay?
Thanks for waiting.
Not at all.
- Sorry for being late.
- It's okay.
I'm just happy to be here drinking.
An early afternoon love affair.
The two people just now, what room
are they in?
Huh? May I know who do you mean?
The people who just rode the
elevator.
I don't know what you mean.
Ah... then, is Haruka Kubo
staying here?
She may not be actually
staying here...
I'm afraid I can't give
you that information.
Then I'll just go ringing
each room's doorbell.
Hey!
Ma'am! Ma'am!
Ah ouch, ouch.
I understand! Okay, I understand.
Thank you for coming.
Hey. Ma'am! Ma'am!
- Oh look there!
- Liar!
What're you doing there?
Mama, you're deceiving
Suzuki-sensei, aren't you?
What're you talking about?
You received 3 million yen
from Sensei, didn't you?
So, what if I did?
Earlier, you were meeting an old
guy at the club, right?
You were watching us?
Let's work hard today, everyone.
We'll do.
I saw you two go up to a room.
And in there, you gave him
the 3 million, right?
Yes, I did.
How would that mean
deceiving Sensei?
You deceived him for money and
then you give it to another man.
That money's our credit sales
he collected for us.
Credit sales?
Our customers usually pay
on a monthly basis.
Why would Sensei do that?
He's a lawyer, that's why.
Huh?
Only lawyers can collect debts.
However, who was that man you
were secretly meeting at the hotel?
Secretly?
You were walking arm in arm.
I was only assisting him.
My dad's old and his knees buckle.
What! Your dad?
Yes.
Whoa!
Welcome home!
What're you doing here?
I was thinking you'd be
coming at any moment.
I figured I'd wait here.
Ah, you're up to something.
Not at all. It's my duty as
daughter to care after...
...her father who's been tired
working all day.
You're up to something.
Not at all. I'm being honest.
Huh? Tonight's a feast.
What's wrong?
I've misunderstood terribly.
I heard what that 3 million was for.
Sakurai again!
No, it's not him!
Sakurai-san didn't tell me because
of confidentiality.
I see.
I asked Haruka-Mama directly.
My father's company went backrupt.
He was saddled with a huge debt.
For that reason, our family
broke in pieces.
Then I quit my day job I loved,
and became a hostess.
I wanted to help pay off my father's
debt.
So it's for the sake of your father.
If we pay his debt back,
my mother he divorced, and
missing brother as well...
They'll come back to us.
Then I'll build a house my family
can live in.
That's my current dream.
Mama!
When you and Haruka-Mama met,
it was when she was my age, 19
years old, is that correct?
Yeah. She worked in Roppongi.
It was her second day.
You've been supporting Mama
ever since, right?
It wasn't just a part time job,
she was determined to
make it her career.
I myself too, want to
support Haruka-Mama.
She booked a luxury hotel
for her father
who came from Hokkaido
to visit her.
Her father also runs around
trying to pay his debt.
At least when he visits Tokyo,
she wants him to relax.
That's what actually happened.
What a great loving
daughter she is.
I need to learn from her.
I thought of taking
good care of you even more.
You can do that by staying
out of my private life.
No, what my goal is...
...is to make you happy.
That's why, I'm happy if
people butt out of my business.
Dad, sit down.
What is it?
On your knees.
Okay.
Haruka-Mama, she
seems to like you.
She said you're
the first customer...
she'd gotten romantically involved.
Okuno-san as well,
she likes you, Dad.
Sure, Ryota-kun comes first, but...
"I'll be borrowing your father once
in a while, okay?" She said to me.
Hanako-san too.
She seems unsure, but
she does like you.
Wait, what's "unsure"?
Hmm, she said she was
in life's crossroad (kiro).
I don't know how many kilometers
or kilogram that is.
Dad.
What now?
Hanako-san, Okuno-san,
or Haruka-Mama.
Which of them is your
true love interest?
Or is there someone else?
Ah, there are more of them!
No, I don't have!
Then who it is then?!
Say it clearly!
Why do I have to say it clearly?
It's rude to those who aren't
your love interest!
Besides, you have to nurture
your love seriously.
Or else it's going to
fail like your marriage with Mom.
I don't want to...get married.
It's better to be!
Dad, you're about to hit 50 already!
You have to think about
what'll you do when you're old.
It's not like I'll be with you like
this forever.
You gonna take care of me when I'm
old?
Dad! Please take this seriously!
Okay.
With marriage aside,
who do you feel happy with
the most?
All of them. Or I wouldn't date
them.
Having a relationship with three
at the same time, isn't that too
selfish?
You really think so?
Ah!
Those words, just now.
All of Japan, no all the
women in the world...
you're their enemy, you know!
No, not just women.
You've made unpopular guys
your enemies too!
Hey, you done?
I'm getting hungry.
Did you know? I invited them.
All 3 of them.
What?
Hanako-san.
Okuno-san.
Haruka-Mama. Right now,
they're heading here.
You're kidding.
Whether I'm kidding or not,
you can confirm in 3 minutes.
Or maybe in a minute?
Quite possibly in 30 seconds?
Hey. Hey, what did you just do?
Prepare yourself.
You've got to be kidding!
Hey. Hey.