Business trip?
Staying overnight?
So I don't need dinner
and breakfast.
I'll borrow a towel.
But, hey...
Do lawyers do business trip?
I've never heard of it.
In the world...
...there are so many things
you do not know yet.
I'm aware of that.
Tomorrow's trial is...
...about the case in Iiyama Onsen
in Akita prefecture.
So, it's taking place there.
And I have to go to Iiyama Onsen.
The trial is starting
at 10am, so I won't...
...make it tomorrow.
That's why I'm staying tonight.
Aren't you staying in onsen resort?
Kind of.
I'm coming.
- It's for work.
- Yes, sounds fun!
They apparently have
hydrogen carbonate spring.
I'll enjoy open-air bath.
It is probably going to be fun.
I won't bother you.
Can I come?
It's mixed-bath.
No problem!
No.
- You're going with someone.
- Oh.
Hanako? Okuno?
Or Haruka?
No.
Then, with whom?
Yes, I'm coming with him.
You see?
Mr Sakurai, isn't it OK
for me to come with you?
Well, sir...
No, we need to have
some meetings before the trial.
That's not fun.
Actually, the nursery
called me just now.
I asked them to take care
of Hitomi tonight, but...
...the child carer
is off sick today and...
...now they can't.
Ah, I see.
That's a problem.
I'm contacting
other nurseries as well, but...
...it's difficult to find a place.
Urara, can you do it instead?
I'll get my bag.
Not that! Take care of Hitomi.
But it's too much for her.
Urara, please.
I'll get a souvenir.
Sure.
Something other than
onsen dumplings, though.
Are you sure?
I really like Hitomi.
In which case...
...take the key.
Certainly.
I'll call the nursery
to let them know.
What shall I cook tonight?
Does Hitomi have
any dislikes?
(Failed)
She likes rice omelet recently.
Got you.
See you later.
Bye.
- Sorry, sir.
- Not at all, Urara...
...will do a favor
with all her effort.
She is nosey and noisy
if nothing to do.
Sir, the car is here.
Thanks.
Shall we go?
Yes.
Have a nice trip.
Thank you.
- Yes?
- I'm here to pick up Hitomi.
I'm Urara Saeki.
Come in.
Flat Out Girl Tokyo
Can I do the slider once?
Sure.
Thanks!
What shall we have for dinner?
Hamburg steak!
Hamburg steak?
- Ah, hello.
- Oh.
Are you here for Mr Sakurai?
Yes. He's away for business trip
with my father.
I see. Can I do anything?
I think we're fine.
Call me if there is something.
Thank you so much.
Oh. Wait a second.
Hello.
Hello. You sound fine!
Would you like to work today?
Ah, sorry.
I can't tonight.
Really? I only...
...ask you when I'm
in a real trouble.
I know you don't want me to come.
I don't mean that.
We've got a group reservation.
We fall short by one hostess.
I'd like to help...
...but I need to be a mother today.
"Mother"?
Sorry.
Wait, wait. If you can't...
...it could be one of your friends.
My friend?
What?
If I can be of your help.
Well, I can't ask you, Ms Okuno.
What is it?
A substitute for night-time job.
Don't you know someone?
Someone pretty, obviously.
- Oku...
- Yoko!
Yoko was lamenting...
...she can't save up
for travel overseas.
- Ah, Yoko!
- Yes.
I'll ask someone.
Oh! That's brilliant.
Thanks!
Who's coming?
Ayu? Is Ayu coming?
"Tokyo Dome!"
Ah, thank you.
Here.
- It's a bit far.
- True.
Thank you for coming.
Please come in.
Sir.
I'd like to go and check something.
What? Is it about the trial?
Yes.
Take this.
Certainly.
Please wait!
This way please.
Hitomi, turn off the TV...
...and clear the table, will you?
OK.
Good.
Hitomi. Look at this!
- Do you want to see?
- I do.
Ready?
There you go.
Wow, a little bear!
- Isn't it cute?
- It's cute!
Hasn't Sakurai been back?
I'm going to start.
You're late.
We can't trust the witness.
What?
The documentation says
the witness saw...
...the crime scene at 9pm.
But it's impossible.
He was on the way home
from the nursery.
What's wrong?
Unlike in Tokyo,
nurseries in this area...
...can only open until 7pm...
...at the very latest.
Which means...
...the time wasn't...
...at 9pm?
That's right.
It could be the case that
he hasn't seen it at all.
Wait a second.
Wouldn't that be the case...
...the child carer personally
made an exception?
I checked that too.
That wasn't the case.
Sakurai.
Well done.
It felt strange for him
to go here...
...with a child
on the way home.
You realized since you pick up
Hitomi every day.
Yes.
Good! We can win this case.
Do you want a drink?
Want a hostess?
No, I'm just happy
to be able to help.
- Let's eat anyway.
- Yes.
Hitomi, shall we have a bath?
What happened to you, Hitomi?
Daddy won't be home today, will he?
Daddy has his work.
Shall we make
a phone call to Daddy?
Make a phone call to Mummy.
I don't know about your Mummy.
Urara, don't take my Daddy from me.
I won't do such a thing.
Really?
No, you don't have
to worry about that.
But Urara, you like
my Daddy, don't you?
I like him, but...
I don't love him, you know.
I don't understand.
Don't cry.
Hitomi, I have a good idea.
I'm coming.
Sorry.
- Good evening.
Oh? Hitomi, are you crying?
No, I'm not.
I know. You're
a big girl, aren't you?
Will you play with Ryota?
I can!
Just treat her as a big girl.
You're brilliant!
It's from Chaconne.
Didn't Yoko help them?
Hello.
- Rei?
- Ah.
Mama.
Was it you who sent Yoko
from that sports gym?
Ah, yes, it was me.
Was it not good?
- Boing boing...
- It's the opposite!
I was so surprised.
She's more suited
to be a bar hostess.
Drink anything you like.
Oh, thank you!
Now I don't have
to ask you a favor.
Bye then.
Let me join you!
Ah, I'm so stuffed!
Will it stop snowing?
Guess so.
The forecast said so.
Shall I prepare futon?
Sorry?
- Futon.
- Hello, it's Sakurai.
Hello. Good evening.
Has Hitomi gone to bed?
She did. Sorry...
...she is asleep.
I see.
Do you want to speak to...
Sir, I will do it.
No worries.
Was Hitomi a good girl?
She was.
She told me not to take
her Daddy from her.
Sorry.
What did you have for dinner?
Hamburg steak?
A bear-shaped one.
Thank you so much.
Did she eat OK?
(Failed)
It is cold here.
But apparently it'll stop snowing.
Yes. Is Tokyo cold too?
Please wrap her up warm.
Sure.
Keep your good work.
I will. Thank you.
Not at all.
"The Code of Criminal Procedure...
...is one of the six codes of laws."
"The six codes consist of
the Constitution, the Civil Code..."
It's a bliss.
- That's rather old-fashioned.
- Hmm?
How do you say it now?
Now? Well...
I'll check it up.
Oh, Sakurai.
It's just a chit-chat.
OK.
Thank you about the witness.
It's nothing.
I'm just happy to serve you.
So?
How is your study going?
Yes.
Just now...
...I saw your result.
- I'm sorry.
- Don't be.
You don't need to say sorry.
It's going to be the last chance
to try next year.
I know.
I'll get third time lucky.
I'll do my best.
Sorry for reducing
your time to study.
You mean, this trip?
Yes.
That's not a problem.
It's great for me
to shadow your work.
No.
You have to pass the Bar Exam first.
I know.
When is the last train to Tokyo?
It's already left. Why?
Then, return to Tokyo
as the first thing in the morning.
Was there any meeting scheduled?
Go home and study.
As I remember, the mock exam
at Kanto Law School...
...was in two weeks.
Have some time off.
I'm not taking it.
Why?
I need to prepare for the redress
suit over vaccination.
No, no.
Do you know the priority, don't you?
I do.
This suit has to be won.
I would like to work on it,
even when I failed the exam.
Even if you failed?
Yes.
I hope to work as your assistant.
Stop joking!
Shut up.
What?
Thank you.
- Thanks.
- Hope to see you again.
- Sir!
- Thank you.
I'll get those bags.
Sir!
(Namahage Transport)
- Open the boot.
- No need for it.
Get your own taxi
and go back to Tokyo.
But, I...
Can you go to Akita Central Court?
Sir!
Wait!
(I will pass the exam)
Will Daddy come home today?
Yes, he will.
That's nice.
But isn't he too busy
to play with you?
I heard he is studying here too.
Daddy always plays with me.
Really?
What time will Daddy come home?
Well...
If you go to the nursery...
...and play with your friends,
he will pick you up.
Will Daddy not come home,
if I don't?
You do not need to go!
We have some time till the evening,
so shall we go somewhere?
Yes. We need to tell the nursery.
Got you.
Shall I make a packed lunch?
Where shall we go?
- Swimming in the sea.
- Huh?
It's already cold now.
(District Court
No. 302)
Did you really witness the scene...
...at 9 o'clock at night?
- Definitely.
- With your child?
Yes.
That is strange.
The childcare hours in this area...
...is until 7pm.
Our research showed...
...you did not use
another child carer on that day.
In the first place, it was...
Thank you.
Thank you very much.
Ouch, ouch!
I mean, I broke up with Aki.
I'm clean. Like just after the bath.
Daisuke, aren't you insincere?
But she dumped me.
Isn't she pregnant?
Why do you know it?
Breaking up with
a pregnant girlfriend?
No, no. It was her...
...mistake.
Oh really?
I was prepared to become a grandpa.
Me too.
Good morning.
Udval! Oh, no Yukari.
It's already after 10am.
No need to use Mongolian now.
- Any drink?
- Can I...
- Hello.
- ...stay here?
Hello.
- Ah, there you are.
- So cute!
Isn't she?
Is she yours?
No way! Whose is she?
Sakurai's. My dad's assistant.
What's your name?
Hitomi Sakurai.
Good job, young lady!
You can introduce yourself.
Your clothes look pretty.
- Would like to try?
- Yes.
Come.
Urara. How's your mother?
Ah. I guess she's fine.
She was a lovely person.
Don't you think?
I only had a glimpse of her.
Mika?
Apparently, Dad...
...fell in love at the first sight
with her.
Mika!
- What?
- What's that?
You're not in the place to say that.
Like father, like son.
You both might
have forgotten, but...
...Mum is working hard in Cambodia
removing landmines.
I know! I'm hoping
for her safety every day.
Hey, you're free today.
Don't assume.
Are you not?
I quit the job
at construction site.
Let's go out.
With us two?
Of course.
With Hitomi too.
I don't mind.
Isn't he handsome?
Not really.
Kids are honest.
I'm leaving.
Hey, wait. Wait!
OK.
Can you carry me
on your back?
On my back?
Go on.
Not on my back,
but on my shoulders!
Wow!
I want to see lesser pandas.
I agree.
Sir.
What are you doing here?
Go back to Tokyo.
I researched the people
concerned to the defendant.
Please let me be at the meeting!
Look, Hitomi.
There's an elephant!
Wow, it's big!
It's big, isn't it?
It's huge.
Doesn't it look like Daisuke?
Does it?
It does.
- You see?
- See?
There is my Daddy.
It looks like him.
- Does it?
- Yes.
There's my dad.
- Which?
- That one.
Daisuke in 30 years?
Ah, there is me.
You chose a pretty one
for yourself.
It look like me, doesn't it?
I don't think so.
- See?
- Really?
It's eating.
You made good friends.
Ta-da!
Pretty!
I know.
Let's eat.
Thank you for food.
Daisuke?
Ah, thanks.
What was I for her in the end?
- You mean, for Aki?
- Yeah.
I wasn't needed
for her life in the end.
But "in the end", right?
I probably should think
we had a happy time together.
Yes.
That's right.
You will find someone.
I am quite happy now.
Really?
Love at the first sight again?
Come on.
I mean, now.
- Which animal?
- What are you talking about?
I mean you.
You?
- You mean, me?
- Yes.
What about me?
You don't know what I meant.
Think harder.
You're happy when you're with me?
Never mind.
Why can't you talk normally?
Pop.
- Shall we go?
- Hey.
I want you to carry me
on your back.
That one?
It's not carrying on the back.
On the shoulders.
Good for you, Hitomi.
My dad used
to do this for me.
Shigesan carried you?
Higher! Higher!
When I was a child.
How about you?
My dad has never done that.
Urara, you like your dad so much.
Everyone likes their dads.
Don't you think, Hitomi?
But you haven't seen him
for 15 years.
He is still my dad.
What if he was a weird guy?
He is weird in a way.
He has three girlfriends.
That means he is popular.
It's not good for him!
I want him to get re-married.
Are you sure? Then, you won't
be able to be with him.
I'm not his girlfriend, you know.
I want him to be happy.
How about yourself?
Most ordinary girls say...
...that they want
to be happy.
Oh, really?
Ah. I forgot you're not
an ordinary girl.
My own happiness?
What's up, Hitomi?
I lost a shoe.
Oh. I'm sorry!
Why didn't you notice?
Is it my fault?
I can't see any.
We're sorry, Hitomi.
I'll get you a new pair.
Stop crying.
My Daddy got me that pair.
Wait here. I'll go and find it.
- Excuse me!
- Yes?
Have you got a shoe like this
at Lost and Found?
Is it... this one?
It is!
- We've found it, Hitomi!
- Wait!
It may not be the one.
- It's the same.
- No, no!
Let's see whether Hitomi
is the Cinderella.
- There.
- Wow, it's heavy.
Give it to me.
Here.
It fits perfectly!
Good for you.
- OK, let's go.
- Yes!
Thank you so much.
Take care, you both.
Mum and dad.
You are a dad?
And you're a mum?
Come here.
That was so funny.
No, you look older than you are.
You don't want this guy
as a father, do you?
Why do you say that?
It's from your dad!
Here you are.
Daddy?
Hitomi? Where are you?
Hello. This is Urara.
Urara. Where are you?
I'm at the nursery.
They say she's not here today.
Oh, sorry.
We're in the zoo.
I forgot to tell you.
Why didn't you let me know?
"Northerly wind
blew the wind to let...
...the traveler
remove his coat."
It's Daddy!
I'm home.
Welcome home!
Were you a good girl, Hitomi?
You cried a bit, didn't you?
Thank you so much.
I had a good time myself.
We went to the zoo.
Really?
Did you see many animals?
I did.
Elephants, giraffes,
gorillas, rabbits...
Wow, that's cool.
But, aren't you back early?
Welcome home.
You were late.
Really?
After the trial, we had a meeting
with people concerned.
Mr Sakurai was back before evening.
What's happened?
I want Sakurai to become a lawyer.
Won't he?
Take a seat.
Let me explain.
- OK?
- Yes.
In order to be a lawyer...
...firstly...
...you need to pass the Bar Exam.
And...
...you need to either
graduate from law school...
...or to pass the preliminary exam.
Then, you are eligible
to take the Bar Exam.
You take the exam
within five years...
...up to three times.
Can't you take it every year?
The rules were changed
in 2002.
Sakurai started working with me
in the year...
...he graduated.
Three years ago...
...he took the exam
for the first time.
But he failed.
He took it this year again...
...and failed.
Next year is the fifth year...
...and the third time.
It'll be the last chance.
However...
...looking at
his results this year...
...it'll be difficult.
But that is...
...partly my fault.
Sakurai is an able guy.
He helped me a lot
in this trip too.
I tend to rely on him.
It ended up him
not having time to study.
So I'd like him to concentrate
on studying.
That's why I told him
to take a day off.
I see.
However good as an assistant
he might be...
...without the license...
...there will be limitations.
So I want him to become a lawyer.
It must be hard as he needs
to take care of Hitomi.
I'll get on with work.
- Aren't you hungry?
- I had dinner.
Why don't you tell me?
I didn't have time.
Here's some snack.
I went to the zoo with Hitomi.
Oh, really.
Did you get me a souvenir?
I forgot.
No!
Sorry. As I gave
Sakurai a day off...
...I have things to prepare
by tomorrow.
My workload increased.
I'll help you.
No way.
Then, I'll be a lawyer and...
OK, OK.
Listen to me.
Don't worry about me.
Do whatever you want
while you're in Tokyo.
While I'm in Tokyo?
You're going back
to Kotohira.
That's Mum's idea.
Do you want me to go?
Whatever you wish.
(Redress suit over vaccination)
Hello.
Sir, you have a guest.
Sorry for bothering you.
- I came nearby...
- No worries.
You're always welcome.
Here is a souvenir.
Did you visit Aomori?
Just for one night.
How was your dad?
Thanks for asking.
He can leave the hospital soon.
That's good. Just a second.
Hello?
You don't seem
to have time for lunch.
Go and get lunch.
I told you not to come.
Here's the reference
for the redress suit.
I don't need it.
Sir.
Tell me if I made a mistake.
I told you take holiday.
I can't when there
are so many jobs to do.
You don't understand me.
Don't you need me?
I myself think...
...I have contributed to your work.
Ms Shimizu. I'd like to
put a call for a new assistant.
Can you ask to Bar Association?
Oh, OK.
Get your stuff
and vacate the desk.
I'll pay the salary until now and...
...the salary
until next September...
...as retirement allowance.
- Wait...
- That's all.
Leave now.
I understand.
Please make a call.
Certainly.
Are you sure?
Yes.
Wasn't he a trustworthy
partner for you?
That's why I fire him.
Won't you miss him?
I will.
I almost certainly will be.
I am going to be in trouble.
"The six codes consist of...
...Constitution,
Criminal Code...
...Civil Code, Commercial Law,
Code of Criminal Procedure and...
...Code of Civil Procedure."
I got it right.
Well, OK!
Who is this?
Can I help you?
I'm Shimizu
from "T. Suzuki Law Firm".
- Excuse me.
- Huh?
Hey, um, what?
What are you doing?
I was asked to deliver the reference
for the redress suit.
Oh, well.
Ah, this is it!
Dad? Why didn't you ask
about the reference to me?
I don't know your schedule.
I didn't know you're at home.
You can't find it either.
I will deliver this.
He is in hurry!
I know that!
I'm quicker.
I'm still young.
Hey!
Wait!
Mr Sakurai.
Ah. Hello.
What are you doing here?
Well...
He told me to quit the job.
- You're late.
- Here.
Where were you?
- See you tomorrow.
- Dad.
Did you really have
Mr Sakurai fired?
Did you hear from him?
He was sitting in the park,
so depressed .
He still doesn't understand.
Aren't you wanting to support him?
But things have to be changed.
Changed?
He said he'll prepare for exam
while helping you.
If he can do that, he would
have passed already.
He hasn't realized it.
Actually, he probably knew that.
I shouldn't have relied on him.
Relying on him?
Yes. Of course.
So I want to work with him
as a partner not as an assistant.
Partner?
Working with him
for four years...
...I know he is enthusiastic...
...considerate and sensitive person.
He is a bit careless sometimes...
...I can guarantee
he will be a good lawyer.
He is a person...
...needed for this firm.
Needed?
Assistant and partner
are different things.
So, I really want him
to pass the Bar Exam.
If he is fired,
he is nothing, not even a partner.
Sakurai may not have
heard it properly.
I said I'll pay his salary
until next September.
Next September?
Until he knows
the result of the exam.
So he can concentrate
on studying until then.
That's right.
Are you going to pay him
for a year without working?
When he passed, I'll pay
the maintenance during...
...the training, registration fee
and the allowance to join the firm.
Dad.
You'll be in trouble
if Mr Sakurai is not here.
Yes.
I see.
You see what?
(Pass the Exam)
(Job Search Navi)
(Part time job)
What's up?
What are you going
to do, Mr Sakurai?
I would have liked
to work with Mr Suzuki.
I'll choose another way...
...for Hitomi.
(Pass the Exam,
1st Jan 2005)
You have no idea
what my dad is thinking.
Sorry?
Also, you shouldn't use Hitomi
for your excuse.
Aren't you becoming a lawyer?
I would like to.
But...
I probably can't.
Do you think my dad
doesn't know anything?
My dad knows...
...you will become a good lawyer.
He is expecting to you.
That's why he said he will pay
your salary until next September.
So?
He wants you to pass the exam
whatever happens.
He want to see you
celebrating...
...your success with Hitomi.
Why don't you understand that
when even I can see it?
My dad is planning to support you
after you pass the exam...
...to become a lawyer
until you can join...
...his law firm.
He doesn't need an assistant.
He needs a partner.
Mr Sakurai, as a lawyer.
Then...
...you can help him
as much as you want.
He needs you.
It can't be me.
So, please do your best for my dad.
Do your best...
...and respond
to my dad's expectations.
Please!
Look, there is a rainbow
Let's go and find
Our big dreams
If we hold our hands together
We feel so strong
Daddy?
Hitomi.
Daddy will do my best.
About what?
Studying.
Are you not sleeping again?
Maybe.
So that we can play together
while you're awake.
Don't work too hard, Daddy.
I know.
Daddy. Can you carry me?
No. I want these.
Ah. On my shoulders?
There.
There!
Look, now the rain has stopped
The sun is coming out
Beyond the blue sky
We can see a rainbow
Let's go and find
Our big dreams
Hitomi, wash your hands.
OK!
Daddy.
This is wet.
What?
(Pass the Exam,
1st Jan 2005)
Respond to my dad's
expectations.
Please!
I'm home.
Hello.
It's Chaconne.
I'm Suzuki.
Ah, hello.
Are you visiting us tonight?
No.
Is there Rei?
She is not here tonight.
Shall I call you
if she comes?
But she may not come.
Don't worry. Thanks.
(Receiving call
Dad)
Thank you for waiting.
Departing at 23:15.
This bus is for Kagawa,
Kotohira Kannonji Terminal.
Thanks for waiting. Express coach
for Shikoku is now departing.
The bus departing.
Beware of the moving vehicle.
(Shinjuku Station)