This bus is bound for Tokyo
via Seto Ohashi departing at 19:45.
Impossible.
You must be joking, Mom.
Actually...
It's true.
"Dear Urara,
Happy birthday. Sayuri"
This is Sanuki Express,
Shinjuku bound.
Impossible.
Good evening.
"Express Bus Ticket"
Thank you.
Impossible.
Huh?
It's my seat.
7A.
"Seat 7A"
I'm sorry.
The bus is leaving soon.
Please be seated.
"Kotohira station"
Good bye, Shikoku.
Good-bye, me.
I didn't know anything.
"Sanuki Express"
The light will turn out soon.
Urara, where are you?
Huh? I am on the bus.
What? Come back.
Impossible.
Can you try to keep it down please?
I'm sorry.
Thanks.
Can I talk?
I actually have a father.
I'm sure you do.
My mom said that he died.
I had believed what she said
for 15 years.
I told you that your dad had died
after we got divorced.
But he is alive.
I haven't told you about this
because I thought you wanted
to see him if you knew.
But I didn't want you to see him
because he is such a cruel man.
But you became 20.
So...
Actually, I became 19.
Not 20.
Your mom miscounted your age?
She is that kind of person.
Please return by the departing time.
People in TV go see their parents
once they know he or she is alive.
Before, I couldn't understand why
they wanted to see their parents.
I didn't care about birth parents.
But...
when it comes to me,
I want to see him.
So you are going to Tokyo
to see your father.
How could you know?
That's why you got on the bus.
But my mom doesn't know
where my dad is in Tokyo.
Huh?
Thanks.
My mom returned to Kotohira
with me when I was three
because she was too tired
to live with him.
All I remember about my dad is
his hand.
Push me more!
More!
In the countryside,
people live in a small world.
For example, I withdrew
all my savings from the bank
in order to go to Tokyo.
The bank teller was Asuka.
- Asuka?
- She was my classmate.
So what?
It's a small world.
I'm from Tokyo.
So I don't really understand.
You don't look like
people from Tokyo.
My mom is going to remarry.
Are you going to live with
your dad then?
I don't think I can find
my dad easily.
Tokyo is a big city.
All I know about him is
his name and his birthday.
He is Takuya Suzuki.
What an ordinary name!
I searched on the net but
look how many I hit.
What will you do if you find him?
Huh?
I may hit him.
Hit him?
I will hit him.
All right.
Let me help you find him.
No, thanks.
Why?
I don't think you are useful.
You...
Hey.
I am Daisuke Tamagawa.
What's your name?
Urara Saeki.
Urara?
U-ra-ra.
Kanji for "Beauty".
Is that Urara?
People say I'm cute
rather than beautiful.
Don't you think so?
Maybe.
One question.
Why were you crying
when I got on the bus?
You said that
you were from Tokyo.
I know why.
You were dumped by your girlfriend
and followed her.
And you were dumped again.
That's why you were crying
on the bus back to Tokyo.
Right?
Shut up.
The area in Tokyo
where fashionable girls live.
Hey! We are here.
It's Tokyo.
Good morning, everyone.
We will soon arrive at Shinjuku.
Please make sure that you
have all your belongings with you.
This is Tokyo.
Wow.
I made it.
Ok.
Let's get started.
Good morning.
One beef rice.
Big size with extra sauce.
I want miso soup, too.
Thank you.
Beef rice, regular with egg.
Are you ok with eating
beef rice alone?
In Tokyo, girls don't eat beef rice
alone?
Thank you for waiting.
Did you order big size?
Is that bad?
Not at all.
Let me eat.
Thanks.
Wait.
I will help you find
Takuya Suzuki.
No, thanks.
I'll do it by myself once settled.
Thank you.
What is it?
Thanks. Bye.
Thank you.
Were these on the net leased
in a day?
Yes.
Are you sure that there were
rentals like those?
Wasn't that false advertising?
No. We don't do such things.
I can't believe it.
You can't find any apartment
for that price in Shimokitazawa.
Please find it.
You better go to a local
small real estate company.
Our company is too big.
Thank you. Bye.
Ok.
Thank you very much.
"Shimokitazawa South Exit Avenue"
Hi. Do you know any
real estate agents around here?
Sorry, no.
Ok. Thanks.
Hello.
Hi.
I guess it's not your thing,
right?
Yeah.
Why don't you try new thing?
Ok?
Sure.
That's why I came to Tokyo.
From where?
From Kagawa, Shikoku.
You mean Udon?
That's how people think
about Kagawa.
Sorry.
It's ok. I love Udon.
Why don't you try them on?
Sure.
Let me keep it for you.
Thank you.
How is it?
Looks good.
It looks great on you.
You think?
- I'll buy and wear them.
- Ok.
Here is your bag.
Thanks.
Are you sure that it's 500 yen?
I wanted to clear the stock.
It doesn't look like a dead stock.
Thanks.
I have many dresses that
I wore only once.
You must be a fashion model.
Well...
Wow.
Beautiful legs.
I just heard that you are looking
for a real estate agency.
Yes.
I want to find an apartment today.
I don't want to pay for the hotel.
I see.
Turn left at that corner and
there is "Kadota Real Estate".
Why don't you go?
They found an apartment for me, too.
Thank you very much.
Take care.
There is a nice wind.
Does this let for 30,000 yen
a month?
Shh...
I will rent here.
Are you sure?
- You said that this is a rare rent.
- Yes.
This has no problem.
Actually... it does have a problem.
This is a stigmatized property.
What do you mean?
The former occupier...
used the door knob over there...
- Committed suicide?
- Yes.
I will show you another apartment.
- This is totally fine for me.
- Huh?
Can I move in from tonight?
Ok.
You have to put down a deposit
of 200,000 yen first
with a signature of
a guarantor.
- A guarantor?
- Yes.
Hi, Mom.
Can you be a guarantor?
Where are you, Urara?
I'm in Tokyo.
I heard that you withdrew
all your savings.
I knew Asuka would tell you.
Here is 621,000 yen.
Put it in an envelope and
hide it in the bottom of your bag.
She is violating the obligation
of secrecy.
Urara, are you opposed
to my remarriage?
Of course not.
I introduced Mr. Sasaki to you.
I want you two to be happy.
Then why did you go to Tokyo?
Is that because of your dad...
I need a guarantor to
rent this apartment.
No! Come home.
Can I rent here without guarantor?
No...
Please help me.
The loan company can be
a guarantor
if you pay about 30 per cent of
your rent every month.
Tokyo is a great place.
I will sign a contract.
I have money.
Let's go back to the office
and I'll explain about the contract.
Oh, no.
I put it in a bank envelop.
Miss?
FLAT OUT TOKYO GIRL
Excuse me.
Hello, again.
I lost it.
Lost what?
I put it in a bank envelop
and carried it in my bag.
Cash?
Yes. 620,000 yen.
That's a lot of money.
Where is it?
That was all money I had.
Are you sure you lost it here?
I put it in the bottom of
my bag.
I don't think I dropped it.
Try to remember.
What's this?
"Call me! Daisuke Tamagawa"
Excuse me.
Hello.
Who is it?
I took the same bus to Tokyo
and met you at the restaurant.
I remember you.
You found my number finally.
Yes. Finally.
That's good.
When do you want to go out with me?
As soon as possible.
I'm busy now.
Where are you?
I'll come to see you.
You are very active today.
I like that.
Just tell me where you are!
Excuse me.
Do you know a cafe "Tamagawa"
around here?
Tamagawa?
You mean "Tamariba"?
Tamariba?
It is the same kanji for Tamagawa,
but it's called Tamariba.
Ok.
Come with me.
Are you taking me there?
Tamariba is my home.
Are you the employer of
Daisuke Tamagawa?
Well, I am more like
a production director.
I don't think my son had
stolen your money.
But it was only your son who
came within a 50-centimetre radius
after I arrived at Tokyo.
He has been jobless since
he graduated university.
But he is not a bad guy who steals.
I've never raised him
in such a manner.
But...
This way.
Hum... Hello.
Thank you.
- Where is Daisuke?
- Supermarket.
Thank you.
Are you sure that
he is coming back?
Are you the one he met
in the bus?
My brother said he would be back
so please wait here.
Hey, wait.
Sit down and
have a cup of coffee.
- Mika! Bring some coffee.
- Ok.
She is Joanna from France.
Bonjour.
I came to Japan to study
Japanese anime.
She is unique...
It's cute.
Henry from Canada.
He looks Japanese, but he isn't.
Fashion model?
That's like Tokyo.
There are many fashion models.
She is Urara Saeki.
Urara?
Yes. Kanji means beauty.
Urara is a cute name.
My dad named me.
Your cafe is very international.
I am leasing a flat
only for foreign customers.
Are they sharing a flat?
Shige-san is really nice.
They call me Shige-san.
Shige?
It's ok, Dad.
I'm back.
I bought some cakes.
She is Udval, a foreign
student from Mongolia.
Mongolian?
Hello.
How are you?
What's wrong?
You look like someone I know.
That's interesting, isn't it?
Do you want to see my room?
I know you do.
Try this on.
You look so cute.
Come with me.
You can be a Mongolian.
I brought her a cup of coffee.
Awesome.
Look here.
Urara.
- Yamamoto...
- Shh.
Yes.
Here.
I remember this.
Yes?
When did you become a Mongolian?
No, I'm just pretending.
Why?
The rent is very cheap.
And the owner is a good cook.
You are clever.
Don't tell them.
But why do you pretend to be
a Mongolian?
I love Asashoryu.
Hey, are you a friend of Udval?
Huh?
No, I'm not.
I like this place.
I wish I can live here.
Sorry. Foreigners only.
Why?
She lost her fortune.
Why do I have to work right
after coming back from Shikoku?
Give me back.
What?
When you put a piece of paper
in my bag, you stole my money.
It was you who stole.
Huh?
You stole my heart.
Just kidding.
That wasn't funny.
It's not a joke, Daisuke.
She says she is going
to the police.
What do you think I stole?
621,000 yen.
I put it in an envelope of
Kagawa Mirai Bank.
Did you put it in your bag?
Don't play innocent.
I am not a magician.
What do you mean?
Do you think I could steal it
in a second at the restaurant?
If I stole it, I wouldn't leave
my number in your bag,
pick up your call, and
ask you to come to my house.
It seems that her misunderstanding
has been cleared up.
How could she think that
I stole her money?
She doesn't know what to do.
I am very sorry.
Huh?
Ouch.
I came to Tokyo and I failed
in five hours, huh?
"Mom"
It had to be that shop.
I'm glad you came back.
It was a luggage lifter
who stole your money.
Huh?
Excuse me.
She is also a victim.
I would like you to tell us
the situation after I finish this.
Can I ask your name?
Urara Saeki.
Kanji for beauty.
I am Hanako.
Kanji for brilliant.
We can make a word "splendid"
by putting our kanji together.
Right.
I'm sorry about this.
I remember that I was
keeping your bag when you changed.
I shouldn't have put it in here.
It's not your fault.
It was a luggage lifter.
Thanks.
I wish the thief is arrested
and I can get my money back.
You need money, don't you?
That's the money to get around
in Tokyo.
Thanks to your information,
I found a nice apartment.
That's great.
But you can't live there
without paying rent.
Right.
Is there anyone who can help you?
Give me a second.
Is there anything wrong?
No.
Wait here.
It's me. Hanako.
Come in.
What is this place?
Um...
Just come with me.
Over here.
Hello.
Wait here.
Hi. How are you?
I appreciate your help.
I took her here.
Have a seat.
Excuse me.
As I explained over the phone,
she lost her money because of me.
I want you to give her a hand.
- But...
- It's ok.
Are you a high school student?
I graduated.
Where are you from?
From Kagawa.
Why did you come to Tokyo?
I got mad at my mom.
She is a runaway girl.
No, I'm not.
Please listen.
- Yesterday was my 19th birthday.
- Anyway...
- Thank you.
- Not for you.
Will you lend me this?
No.
I want to buy something from you.
Buy what?
Your underwear.
What are you talking about?
How about 10,000 yen?
Mr. Suzuki.
You must be joking.
In Tokyo, you will have a bad
experience like today.
Give up the money that was stolen.
You learnt a lot.
No.
Why did you trust her?
You met her today, right?
You followed her without
any suspicion.
What if I am a gangster
who preys on women?
I could be a murderer.
No, you are not.
Mr. Suzuki...
Don't underestimate Tokyo.
No, I don't.
Give me a second.
What are you doing, Urara?
I decided to live in Tokyo.
I need money.
Go back home.
Your parents must be worrying.
No.
Why?
There is no place for me
in my hometown.
I am looking for my dad.
What do you mean?
My dad left my mom and I
15 years ago.
He is somewhere in Tokyo.
Really?
What do you want to do
if you find him?
I want to hit him.
Oops.
Excuse me.
Wait.
She called you Urara.
Is that in Hiragana?
No. I have a kanji
for beauty.
Not many people can read
it "Urara".
- What's your surname?
- Saeki.
What's wrong?
Huh?... Nothing.
I don't want your underwear.
Pick up this money and
go back to Kotohira.
No.
Sorry about that.
My office called me.
Please take good care of her.
Sorry, but I have to go now.
See you later.
Did you just say Kotohira?
You don't have to pay me back.
Just go home.
You said Kotohira.
Sakurai. She is going back
to Shikoku. Give her a ride.
Yes.
Push my back again.
Go home.
Let's go.
Push it again.
Where are you going?
Shikoku. I was told to drive
you back home.
I thought you would take me
to Tokyo station.
I am responsible to drive you
back to Shikoku.
Stop here.
No, I can't.
Hey!
Are you insane?
Don't act stupid.
No.
You called him Mr. Suzuki, right?
Is his first name Takuya?
So what?
Check my father's name.
Takuya Suzuki?
He is my father.
No doubt.
I knew it at the moment
he touched my back.
Is he remarried?
He is single.
He hadn't been married again
after he divorced my mom?
I don't know.
Tell me about my dad.
No. I can't talk about him
anymore.
I have been looking for
my father since I was a child.
I went to Hokkaido with my mom
when I heard that he was there.
I went to Okinawa, as well.
I found him finally.
I just want him to call my name
and give me a hug.
Mr. Sakurai.
Please help me.
No...
Force of tears doesn't
work for me.
Mr. Sakurai.
No.
Mr. Suzuki is a lawyer working on
false charge, public nuisance,
lawsuit on adverse drug and so on
trying to impair human dignity.
That's all I can say.
Mr. Sakurai, you are
a good man.
But is my dad really a good man?
He asked you to sell
your underwear...
... because he is worrying
about you from his heart.
Then why didn't he admit
that he is my father?
I don't know what he is thinking.
I would never be in his shoes,
but if I left my daughter and
she found me after 15 years,
I would give her a big hug
no matter what.
Mr. Sakurai.
Do you have a daughter?
Yes. I got divorced and
have a 4-year-old daughter.
Are you raising her?
Yes.
Then you should understand
how a daughter longs for her father.
Y... Yes.
Please avenge my wife's death.
I understand how you feel.
But your wife vomited blood
before...
Hello.
I'm back.
Excuse me for a moment.
Sakurai. How was it?
I drove her to Tokyo station.
Did she go home?
Yes. I warned her to stop
stalking behaviour,
and she took Shinkansen...
Good job.
Sorry about that.
So your wife vomited blood
because...
He doesn't talk about
his private life.
But I know that he goes to
the gym three times a week.
Hello, Mr. Takuya Suzuki.
You look beautiful as always.
Thank you.
Hello.
Please go
if you are not buying.
Miyuki Nakajima?
Yes?
Wow. Tokyo is great.
Hello.
Can I see inside?
Sure.
We have a trial lesson.
I didn't bring anything.
We have rental wears and shoes.
Jump and jump.
Step forward.
Up and down.
Jump and jump. Step back.
Are you ok?
Let's cool down.
Please walk.
Get some water.
Mr. Suzuki.
You left this behind.
Thanks.
Are you busy this weekend?
No.
I booked the hotel
you wanted to stay.
That's nice of you.
Thank you.
I'll go swim.
Ok. See you later.
- Hello.
This was my first time.
I became a fan of you.
Thanks.
Can I ask you something?
Sure.
Is he your boyfriend?
How long have you been dating
with him?
I can't answer
that kind of question.
Thank you very much.
Hello, Ryota?
What do you want for dinner?
I'll cook whatever you like, Ryota.
Ryota?
Thank you for coming.
Please watch your step.
He has dinner with executives of
companies he works for as a lawyer.
It's a part of his job.
Don't get in here.
Please.
- Look over there.
- What?
He goes to a bar "Chaconne"
in the night.
Does he go there every night?
No. Only when the owner Haruka
called him.
Hi.
Do you want a trial?
Trial?
Do you want to work here?
Hello.
Who is Haruka?
Wait here.
Haruka.
She wants a trial.
Are you Haruka?
Yes?
You are beautiful.
If you want a trial,
you have to do your hair.
You can use our dress.
You look different.
Ok.
Thanks.
What name do you want?
Huh?
A professional name.
Call me Rei.
Kanji for beauty.
Go to the table over there.
Am I going to sit next to
the customer?
Yes. That's your job.
Didn't you watch TV drama?
Most of them wouldn't say no
if you ask them for alcohol.
Drink champagne
as much as you can.
No, I am underage.
Anyway.
She is a new staff. Rei.
Hello.
Sit down here.
Do you leave me here?
Thank you for champagne.
You came finally.
I thought I would die.
Look.
What are you doing?
Can I order another bottle of
champagne?
Sure. Just leave us alone.
Cheers to our new staff, Rei.
Please.
What are you doing in here?
Do you know her?
- Dad.
- I know her dad.
Come with me.
Why are you here?
Just a coincidence.
You know who I am, don't you?
I don't know.
I want to hit you.
Go back to Kotohira.
I will, only if you admit
that you are my father.
I don't know.
- Ok. Let me talk to everyone.
- Listen!
Are you all right, Rei?
I have to go.
Bring my bag.
Bring his bag.
I'll go then.
No. This is your job.
- Here is his bag.
- Thanks.
Go back to your table.
Listen.
She is a habitual liar.
Be careful.
See you.
Can I see you again soon?
Yes.
- Happy birthday.
- Thank you.
Happy birthday.
Shige-san, Mika,
thank you for such a great party.
Please leave a message
after the tone.
What is she doing?
Do you have a crush on her?
Huh?
You can't get her.
How rude!
See? I don't think you can
handle that kind of girl.
Shut up.
You better find a girlfriend
before you start looking
like dad.
How dare you!
"Skylight tower Azabu"
Hello.
It's me. Can I talk now?
Yes.
Sakurai! You told her
that I go to Chaconne often.
Um...
That can't be coincidence.
No, I didn't.
You didn't tell her my apartment,
did you?
N... No.
It wasn't her.
Hello.
Hello. Are you ok?
It's late.
I know.
Did you see a girl I saw earlier?
A girl?
She said she is Urara Saeki.
Ah... She went back to her hometown.
It's automatically locked.
There is no way I can open it.
Darn it!
Maybe I'll stay her tonight.
That'll be nice.
No. I'll go home.
Too early.
Have some wine.
Is she in relationship with him?
Did you leave something?
How did you enter?
It's Sakurai. Right?
Don't blame Mr. Sakurai.
You are wrong to kick me out, Dad.
Dad?
You must remember me.
Do you admit that
you are my father?
Yes.
But I truly think that
you should go home.
Because you think I am troublesome.
No.
You will become dirty
if you stay in Tokyo.
I can understand well
because I saw how you are doing.
Now I also understand why
mom didn't say that you are alive.
What do you mean?
You met your daughter for
the first time in 15 years.
And you tried to kick me back home.
I want to hit you.
Ok. Hit me.
After you and my mom
got divorced,
or even before you got divorced,
she had had a hard time.
I married your mom when
I kept failing bar examination.
She took care of us
while working at the hair salon.
But we both got tired.
You were bad.
But I wanted her to wait a little
longer to make my dream come true.
You grew up.
I have never forgotten about you,
Urara.
- A liar.
- Look.
Are you kidding me?
Why didn't you come to see me?
Because your mom didn't want
to see me.
Still, you should have come to
see me, or call me.
Even you thought about me,
I knew nothing.
You kept this picture to
make an excuse.
That's not true.
Urara...
You said I can hit you.
That was too strong.
Go home.
What?
It's too late for Shinkansen
or express bus.
Let me book a hotel.
Let me hit you again.
Why are you trying to kick me out?
Your mom must be worrying.
She will remarry.
There is no place for me.
But you can't live with me.
I know.
Because your girlfriends visit here.
I thought so.
You and Hanako are in relationship.
I am single.
Ms. Okuno, a gym instructor,
and Haruka at Chaconne also
come to see you, right?
You must be busy.
Hey!
But Dad...
You are deceived.
What do you mean?
Ouch.
Ms. Okuno has another boyfriend.
Haruka thinks you are
nothing but a customer.
She told me to ask you
for champagne.
Hanako was very nice to me,
but she must have a reason to do so.
Don't interfere in my affairs.
Will you let me stay here
if I don't?
No.
Wait.
What's this?
Garbage collection is only
once a week.
Do you always eat out?
Yes.
Hey.
You drink every night.
So what?
Don't you do laundry?
I'll do on weekend.
You have a date on this weekend.
- Don't enter!
- What's this?
It's an indictment.
Don't touch it.
- Stay out of this room, ok?
- What's this?
Dad.
You have to improve your eating
habit and your sex life.
- Improve?
- You can't be happy otherwise.
Happy?
Dad.
Are you happy now?
I am sleepy.
I forgot about that.
I couldn't sleep in the bus.
I am tired because I did exercise.
Good night.
What are you talking about?
It stinks.
Is this how father smells?
Hey... Hello?
Don't sleep here.
I need to go to a bathroom.
I feel much better.
Dad.
I will make you happy.