Dad.
What?
Hanako-san, Okuno-san,
or Haruka-Mama.
Which is your love interest?
Why do I have to spell it out?
Did you know? I invited them.
All three of them.
They're heading this way now.
Hey, hey, what did you just do?
Prepare yourself.
You've got to be kidding!
Wait, how did you contact
all three of them?
I know Hanako-san's number.
Haruka-Mama's too.
How about Fuyu?
How did you contact Okuno-san?
I used your phone to text her!
Remember to take it with you.
Give it back.
No!
It's locked.
It's your birthday
so I figured it out right away.
It's a crime to--
If you manipulate other phones!
That's a lie.
If I break it, it might be a crime
but texting won't count as a crime.
Wrong.
You said in a magazine, didn't you?
"For an act to be a crime,
it has to be punished
by the authority of the nation.
Concerning every deleted voice mail,
there won't be enough cops
to deploy!"
Yes, but texts are different.
Documents can be forged.
- Dad!
- What?
I'll ask you one more time.
Hanako-san, Okuno-san,
or Haruka-Mama,
which do you really love?
Hey, what about the text issue?
I date who I like.
How did you meet Hanako-san?
Why do I have to explain it to you?
I just want to help
make up your mind.
That's unnecessary.
What does a model and lawyer
have in connection?
Oh, Dad, you're a corporate lawyer,
aren't you?
And Hanako-san did a commercial
for that corporation!
You saw that and fell for her.
So you invited her to dinner...
That's not true. I didn't ask them.
You didn't refuse either!
Why would I refuse?
- So dirty!
- Oh, come on.
Chaconne's Haruka-Mama,
you met her five years ago
in Roppongi, right?
That's right.
Didn't you meet Fuyu Okuno-san
five years ago as well?
You met her in Hamamatsu,
didn't you?
When you were there
for investigating a case,
You met Okuno-san
at the sports club.
In spite of that, you often go back
to Tokyo to see Haruka-Mama?
So what?
So you're now giving
that attitude?
Write that in a magazine,
a lawyer's true colours!
Lewd, perverted, liar, smelly feet,
and snores a lot!
I don't snore!
My feet don't smell.
Go ahead.
Magazines aren't on my reach
but I can write them on the net!
Even on the net,
you can be sued for libel.
- Even it's the truth?
- That's right.
Conversation's getting off track!
The main problem
is you're a three-timer!
- Well, then, then...
- What? What?
Was cheating part of the reason
of your divorce with mum?
It was not!
No, that's the only thing
I can think of!
Hey! No!
No. What are you up to?
I'll cancel.
Hey, hey.
- Hey.
- Never mind.
Who arrived first?
Hey, wait.
Hi.
Haruka-Mama!
Hurry and open up.
Wait a moment, I'll go down.
I'd like to go to the toilet.
- Ah, right there, if you--
- Enough!
I'll let it out, seriously.
"Open"
Hey, hide yourself!
Why?
Not "why," get a clue!
But I arranged this.
Just hide!
Very well.
You might need to clean up.
Ah, hot, hot!
Hello?
It's Hanako. Sorry for being late,
I'll be arriving soon.
No, no, not at all.
You don't need to come here. Hello?
Sensei, I'm coming in.
Hi.
Toilet, toilet.
Hot, hot, hot!
"FLAT OUT TOKYO GIRL"
What were you doing?
No, nothing at all.
Mama, you should've called me.
I did, but couldn't get through.
Something change?
No, might be your imagination?
Where's Rei-chan?
No way she's here.
But she said you have something
urgent to tell me so I came here.
Mama! Sorry for the trouble.
She's here.
Right.
What is this urgent matter?
Actually, Takuya Suzuki is my father
Friend, correct?
Dad is dating other women.
That's right, this girl's father.
Mama, my father is...
Okay, then! That hurt.
What?
What's wrong with you two?
Got a call.
It's from the club. Hello?
Ah Mama, excuse me
but Fuji-san just called.
Seems he'll be here soon.
Got it, I'll be back soon.
An important customer's coming.
Got to go.
No, no, no.
It has to be now.
That's why I called you here.
Mama, you'd better go back.
Don't disappoint him.
Mama, there's someone
I'd like you to meet.
A girl who'd like to work
in Chaconne.
In that case, you let her come
for an interview.
No, she'll be here any second.
- Who is?
- Like I said...
Mama, you can leave
this matter to me.
Hurry and go back to the club.
You're acting strange.
Well, then, see you again.
Dad's dating other women...
My friend. My friend that is.
So that's how it is with you two?
What?
See you then.
She somewhat misunderstood.
Looks like it.
This is not a joke.
I would never with a 19 year old.
Wait, didn't you met Mama
when she was 19?
Ah, it's Hanako-san!
What should we do?
I know you're there. Open up.
- We need to let her...
- No, no...
Pretending to be not home?
Thanks!
What just happened?
Haruka-Mama must've...
Excuse me.
Yes?
Oh, my, please let them pass
each other without incidents.
Will things work out easily
in your favour?
Are you a tenant in this building?
Yes, an acquaintance of mine is.
Excuse me.
I think it's okay.
It's not okay!
Okuno-san's coming up.
Okuno-san doesn't know
you have other women, right?
I understand. I'll straighten
things out. Satisfied?
Straighten what?
Narrow it down. So hide!
I don't want to.
Now that Mama left,
you can't bring them together
anymore.
Just telling Okuno-san is pointless.
No, I don't think so.
Okay, then, I'll tell you who's
my true love interest to you, Urara.
When?
- Near future.
- When's that?
Near future.
- Tomorrow?
- That'd be...
- Next week?
- The week after?
- Maybe after...
I can't trust you.
Wait a minute!
Anyway, tell Okuno-san the truth.
I need to pick Ryota up soon,
so I don't have much time.
Let's go outside.
What? Where do you mean by outside?
That hurts!
Hey, wait, something the matter?
Well, sort of.
Going out in those clothes?
Yeah, sort of.
Where are we going?
Sort of...
What?
No use.
No, let's run!
What?
Come on.
I'm fine inside your room.
Hey, what is it? What?
Hey! Why the emergency stairs?
It's an emergency.
What is?
No, that's not it.
Recently,
I haven't been to the gym so I was
thinking of not using the elevator.
- What?!
- Okay, then. Let's go.
Hey, it's dangerous!
What's wrong with you?
Sensei, I'm coming in.
Good evening.
Where's Sensei?
He ran away.
He ran away?
Yeah.
Did you tell him
that I knew about you?
No, not yet.
Hanako-san.
Do you really love my father?
What's this all of a sudden?
Well, I thought of telling you this,
but...
No, on second thought,
I won't tell you.
What is it?
You feel something's not right,
don't you?
That's why about my Dad...
I'm confused on things.
Is that Dad's fault?
I may be at life's crossroad.
It's my own problem.
I'm at an age
when I need to think things.
Like my work.
So Dad's not part of this?
No, I enjoy talking with Sensei
and he helps me out many times.
What about other women?
I forgot to bring a key. Open up.
Good evening.
What? So you came, huh.
Did you open the door for me?
Who else would open it?
No one.
What's the matter?
No, nothing.
Did you start living with someone?
What?
In this room.
No, no, no.
That doesn't count
as an answer, though.
Ah I thought of starting to learn
to cook for myself.
So I tried to make various things
so it ended up like this.
You started eating sweets too.
Yeah, been craving for sweets
lately. Maybe I'm just tired.
Did something happen
to make you tired?
Torture him more.
Right, that's right.
What about outside of work?
Oh, I'm totally fine!
Oh, right, right. Shall we go
somewhere else?
That nearby cafe again?
Yes. No, I mean somewhere else.
That Italian place that closes late.
I'm not hungry.
Sensei, I'll stop meeting you
for a while.
What? What's wrong?
See you.
Hey, wait.
Hey, hey,
you said something to her?
No, I was hiding there.
I see.
Dad.
Just now, did you get dumped?
I don't think so.
Hey, wait.
Tell Hanako-san everything.
No, no, Okuno-san
is waiting at the cafe.
Shouldn't you chase
after Hanako-san?
Chasing her is useless.
But you like her.
Like I said, Okuno-san is waiting.
I don't get it. What you're
thinking, I don't get it!
That should be my line.
You called all of them.
Stay out of my private life.
I'm tired of hearing that!
You make me say it.
Come on, Dad!
Please nurture your love
with the woman you truly love!
Mind your own business!
Your daughter is pleading
with you,
won't you listen?
Then don't trouble your dad.
I just want to make you happy.
One more shenanigan
and I'll kick you out.
Is that so? I understand.
I'll move out of here!
Fine, go ahead and leave!
Goodbye!
Hello? What was that "goodbye"?
You're planning to say that to me?
No, no, that's not it.
I'll be right there.
Too late, I already left the cafe.
I'm on my way.
I get it now.
Tada!
The unknown love affairs
of Daisuke!
Yay!
Wait a minute. Hey. Wait.
Anyway, what's with that make up?
It all started when...
when Aki-san dumped him
in which started his misfortunes.
Joanna, you're good!
Though I thought they were
pretty a good couple.
Stop it.
Then Daisuke followed Aki-chan
back to her hometown.
However, he came home rejected.
Aki!
But on the return bus,
he met Urara-chan.
But since then, it's all a series
of rejections for him, right?
Hey, what is that drawing?
Nice one!
Next, he fell in love
with an older woman.
Oh, she really looks her!
Why? Why do you know her?
Didn't you mention her?
The girl you were about
to have dinner with,
but she went to Hakone.
And here comes the instructor
from the fitness club!
She looks like Okuno-san.
But it was done fast.
Well, of course it was.
He found out she was older
and had a kid, didn't he?
He gave up quickly.
Next is a Mama from a club
in Roppongi.
It does look like her.
The end.
Finished?
That was good.
How far did you go with her?
I gave up on her.
We live in different worlds.
So you going to go for Urara now?
Who knows.
You don't know?
It's her I don't understand.
She came to Tokyo to find her dad,
she found him but didn't,
and Okuno-san's kid
is her brother, she said.
So what? You cannot like somebody
after knowing her details.
It's got to be, got to be true love.
You don't have a chance, though.
Shut up. Geez.
Urara!
Good morning.
- Morning.
- Good morning!
What? You spend the night here?
Do I have to notify you every time?
It's on the contract, only tenants
can spend the night here.
Is that so?
Why are you mad?
Want to eat breakfast?
Yes, please.
Just a moment.
What happened?
I'm mad.
About what?
Arrogance of men.
You mean her boyfriend?
Sort of similar to it, right Urara?
What do you mean?
You probably have
romantic feelings for him.
No, no, that's not it.
Urara, you're jealous
of those woman.
Jealous?
Who is he?
I haven't met him. You see...
Give me a break!
He's playing three women.
Three women?
No, I'm sure he has more!
He has no decency.
What a jerk.
That's why I have to do something.
Why?
Because only I can.
Just break up.
Well, it's love because
you can't break up.
Miku, don't tell me you have
someone like that.
Generally speaking!
Besides, I'm still a virgin.
Really?
Parent and child conversations
have evolved in Japan.
Shige-san.
Should I lend a hand?
Won't be necessary.
Can I stay in Senpai's...
That's Udval.
I mean Udval-senpai's room.
Can I stay there in the meantime?
I don't mind.
Okay, breakfast is ready.
You can't miss this chance.
What do you mean by "chance"?
Oh, nothing.
How long will stay here?
I don't know yet. I wonder will I be
able get out of here.
Don't let her, okay?
Time to eat.
"T. Suzuki Law Firm"
I beg of you, please bring
my daughter back.
I tried talking to them many times.
But my daughter participated
on her own will...
and that she was refusing to see me.
I can't even talk to her directly.
Have reported this to the police?
Yes, but...
They won't do anything.
Sensei...
Please!
Thank you.
Time to eat.
What's wrong? Don't want to eat?
Ah well, Sensei, we can accept
that man's request, can't we?
Yes.
I'm glad. I was worried a bit there,
since you didn't gave him
an immediate answer. I'll eat now.
I can understand the reasoning.
No, maybe I should say
I can understand it in my mind.
What?
A father's love for his daughter.
But you have Urara-san, don't you?
We've been apart for 15 years.
We're like strangers.
Honestly, I don't know what to do.
I guess so.
But I don't sense her tendency
to hesitate at all.
She naturally calls me "Dad"
and she butts in my business.
Well, you consider yourself
blessed, you know.
If you'd been living together
all these years,
she's be treating you like
an old rag by now.
- Rag?
- Yes.
"Don't do my laundry with Dad's."
"Mind your own business.
I don't want to talk to you.
You're gross!"
I hear they say things
like that repeatedly.
It's puberty. An age when
they become rebellious.
It's the passage from childhood
to adulthood, but...
Right now, Hitomi still says
"I love you, Papa,"
and snuggles with me.
But in 10 years, I'm afraid
she'll say those things to me.
That'll be the end of me
if she does.
Your daughter is pleading
with you,
why won't you listen?
Come on, Dad!
Please nurture your love
with the woman you truly love!
"Hanako Serizawa"
Happy, happy, yes!
That's it. Okay!
Good work!
You're both done now.
Thank you.
Thank you very much. Good work.
"Suzuki-sensei"
Your call is being redirected
to voice mail.
Serizawa-san!
Yes?
Someone wants to see you.
Do you know any Saeki-san?
Cute.
Yes.
Saeki-san! Saeki-san!
Sorry about what happened yesterday.
After I asked you to come.
Not at all. It was fun.
Oh, you mean?
You weren't being serious?
About not meeting Sensei
for a while?
That's right.
Of course, I want just wanted
to torment him a little.
I'm glad.
I want to make my father happy.
I want him to get married.
It'll be his second time though.
That's what I wish for right now.
I think Hanako-san
is Dad's true love.
In order to confirm that,
I asked you to come yesterday.
"True love"?
I mean...
Well, I expected as much.
Who else is going out with him?
Let's see, a sports club instructor
and a club's Mama.
But that's only within
what I know of though.
There might be others.
If you're his true love,
will you get married with my father?
Do we have to get married?
Not necessarily, but...
I want him to change
his sloppy lifestyle.
Sensei still doesn't understand
how I feel, does he?
It's going very slowly.
As I thought, I won't be meeting
with Sensei for a while.
What? Why is that?
The time he spends with me,
he can spend it with you, right?
It hasn't been long
since you got reunited.
Your priority should be taking back
the 15 years you've spend apart.
And you do that, he should
understand your feelings.
Hanako-san, I love you.
Thank you.
Kick! That's it. Kick, kick! Yes.
Everyone, smile! Yes, that's it.
Good evening.
Is Okuno-san on leave?
I think she's by the pool.
Thank you.
Refrain from diving please.
Sorry about last night.
Should we stop seeing each other?
Not you too.
"Not you, too"?
No, never mind.
It's tough having a child, isn't it?
Don't say that
and spend time with me.
I'm talking about you.
Urara-chan.
What do you mean by that?
Didn't you show me
her picture before?
Did I?
You're living with her right now,
right?
That's why you wouldn't let me
in your room last night.
Don't mind about me,
so please be a father to Urara-chan.
"Urara"
"Roppongi St."
Thank you calling, this is Chaconne.
Ah, Suzuki-sensei. Are you coming?
No, I was wondering if Rei-chan
is coming to work.
Yes, she's here now.
I see.
Sensei?
Yes.
Sorry for the intrusion yesterday.
"Intrusion"?
You're misunderstanding, Mama.
On what?
I don't have that relationship
with Ura, Rei-chan.
What do imply by saying that?
Well, like I said...
Oh, should I pass
the phone to her, then?
You don't have to.
Like I said...
I'm busy. See you.
Mama!
You startled me. What is it?
Mama, you're misunderstanding.
About you and Sensei?
That's right.
I'm not misunderstanding at all.
I totally get it.
No, that's what I mean
you misunderstanding.
Sensei is your father, isn't he?
Stop the act.
Of course I would notice.
I'm sorry.
Why are you apologising?
I wonder...
You wanted to tell me that
yesterday.
That's not it.
Oh, well.
Okay, back to work.
"Cafe Tamariba"
You call that an adult relationship?
You startled me!
Welcome back.
Why are you here?
Why don't you quit
working at the club?
- Why?
- "Why" you say, look...
Men would seduce you,
and you would be in danger.
I'm not worried. Not at all.
Don't tell me you're being
forced to work?
Why is that?
Well, for a guy.
Ah, it's the same for you?
What is?
Would you go out
with several woman at once?
Not me. I can't take on
more than one at a time.
Really? You liked Hanako-san,
didn't you?
Okuno-san and Haruka-Mama as well.
Why do you know?
From Joanna's picture story.
Men are all the same, right?
No, I'm the faithful type.
There are times I'm forced to flip.
You mean you get
reluctantly dumped, right?
Well, that's normal.
I'm quite righteous, you know.
You could say that.
Urara-san, I like you!
Yeah, I know. I know.
Good night.
Hey, hey, that hurts.
What was that about?
What happened?
I can't tell.
What? She left home?
Yes. It's been two days
since she left home.
Aren't you worried?
I'm not worried.
But I'm worried.
She won't answer the phone?
Excuse me.
Good morning.
Please have a seat.
If it's Urara-san,
please leave her to me.
- I'm counting on you.
- Sure.
Good morning.
Excuse me.
Thank you.
It's a nice place.
How's that guy doing?
He's very worried about you.
Are you really sure?
Why won't you pick up his calls?
Who's he?
I don't know. Her boyfriend maybe?
He looks like a diligent man.
I understand what happened, but...
that's been Sensei's lifestyle
since he got divorced.
That's why I...
There are things you can't quit
though you know you should.
Things like sneaking snacks
and smoking?
Is that the same thing?
You can't force a person to quit
if that person doesn't want to.
I should make him want to quit,
then?
That's right.
It might take some time though.
Don't you think it's better to stay
by him instead of moving out?
You think so?
But I don't know how to face him
when I get back.
I understand.
Let's have Sensei come get you.
There's no way he'd come!
Well, you can leave it to me.
"Cafe Tamariba"
The guy earlier isn't back yet.
Maybe he left?
Hey, who was that man earlier?
Sakurai-san.
Not his name. What is he?
While studying for his bar exam,
he's working in a law firm?
That's not what I mean.
I don't know how to answer you then.
In other words, what is he to you?
This conversation is annoying.
You don't get me at all.
What should I do?
How do I make you understand?
Speak Japanese.
Like I said, what are you mad at?
I said it before, what I'm mad at...
He's quite an old man.
What are you doing?
Let's go home.
Hey, you're not even apologising.
Why must I apologise?
Wait a minute.
So it's you?
What?
Aren't you ashamed at your age?
Leeching on women,
do you have any shame?
Leeching you say?
Leeching?
Daisuke is?
Move.
Of the three, who do you choose?
Deal with that later.
We're going home.
Hey, hey!
Don't ever come near Urara
ever again.
No, he was kind to me.
That's how men exploit you!
Enough of this!
Dad!
"Dad"?
Yes. He's my father.
Takuya Suzuki?
That's right.
Why does he know my name?
This is bad.
Why?
Here, Dad.
I said it hurts!
All you can do is ice it, right?
Sakurai, he's fired.
Sakura-san must've lied
to make you come get me.
Yeah. Urara is living with
a good-for-nothing guy he said.
That's why you came for me, right?
If you hooked up
with a bad guy in Tokyo,
I couldn't face your mother.
What is it?
Nothing.
You're creeping me out.
I won't interfere
with your love life anymore.
I'm glad to hear that,
but what's with that laugh?
I thought of being
a two-timer as well.
What?
If I do that,
you'll even worry more.
What are you saying?
Don't you dare do it.
I'm not kidding.
If you lose confidence
And get discouraged
What's wrong, Papa?
What? Your Papa got scolded
by Sensei.
Did you do something wrong?
No, I did something good though.
Things didn't turn out
the way I expected.
Won't it be okay?
I see. I think it'll be okay.
If you lose confidence
And get discouraged
Just all the good things
Try to remember them
Don't worry, you were cool.
Even though
it was a misunderstanding.
I wanted to see
how cool Daisuke was.
Hey, was Urara impressed?
Who knows.
You got this, man!
Hang in there!
Okay, I understand.
I'll seriously go for it.
Oh, that's good.
Come on. We got to help him out now.
Yeah, yeah. Let's do this.
Yeah!
Let's go.
They're just having fun.
But it's fun.
My phone?
What's wrong?
No, it's nothing.
Who's it from?
I don't know.
Maybe Aki from Shikoku?
No way!
"Aki Ozaki"
Hello.
Daisuke-kun.
Yes?
What's up?
Where are you?
Kotohira.
I'm sorry.
I asked you to not call me
ever again,
but I'm the one who's calling.
No, it's actually fine with me.
Oh, hot pot again?
I smell something pungent.
Sorry for the wait!
Tada!
What is this red stuff?
Saeki Family Special Hot Pot
Szechuan Style!
I've been wanting to make it
for you.
It's really good when you add udon
at the end.
Look, I have a cut inside my mouth.
I shouldn't eat spicy food.
Isn't it cold? Here.
If you eat this,
you'll be warmed up till morning.
Bon appetit.
Go ahead.
Time to eat!
Good?
Yeah, it is, but it hurts.
Didn't you make too much?
You think so?
Don't tell me you invited
someone again, did you?
I called up mum.
Why did you...?
Got you! I haven't even told her
about living with you.
It's from mum.
Yeah, right.
Hello, Mum, what's the matter?
Don't "what's the matter" me!
After I sent you your things,
you haven't called.
Are you doing fine?
I'm fine.
Ah, get some tissues.
Urara, is there someone
there with you?
Yes. Someone that really
takes good care of me.
Put him on.
If you say so.
She wants to talk.
Urara, don't tell me...
You're with a strange...
Very strange man, are you?
What?
- Urara!
- I'll call you again.
Hey! I have my own thoughts...
What?
You can't just hang up.
I don't want anyone to bother
my precious time with dad.
Let's eat.
Come on, eat up, eat up. It's good.