Ouch!
What is it?
Why are you sleeping in here?
I feel sorry.
Why didn't you let me
sleep in bed then?
Both of us can sleep here.
Hey!
She lied that she had a business
trip to Hakone.
She goes to a hotel in Akasaka
to get a job.
That's enough.
Hanako really went to Hakone.
Do you know what this means?
I made a lot of fuss for nothing.
Exactly.
Please leave a message
after the tone.
Hello.
Hi, Hanako.
It's Urara.
I shouldn't have done what I did
yesterday.
I am sorry.
Bye.
Ok.
Is that Hanako?
She should be in Hakone.
Hello.
Is this Mr. Suzuki?
Yes.
I have a package for Rin Saeki,
Room 1103.
Urara Saeki, not Rin. Come in.
Rice cooker, food processor,
frying pan...
I wanted those.
What?
Made in France.
Mom wanted them.
That's all. Please sign here.
Ok.
That's my seal.
Is this ok?
Thanks.
Thank you.
How do you know where my seal is?
Bring that one.
It's heavy.
How did you pay?
I put it on your office tab.
- I won't pay for these.
- Why not?
You didn't ask me.
I needed those.
I had 620,000 yen.
I put it in my bank.
I'll sue you on a charge of
embezzlement if you use it.
I just ate Udon earlier.
We eat Udon at every meal
in Kotohira.
- Everyone?
- Yes.
Liar.
It's delicious if you add this.
Let's eat.
Ok.
See?
- By the way...
- Say something nice.
I excel by being praised.
Don't get carried away.
Coming.
Hello. Package delivery.
Come in.
Who is it?
Hey!
Rei Saeki?
- Not Rei.
- Sign here.
- My name is...
- Here.
My name is Urara.
- Thanks.
- Thank you.
Good.
Hey, what did you buy?
I bought only the things I need.
Be careful.
Sorry.
What is he doing?
I don't know.
What do you want to do?
I want to live happily as a family.
Honestly, I wished Mom and Dad
will get back together
and reunion as a family.
It's too late.
Right.
Mom will marry a man I found
and be happy ever after.
I will make you happy, too.
I asked you if you were happy
when I first met you.
Are you happy now?
You couldn't answer me.
An adult doesn't worry
if he is happy or not.
Men would envy you for
having three girlfriends,
But you don't know
what Hanako is thinking,
Okuno has a child,
and Haruka wants your money.
You are not happy at all.
How would you know?
I know.
Don't interfere in my privacy.
Again. I don't interfere in
your privacy. We are family.
You wouldn't like me to do the same.
Oh, yes, I do.
I want you to act like a father.
I'll act like a daughter.
How?
I don't know.
You don't know?
You left me alone for 15 years.
I had never acted as a daughter.
Of course I don't know.
You know a family in TV commercials,
go on a trip, eat something
and enjoy autumn leaves...
That's what I want.
A family trip?
Let's go to a hot spring
this weekend.
Sorry. I'm busy this weekend.
It's Ms. Okuno.
Are you busy this weekend?
I booked the hotel you wanted to go.
Thank you.
I'll come with you.
What will she do with Ryota?
Will she leave him with a babysitter
and go on a trip with you?
How nasty!
What are you thinking?
Many things.
Do you have a boyfriend?
- No.
- You are lying.
- Did you go out with anyone?
- No.
Don't lie. Tell me the truth.
Don't hide things from me.
I am your parent. Tell me.
See? You didn't like that.
I'm so excited.
Keep talking like a father.
I really didn't have a boyfriend.
I didn't want to go out with anyone.
It's a small world to
live in a small town.
Everyone knows about their ex.
My friends didn't care, but I did.
I want a boyfriend, of course.
But I have something to do.
What is it?
I have to make you happy, Dad.
Hello.
I want to ask you something.
Can we meet?
You do have a boyfriend.
No.
Who are you talking to?
You should have one or two
boyfriends.
He is not it.
What do you mean "one or two"?
Hello?
Who are you talking to?
Are you trying to deny me?
I am busy now.
W... Wait.
He got turned down again.
I guess so.
Dad.
Are you planning to remarry
with any of your girlfriends?
No.
Okuno has a son named Ryota.
Is he your child?
Ok.
FLAT OUT TOKYO GIRL
Thank you very much.
Hello.
I want a free trial.
I'm sorry. Free trial can
only be used once.
How much is it then?
3,000 yen, please.
It's expensive.
If you become a member,
it's 10,000 yen per month.
Daisuke Tamagawa
Hello. Can we meet?
Sure!
Where are you now?
Hey.
Why are you always
chasing after girls?
Who do you like now, Eisuke?
- A girl who went back to Shikoku?
- Aki.
A girl who came from Shikoku?
Urara.
None of them.
Hey.
Why don't you work?
I work here as a part-timer.
Why don't you find a full-time job?
You are annoying.
- Can I say something?
- I don't want a lecture.
Be nice to your brother.
We need wasteful things
in life sometimes.
Wasteful?
I met you mom because
I went out with many girls.
You were popular among girls
when you were young.
Yes, because I had more hair.
Hey.
You run a little
and are already out of breath.
You are out of shape.
I know.
Do exercise, then.
- Hey.
- Okuno, an instructor at the gym..
Wait.
You never listen to me.
What?
I have a question about Hanko.
Does she have a boyfriend?
Yes.
Really?
Go check about Okuno.
No.
You sure Hanako has a boyfriend?
Yes. Just go.
Hello.
Would you like to sign up?
Y... Yes.
Thank you.
Please fill out this form.
Push slowly...
How is it?
- Excuse me.
- Yes.
Do you know Ms. Okuno?
It's me.
Will you teach me how to
use the machine?
Sure. What's the purpose
of exercise?
Are you lack of exercise?
Do you want to go on a diet?
- For love.
- Huh?
I mean... I want to lose weight.
I don't think you need to.
Let's do some exercise
to build up muscles.
Let's go.
Please have a seat.
Good.
Excuse me.
Let me switch the weight.
Law Firm
Hello.
Hi. Your dad is still in the court.
I have a question for you, Sakurai.
About your dad?
Yes. And about Okuno.
Ryota's mom?
Did they meet at the gym?
I don't know.
I didn't know that they went
out together until you told me.
What type of person is Okuno?
Your dad said I told you about him
too much.
Come on. It's about Okuno.
You are annoying.
She is a good mom.
Have you seen Ryota's dad?
No, I heard that they got divorced.
Sakurai.
Yes.
I think Ryota is a son of my dad.
Huh?
Am I right?
No way.
Ryota is four, right?
Yes. Same as my daughter.
If they started dating
five years ago...
I started working here
five years ago.
He wasn't in Tokyo
most of the time then.
Huh?
He was working on a case in
Hamamatsu, Shizuoka
and he worked there
to collect the evidences.
Please look here.
Very nice.
Good.
This way, please.
Please look at me.
Ok.
Very well.
Let's go to the next location.
Yes.
Thank you.
I'll keep it for you.
Thanks.
Your cell phone was ringing.
Hi, Hanako.
It's Urara.
I shouldn't have done what I did
yesterday.
I'm sorry.
Bye.
What did she do?
He was waiting for me in Akasaka
and was hit by a girl whom
he doesn't know.
Did you know about that?
That was you, Urara.
I'm home.
Hi. What did you buy?
Do you want to know what it is?
- I don't care.
- Look.
What is it?
I became a member of a gym.
Why?
No need to ask.
It's a girl.
No. I needed to work out...
You said you don't like exercising
when I asked you to go to gym.
Did you fall in love with
an instructor?
Why?
It's easy to tell.
When will you be damped next?
Don't tease me.
Hello.
Hi.
Hey. How was it?
Fuyu Okuno.
Blood type A. She likes to swim.
I don't want that.
- You told me to check...
- What else?
She likes a sweet man
who is younger than she.
You are 24. How old is she?
26.
But she goes out with a man
who is older.
- What else?
- She is from Hamamatsu, Shizuoka.
Hamamatsu?
She came to Tokyo 3 years ago
after working at a local gym.
Which means she was in
Hamamatsu 3 years ago.
He was not in Tokyo
most of the time then.
He was working on a case
in Hamamatsu, Shizuoka.
So he worked there to
collect the evidences.
She said she worked hard
after she came to Tokyo.
Because she has a child.
Wait a minute.
What are you talking about?
A child? Older man?
Okuno has a child. She got divorced.
She is dating a man
who is older than her.
Really?
Yes.
Thanks anyway.
Bye.
Wait.
Huh?
What did she say?
It's over before it started.
Court
Hi.
Ok.
Get it.
Come on.
See?
Come.
Sit down.
Ready... go!
Here you go.
Push harder!
Harder!
Here you go.
Thank you for waiting.
Let's go.
Did you do it?
Ok.
I'm back.
Did you do it by yourself?
Show me.
Pump it up strongly.
Do it together.
Ready... go.
Ok.
Oops.
Why don't you turn the lights on?
Dad.
I need to talk to you.
Please sit down.
I am sitting.
I... I thought about many things.
Many junk things.
I wanted you to become happy.
I thought I would do anything
for you.
Then get out.
Yes, I will.
But...
I am leaving not because of you
but because of Ryota.
I was about Ryota's age
when you left me.
I had a reason...
I was so lonely.
I don't want Ryota to feel as I did.
Please live with Ryota and Okuno
in this apartment as a family.
Hey.
I will give you all the things
I bought.
I paid for those.
Dad. It was only a short while.
But I was happy to see you.
She will come back soon.
Good bye, Dad.
Hey.
Hello.
Let's go out.
Huh?
I am hungry.
I was about to go out to eat.
I bought snacks in Hakone.
I'm coming down.
Hi.
What's wrong?
Nothing.
- Huh?
- Let's go out.
Are you off tomorrow?
Let's go somewhere.
What are you doing?
- Are you in a bad mood?
- No.
- Shino.
- Yes.
Take Rei out.
She would say that again.
Ok.
I bought a new car.
Come with me, Rei.
Hey.
Please smile more.
I didn't want to do this today.
Please help us.
Rei is here.
Hi.
Don't you have a child?
You better go home and spend time
with your children
instead of drinking at a bar.
- Hey, what is she talking about?
- I am so sorry.
- You will break my arm.
- Come with me.
Get changed.
No.
I know I asked you to come and help,
but please go home.
I don't have a home.
Go to the internet cafe, then.
- Shimoyama.
- Yes.
Come when you are in a good mood.
What will you order?
I don't want anything.
Two coffee, please.
Ok.
Hey. You said you were hungry.
I am satisfied when I see you.
Is anyone in your room?
What?
Someone was there.
What is she doing now?
Who?
A girl from Shikoku.
I remember her.
I don't know what she is doing.
She said she was looking for
her dad.
Did she?
You were married before, right?
Do you have any children?
No.
If you had one, she or he would be
18 or 19 years old, right?
Maybe.
How was the trip to Hakone?
You want to change the topic.
Why do we have to talk about
a girl whom I don't know well?
I'll eat something.
It's heavy.
Let me put it in here.
Hanako and Okuno...
Will you give up?
But...
It's too soon to give up.
Take her from her boyfriend.
You are too aggressive.
She has a child.
It's handy. You don't have to
make your own, then.
I see.
It's fun to make your own.
Mika!
It's ringing.
Pick it up.
Hi, this is Tamariba.
Hi, Urara.
Hey.
Speaking.
Can I stay at your place tonight?
Are you sure?
Y... yes.
See you soon then.
- Why are you laughing?
- What is it?
Thanks.
Are you ok?
Hey.
- Hello.
- Wait.
What is it?
Let's go to the hotel
rather than staying here.
Huh?
I don't want you to stay here...
I mean... I wouldn't do anything.
I don't understand.
Hello.
You are so nasty.
Sorry to come this late.
Yuck.
You are nasty.
I don't get it.
Dad.
It was only a short while...
But I was happy to see you.
I see. You met your dad and
found out a lot of things.
Yes, Senpai.
I am not Senpai.
I am Udbal, Mongolian.
I thought I would go home.
Your mom is going to remarry.
I have no place at home.
One of the residents
will move out soon.
But this is only for foreigners.
Why don't you say that
you are Bhutanese?
You can be happy
if you are Bhutanese.
How about Vietnamese?
That's nice, too.
You look like Vietnamese.
Do I?
Eat Udon and tell them
that it's pho.
Will that work?
But...
Even you left home,
I don't think your dad will live
with that instructor and her son.
You are right.
Then...
Ok.
What are you doing, Daisuke?
N... Nothing.
Henry, let's go out for a drink.
Sorry, I'm sleepy.
Good night.
Bye.
Hey, wait!
This is a shared house.
You can't have a date in here.
I just borrowed this.
Bye.
Books.
Ok.
Daisuke.
Why don't you go to the gym?
Even if I go...
- Good morning.
Do you think I am right?
What are you talking about?
I am right.
Where are you going?
I don't understand what
Urara is thinking.
- Hurry up.
- What?
Don't you want to see Fuyu?
Well, yes. We need to register.
Never mind.
Exhale.
Push slowly.
Good morning.
Glad to see you again.
Hi.
Okuno.
You did a trial lesson before.
I...
I am Ryota's sister.
Huh?
I am not your mom.
But I am his sister.
Hey. What are you talking about?
Come with me.
Huh?
What is this?
What's going on?
I will tell him so. Thank you.
- Sakurai.
- Yes.
- Yes, I am Sakurai.
Do you know?
Know what?
About Urara.
She didn't come home last night.
She told me to make Ryota happy
and she left.
Then Ryota is your son?
Please marry my dad.
You are Urara.
Huh?
Sorry, but you are
not Ryota's sister.
Ryota's father is her ex-husband.
My ex-husband lives in Hamamatsu
and he comes to Tokyo to see
Ryota once a month.
He was planning to come
to Tokyo next week
but he changed the schedule due to
his work and will come tomorrow.
So I cancelled our date tomorrow.
I see.
It's a shame.
Okuno, don't you think about
getting remarried with my dad?
Well...
No.
I'm enjoying my single life
although I have a child.
He talked about his child...
Sorry, he talked about you in bed.
In bed?
Before we go to bed.
I see.
I saw a picture of you he kept
in his wallet.
He talked about you yesterday.
Yesterday?
Go higher.
It's dangerous.
She was so cute.
Push harder!
I wanted to be with her
all the time.
But I couldn't stop my wife going
back home and getting divorced.
My first priority was to pass
the bar exam.
I had no time to think.
Urara wouldn't forgive me
even I tell her about it.
I can't forgive him.
But it's true.
I guess he didn't know what to do.
He enjoyed being single,
then you showed up.
I don't know what to do.
I can understand.
She is such an eccentric girl.
Are you ok?
Someone is talking about you.
I'm sure it's my dad.
I have to go. See you.
Thank you for waiting.
Let's start.
You are Urara.
I've heard about you.
He showed me your picture he kept
in his wallet.
If he insists...
Welcome home.
Hmm...
What are you cooking?
Udon.
Just kidding.
It's a joke.
What?
Hey!
What's this?
I ordered this two days ago
and was just delivered.
Bed?
Because you didn't want to share.
So you want to use this as
a bedroom,
Yes. You can't sleep in a library
or in a living room.
I see.
I tried earlier. It's better
than the one in the bedroom.
You will love it.
Wait.
Do I sleep in here?
I don't like small rooms.
Hey.
Dinner is ready.
Clean the table for me, please.
Let's talk about this later.
Hey, tomorrow's date
is cancelled, right?
How did you know?
I just wanted so.
Right.
What should I do?
What?
Do you want to go out with
women like Hanako or Haruka?
Another girl.
Girl?
Is she young?
Yes.
What's her name?
Urara.
Urara?
How could you go out
with a woman who has
the same name as your daughter?
Where should I go?
I don't know.
You decide.
Don't ask me.
Is that me?
Urara is a rare name.
What are you trying to do?
Like what?
Are you trying to trick me
to send me back home?
What a mean idea!
It's from my parents.
Your mom, then.
Do you really want to go out
with me tomorrow?
I don't know how to act
like a father.
Same here.
You know what?
First of all we can do this...
What is it?
Say cheese.
Why? Come on.
I don't like taking pictures.
Maybe next time.
Or never.
All right.
Is that your girlfriend?
- Come in.
- Who?
- Thank you.
- No problem.
Ms. Rei Saeki. Thank you.
My name is Urara using kanji
for beauty. Please remember.
- Ok. Goodbye.
- Thank you.
Oops.
It's heavy. Be careful.
Here you go.
From Sayuri Saeki.
Hello, Mom.
I've received the box of clothes.
How much is the rent for
an apartment in Azabu?
It's cheap. No worries.
Don't tell me
it's your boyfriend's room.
No, it's not.
I wouldn't get involved with
a bad guy like Dad.
That's too funny.
By the way, you are not
trying to find Dad, are you?
No. I am not interested in Dad.
That's good.
I want you to be happy
with Sasaki in Kotohira.
I will be happy in Tokyo.
You really won't come back?
No.
I've decided to live in Tokyo.
You want to talk?
See you.
Good.
Huh?
Clothes.
Excuse me.
I'll put it in here.
Wait.
Your room is in the closet.
I don't like small places.
Me neither.
Is that our gene?
Wow!
This is great.
Look at this, Dad.
Soy bean with soy sauce.
Kintoki potato.
Let's eat.
What else?
Olives...
Oh.
Look.
Your favourite food. Udon.
Eat dinner.
Hum...
Mom sent me some soup stock.
I won't have to shop for a while.
That's nice.
Tomatoes...
Cucumbers...
Dad.
Udon.
Here you are.