("Law for Beginners",
"100 Judicial Precedents")
- It's cold.
- Morning.
Breakfast is ready.
So we keep eating udon?
- Is that a problem?
- Not really.
- Get changed first.
- Sure.
- Dad, ask me a question.
- A question?
Yes.
Explain the six codes.
Not something easy like that,
but something more practical.
- Shall I ask you?
- I am a law professional.
One of the customers at Chaconne
refuses to pay his bills.
Haruka Mama asks you
to collect the money.
What should you be aware of
in such occasions?
- What a question?
- Answer to it.
Check when that customer
visited Chaconne.
Correct! The payment can be expired
if long time has passed.
How long is the period?
Huh? The period of prescription
for business is... Five years!
Incorrect. It's one year. Item 4,
Article 174 of the Civil Code.
Was it so?
- Then you may not have to pay them.
- Not so easy.
You need a claim of prescription.
Article 145 of the Civil Code.
A claim?
One needs to claim that
the prescription has expired.
- Really.
- Yes.
But you did well, considering
you started only recently.
Urgh... I'm gutted.
- Good morning.
- Have a nice day.
- I'll come with you.
- Huh?
I'm looking for a place for us.
This place is too small
for three of us.
That's true.
But I'll discuss with your mum.
- Can't I look for a place?
- I don't say you can't.
- Don't get a contract.
- I know.
- You have to sort things out.
- To move houses?
Your relationships.
You know, before mum
will explode with anger.
I know.
Please take care of it.
It is 150 square meters overall.
Look at this view.
You can see Tokyo Bay and Mt. Fuji.
- Amazing!
- Wow. This is great.
Wow.
How much does it cost?
This type of room
is 130,000,000 yen.
Oh, it was cheaper than I thought.
The top floor is 200 square meters
and 300,000,000 yen.
Oh. Will you show me that room too?
Yes. Certainly!
Hey. Hey wait. Wait, wait, wait.
- Is your dad that rich?
- Don't know.
Are you sure?
It's 300,000,000 yen.
Isn't it fun to look
around the flats?
He'd say "Urara, wait a sec. Urara."
- Looks good.
- I know.
130,000,000 yen?
Impossible. I am only a lawyer.
- You earn a lot.
- Not really.
Dad, did you see Hanako and all?
I was busy all day today.
Ah. I knew that.
- Oh, there they are.
- Who is it?
- Thanks for coming.
- Who?
I couldn't rely on you,
so I called Hanako.
- Say goodbye properly.
- What? What?
What? Wait, wait.
- Good evening.
Wait a sec.
Let's talk elsewhere.
Are you not letting me in?
That's right.
Dad. That's good.
But...here!
Come in and talk!
- Come in.
- Thank you.
- Hanako, I need to talk...
- I'd like your advice.
What?
I'd like to sue someone
for breach of engagement.
Oh, do you mean...
He was with me for three years,
but without any discussion...
...he is going to re-marry
his ex-wife.
Hanako, based on Article 709
of the Civil Code...
...you can ask him
for compensation.
We are not engaged and
you said you don't intend to...
- ...marry me.
- Dad?
You had a nightmare.
- It's a dream.
- A nightmare?
Y...yeah.
Some dreams can come true.
- I'm coming.
- Can it be Hanako?
- Oh?
- I knew it.
All three of them?
- Why do you let them in?
- You need to talk.
All three at once?
- They're coming!
- What? How can I...
- Morning.
- Good morning.
Good morning.
Wait a second.
Why are you all together?
We ran into each other downstairs.
- Let's talk elsewhere.
- Come in!
- Ouch. Ow!
- Come in.
We wanted to say...
...congratulations
on your re-marriage.
Oh, yes. Thanks.
Thank you so much.
But I need your advice.
- I do too.
- Me too.
I'd like sue someone
for breach of engagement.
- What? Do you mean...
- Do you mean...
He was with me
for three years, but...
- ... without any discussion...
- What shall I do?
About what?
This baby.
- Is it mine?
- Of course.
- I didn't know that.
- Wait.
- Are you in relationship with him?
- Yes.
Article 779 of the Civil Code.
A father or a mother may affiliate
his/her child out of wedlock.
Can you affiliate my child?
- Oh, well...
- I won't forgive you.
What?
- What?
- Calm down!
I'll kill you and myself!
- Wait!
- No!
Oh no.
- Let me take our lives!
- Just kill yourself if you want.
Don't incite her.
Should I kill myself?
- Wait! don't do that!
- Stop it!
Stop it!
Dad?
- What is this?
- Dad?
Dad.
Dad!
Dad! Dad. Dad. Dad!
Ow, ouch. Ow...
- A dream again?
- What are you talking about?
Morning!
- Did she tell you she'd come?
- No.
- I'll let her in.
- Urara.
- W..what?
- Come, Urara.
Can you hit me
to see if this is real...
- Don't punch me.
- You asked me to.
- It is not a dream.
- Huh?
OK. I'll open the door.
What?
A friend of mine in Tokyo
was hospitalized.
- So you're here?
- Just for one night.
I have a customer tomorrow.
I'm visiting the hospital
in the afternoon. This is for you.
- You should call us.
- Oh that's true. I forgot about it.
- Huh?
- Ah!
Wait, wait...
It's penguin express.
A parcel for Rei Saeki.
Sugar, it's "Urara", not "Rei".
I'll get changed.
(Okuno, Hanako, Haruka Mama)
- Dad, the food is ready.
- Huh?
- Have a nice day!
- Have a nice day.
- Good morning.
- Sorry, Ms Shimizu.
- Yes?
I'd like to take an afternoon off.
That's fine, but...
...there are many issues to work on
along with the trial tomorrow.
I understand.
(Sports Gym Renaissance)
(Club Chaconne)
- Hanako, here he is.
- Thanks.
Sorry, I'm done shortly.
Just a second.
- Don't worry.
- OK.
Sorry.
Sorry to bother you
when you're busy.
Isn't it the first time
you visit me at work?
What's happened?
Well, it is...
Did Urara agree about your marriage?
I thought I haven't asked
for your blessing.
Oh, you are so honest.
I thought I already
gave my blessing.
Congratulations.
I wish your happiness.
Thank you.
I have to thank you.
By being with you...
...I grew mature.
You gave me a chance.
You made me feel I could
hang on to my work a bit more.
It's not me, it's Urara.
Including that,
it is because of you.
Well, then.
Wow.
Oh.
Why is it so clammed in here?
- Are we having udon again?
- Of course.
I'm glad to hear your friend was OK.
She can leave
the hospital in a week.
Hey, what about your life insurance?
- What about it?
- Who is the recipient?
I don't know.
You have to change it
either to me or Urara.
You're shrewd.
- It's delicious.
- It is.
It is, but...
- What?
- Well, nothing.
Dad, which is more delicious,
mine or mum's?
Oh, Urara. Are you
competing with me?
I got better.
With dad as a guinea pig?
No, with my love.
- Which?
- Well...
I like both.
- But which is better?
- Both!
I've finished.
When you moved there, I'll take
you to good udon restaurants.
- Move there?
- When are you moving?
What is it about?
You'll move to Kotohira.
When you get married, aren't we
living together in Tokyo?
- Naturally I thought so.
- What? I have my hairdresser.
- Are you not closing?
- I have customers...
...who come to me for decades,
for two generations.
I can't think of closing it.
And you ask me to come to Kotohira?
- You can work in Kotohira too.
- No way.
There are cases in Kotohira.
I have some cases now.
Should I turn them down?
I thought you'd commute to Tokyo.
You can keep the office and
tell your staff to do things.
That won't be feasible.
You know nothing about it.
You are the one who knows nothing.
Stop that!
Didn't you discuss
where you are going to be based?
Why are you arguing now?
- I thought we live in Tokyo!
- I thought we live in Kotohira!
Discuss properly.
- How about Urara?
I'm happy as long as
we can live together as a family.
Thanks for the food.
It's already this late?
Are you going out together?
- Work.
- I got a customer.
Aren't you discussing?
- Unnecessary. We live in Tokyo.
- Unnecessary. We live in Kotohira.
Listen, you both...
- Hey!
- I won't go to Kotohira.
- I won't come to Tokyo.
- Hey...
- Move!
What? Wait!
Isn't it lovely?
You in an apron can cook here.
I will be...
I will be seated here.
I will feel the happiness,
looking at you.
How's that? Shall we get married?
Or, shall we go out together?
Urara.
Sorry. I was not listening.
You should try to change that habit.
Yeah.
What's happened?
Well, I don't think
it's a big deal...
- Thank you so much.
- Thanks.
- Isn't that risky?
- What?
It's a big deal.
Do you think so?
Both of your parents, though I
understand the situations...
...there are no viable solutions,
if both don't compromise.
They can't get married.
They can, on the paperwork.
Are you OK with it?
No. I want to live together
with them.
Daisuke, are you
thinking about this with me?
What do you think I'm doing?
Thanks!
Can we have two of these?
I am always on your side.
Thanks.
Ah. Why doesn't your mum
run a hairdresser in Tokyo?
I said mum doesn't want to close
her hairdresser in Kotohira.
Oh. There is one way to do this.
What is that?
But you three won't be
able to live together.
What do you mean?
Say it.
No, it's not good at all.
Why don't you tell me?
Because Urara may carry this out.
Tell me!
Well, this won't be good for me.
What do you mean?
Say it!
OK, cut! Now let's check it.
- Oh. Hanako!
- Ah, Urara.
- A shooting in front of our flat?
- Yes.
We've finished here and just about
to move to the next place.
The footage was okay.
Why don't we have a chat
while they are tidying up?
I saw your dad yesterday.
- What?
- And...
...he apologized to me.
He really sorted out
his relationships.
He really meant to live
with three of us.
Then, you won't see my dad any more.
I guess so. I will miss him.
You probably won't see me either.
Thank you so much...
...for giving me advice.
If you don't mind,
we can remain good friends.
I'd be happy to.
- What's happened?
- Nothing.
I feel brave now.
Bye!
Where are you going?
Urara.
Did dad ask you to come?
I can't compromise.
I know.
Mum.
Will you do my hair?
I liked to have my hair done by you.
You mimicked me too.
Do you feel comfortable?
Fine, thanks.
If I went to a beauty school
as you advised me...
...wouldn't I have thought
of going to Tokyo?
I think you did anyway.
I think so.
- Mum.
- What?
I gave you a condition.
I'll be happy for you!
- What?
However, there is a condition.
"Both dad and mum have to be happy."
- Wasn't it?
- Yes.
Mum.
You want to be together with dad.
I do.
Then, I will continue this place.
Though it will take time
as I need training.
Wait, Urara.
You wanted to be a lawyer.
It's OK. If it makes you two happy.
How about your happiness?
Your happiness is my happiness.
What... Stop being silly.
I've made up my mind.
I'll be a hairdresser
and continue this business.
You can live with dad in Tokyo.
No.
Then, what are you
going to do with this?
- Hello.
Oh? Is he out?
Yes. He is at the high court to...
...hear the decision for the trial
over the false charge for murder.
I don't think he'd be back today.
I see. This is for you.
(Court)
- Ah!
- Shh.
This court is now in session.
The defendant may come forward.
The sentence of the court is...
...to reverse the current sentence.
The defendant is not guilty.
- Not guilty!
- Thank you so much.
The sentence is long,
so let me state this first.
You are found not guilty, thanks to
the effort of the defender.
We, as the court, could correct
the error in the first trial.
We would like to extend
our respect to his passion...
Thank you so much.
I'm glad it turned out well.
Without your support, my son
would have been in the prison.
Not at all. Your son persevered.
I only gave him
what support I could give.
He'll be busy for a while.
Are you leaving Tokyo?
Until next May
when I take the Bar Exam...
...I will study
in my hometown in Niigata.
The next exam is going to
be the last chance for me.
I'll have to go.
I need to pack stuff up.
- I can help you.
- No worries.
Then, I can look after Hitomi.
Shall I pick her up from nursery?
Well...
Hitomi is not here.
What? She's not here?
My ex-wife is back
from New York now.
Don't tell me you let Hitomi go.
- Yes, I did.
- Did you?
Didn't you discuss?
We did.
But...
Hitomi would like to be
with her mum.
She cried so often,
missing her mum.
She did cry when you
took care of her too.
But she may cry, missing you
from now on.
It's my decision.
I will be her father nonetheless.
Mr. Sakurai.
Will you speak to
your ex-wife once again?
Being with a mother will become
more important as she grows up.
As a father, I will
pass the Bar Exam...
...and become a lawyer
before seeing Hitomi.
I don't know if my ex will
allow me to see her.
That's not good.
If you don't discuss...
...you may not be able
to see them again.
Isn't your ex-wife still in Japan?
- Yes.
- Then, please...
...discuss with her more.
Please!
I have to go,
as I've got things to do.
- Thank you.
- I'll be back next month.
- Thanks.
Urara.
(Tamariba)
Oh, someone came in.
- Daisuke?
- Yes?
Hi everyone.
Oh well.
Can I ask you a favor?
- Hello?
- It's me.
How long will you be in Kotohira?
I'll hold a party
in Tamariba tonight.
You have to come.
Tonight at 6 p.m.
Why don't you answer me?
- I have to talk to you.
- Don't worry. Just come.
- Oh? That's strange.
- What?
Huh?
What's up?
- I'll get this.
- Don't worry.
- OK, I won't.
- Don't push me.
- What?
Oh?
- It's quiet.
Dad! Is mum here too?
We met there. Don't cover
things up, like "it's a party".
Anyways. I want you...
...to discuss your future.
Urara told me she'd be a hairdresser
to continue my business.
I thought that's the best for us.
Urara decided to become a lawyer,
inspired by you.
Should we make her say such a thing?
- I'll go to Kotohira.
- What?
Then, we can live together.
- But you've got your work...
- I can handle it.
- No, you have an important...
- You have your work too.
- Not really.
- You said so...
We can't draw the conclusion
straight away.
So, you'll consider so that
we can live together?
Yes.
Let us start!
- What? What?
- Happy Merry Christmas!
I wanted you...
...to recognize you're together now.
I mean...
...let's have a wedding!
- Now? No way.
- Let's do it!
- I have a surprising guest too.
- What?
- Here's a nice dress!
- Oh, no, no.
You'll look great in it!
Look, so cute!
- Come on, Dad.
- No, no way!
Thanks for waiting.
The newlywed couple is here.
Let us begin the wedding ceremony.
Please look at the entrance.
Welcome the bride.
Hey, Urara.
What are you doing?
I happened to order this
in my own size.
I don't want to waste, so here I am.
- Silly.
- You're a photographer.
Mum.
Hello.
We didn't have the wedding dress.
I made it just now!
Look at me.
So pretty!
- Good one, Dad!
- I'm a vicar.
Let me skip most of the stuff.
Takuya Suzuki, will you take
Sayuri Saeki...
- ...to be your wife?
- I do.
For better or worse...
...for richer or poorer...
...in sickness and health...
...will you have her...
...to love and cherish...
...till the death you do part?
Dad?
I broke the promise once.
You should keep it this time.
I do.
Let me skip it again.
Will you take him as your husband?
Of course!
You should say "I do".
Of course, I do.
Let us prepare for the reception.
- Our MC is...
- Hello.
Congratulations on your re-marriage!
And here are our guests.
- Congratulations.
Congratulations.
- Wh... What?
Urara. What's happening?
I invited everyone concerned.
Sir, congratulations.
Sakurai?
Hey, wait.
You can't run away.
But...
Who'd give us a toast?
Henry, would you like to?
- Mr Sakurai.
- Me?
Please.
Congratulations on your marriage.
Let us make a toast
for their happiness. Cheers!
Hey, Sakurai!
Everyone has a glass?
- Cheers!
Next up is cake cutting.
Please come forward.
Really?
Urara, I'm a bit embarrassed.
- You 're having fun.
- I baked this cake.
Here they go!
Wow. Congratulations!
- Let me cut it into pieces.
- Don't they do the first bite?
- First bite?
- Yeah.
Henry, do you speak Japanese?
Let's have a speech from the groom.
I am very much surprised
at this sudden celebration.
I didn't expect so many people
would celebrate...
...my second marriage
with the same person.
Thank you so much.
Urara. I saw you
after 15 years of gap.
We started to live together
and we had a lot going on.
It is because of you that
I can restart the life with mum.
Urara. You're always flat-out.
Don't you get tired? Right?
- That's true.
- Right!
I agree.
You are sometimes
too intrusive, but...
...don't change that.
You can make people...
...happy with your smile.
That's right, Urara.
Okay. Got you.
Urara. Thank you for being...
...our daughter.
- I am happy to be your mum.
- Me too.
Right, then have a party!
Yeah!
Okay. Say cheese!
Shigesuke!
Look at me.
I'll take a photo.
Say cheese.
Daisuke's father went to Cambodia
after the New Year.
He and his wife are contributing
to landmine removal...
...praying for world peace.
Come on. Let me take a photo.
Cheese!
Joanna went back to France
and doing her art in Paris.
She loves Japan as much
as her father and...
...she occasionally visits Japan.
Henry quit his career a model...
..as he was unsuccessful
both in Canada and Japan.
He became an entrepreneur.
Now he owns several companies
and is doing...
...business internationally
with his English skills.
Look at me! OK? Cheese.
Ms Okuno had a shotgun wedding...
...with a fat guy she met
at the gym.
Now she has three kids,
including Ryota.
She is in the midst of happy life.
Haruka Mama managed
to pay off her father's debt.
She left Roppongi.
Now she owns a bistro...
...back in Hokkaido, using
plenty of local ingredients.
Mr Shimoyama and Yoko.
Say cheese!
They inherited Haruka's club.
Yoko has become
an expert in this job.
They are trying their best
to increase...
...the profit of the club.
Hey everyone.
Let's take a group photo.
Daisuke. Get a tripod.
- Tripod!
- Tripod?
- I'm tired of it.
- Not me.
For a year since the party...
...we have lived in Tokyo happily.
I'm tired of udon, really.
Then you won't eat it ever again?
I'm not saying that.
I want soba for a change.
They have an argument
at the daily basis.
I can't be bothered to worry.
As for the hairdresser
in Kotohira...
...Yukari continued it for us.
Yukari turns out
to be a hairdresser.
Look at you. It's cool.
OK. It's time.
Mum, Dad.
I need to talk.
What's up?
Today, I...
...leave this flat.
- Wh...What?
- Huh?
I thoroughly enjoyed
the life with family.
Thank you so much.
Don't say "thank you"...
Do you really need to leave?
Dad. Mum.
You'll be okay, won't you?
I will live for my own happiness
from now on.
Thank you for everything.
Three years later.
- Thanks.
- Thank you very much.
Daisuke is running café Tamariba
with his sister, Mika,...
...who is now a university student.
Daisuke's dumplings
became so popular.
Business is successful enough
to renovate the interior.
He still tends to fall
in love at the first sight.
But he still fancies me.
- What's up? It's late.
- Well, yes.
What happened to the girl?
- The girl?
- Was it Urara Saeki?
Ah. She went home.
She was surprised at me
buying underpants.
Did you buy them?
OK! Let us check the footage.
Hanako made a successful transition
from a model to an actress.
She is climbing up the ladder.
Mum had a branch of the hairdresser
she used to work for.
She made a great success in Aoyama
as a hairdresser...
...who can sing and dance. She is
thinking of having another branch.
Mr Sakurai finally became a lawyer.
- Hi.
- Thanks for waiting.
Hitomi who is nine years old
worked as a glue...
...no, she held the bond
and get back with his ex-wife.
(Court)
Since the representative
of plaintiff is absent...
Others' happiness is my happiness.
Sorry for being late.
Thank you for waiting.
- Urara?
- Urara.
After I left home, I studied hard,
living like a hermit.
I passed the preliminary exam
in the following year.
I passed the Bar Exam
in the year after too.
After the training,
I became a lawyer.
This court is now in session.
Will you present your accusation?
Yes, your honor.
Representative of defendant.
Will you present the defense?
Yes, your honor.
I ask you the representative
of plaintiff, Urara Suzuki.
I haven't seen my dad
since I left home.
I was determined to see him next
at the court.
Will you clearly explain
what is lacking.
The accusation only
describes the relationship.
There is no date for the engagement.
It is unreasonable to claim
the compensation.
No, it isn't. Engagement was made
when the defendant gave the ring.
The ring worth 500 yen bought at
the flea market in Shimokitazawa...
...cannot be an engagement ring.
The representative misunderstands
the engagement.
The defendant stated
"Be with me forever".
This is clearly an engagement.
The defendant never
asked for the marriage.
The ring has a carving.
The defender is claiming
comparative negligence...
You're never short of words.
- I beg your pardon?
- Nothing.
The defendant betrayed
the affection...
...of the woman who loved him.
This is a problem.
Based on Article 709...
...we claim for the compensation
of damages.
Others' happiness is my happiness.