Hey, you're too slow!
You need to train.
Hey, hey, let me run on my pace.
Please.
I can't take it anymore. No
more. That's it.
Ah.
Because you joined the sports club
for the wrong reason?
Come on, you can keep up. Let's go.
Oh?
Ah.
Goodness' sakes.
Dad!
- Dad!
- Ah no! Wait!
Dad.
You shouldn't do that.
Don't coach me like that.
What? Come on, let's go.
Dad?
Hurry up, it's my turn.
Hurry up! Hurry up!
Oh.
I can't eat all of these.
But...
I was really happy yesterday.
Time to eat.
"Yesterday," huh.
For the first time,
dad finally did something
fatherly for me.
You got so worried and
came to pick me up, right?
Sakurai tricked me.
Sensei, I found out where
Urara-san is.
Apparently,
A bad guy is trying to leech
her and...
she's going out of her way...
Smells like trouble...
I must thank Sakurai-san.
Give me a break.
I got punched for that.
What? So what's a punch or two?
It still hurts!
But our dad-daughter bond has
tightened.
We should be grateful.
You hear me?
I'm full.
Ah ah, however...
About that boy who punched me...
Daisuke Tamagawa-kun?
I think he likes you, Urara.
And what?
He confessed to me.
- And?
- Nothing.
That's mean.
I'm not interested in him.
Try dating him.
Huh? Though I don't have
feelings for him?
If you fall too hard,
you lose sight of
a lot things, you know.
They say love is blind.
Feeling nothing is fine.
Really?
You have my approval to date him.
Well, if you say so...
No, you're tricking me.
Why would I trick you?
You're trying to dodge the issue.
Dodge what?
Dad.
Dad!
You'll straighten things out?
Like I said, what?
Are you playing dumb?
Hanako-san, Okuno-san,
or Haruka-Mama...
Which is your true love?
Decide soon.
Oh, that again...
Because you never answered.
The human heart is complicated.
No, you're dodging the issue.
That's not true.
Geez...
Shall I decide for you?
Why must you decide for me?
Because I'm your daughter!
Makes no difference.
The woman you like the most is...
as I thought, Hanako-san?
No, Okuno-san is also pretty.
You're also close to Haruka-Mama.
Mama thinks you're my mistress.
No, Mama saw through it and knows
I'm your daughter.
Is that so?
We do look like dad and daughter.
So Hanako is the only one who
doesn't know.
Why did you laugh?
Nothing.
So Hanako-san is your
true love, huh.
How is that?
The only one who has
a spare key,
is Hanako-san, right?
But...
It's a shame.
What is?
She said she wouldn't meet
you for a while.
That's right.
Hanako-san has dis-appear-ed.
That makes Okuno-san and
Haruka-Mama left to choose, Dad.
What will you do, Dad?
Yes, this is Hanako.
Do you have time?
Anything happened?
Morning.
Good morning.
How about dinner tonight?
At a nice restaurant.
Work's done soon.
How about this evening?
Sorry, today's a little bit...
I see.
See you again.
See you.
That was Hanako, right?
No, It wasn't.
Dad...
Your back's crying, you know.
Alright.
Hello? It's Urara.
Got a call from your dad this
morning.
I thought so.
Are you working today?
I'm at the Shimokitazawa flea
market.
I'll be there.
FLAT OUT TOKYO GIRL
"Cafe Tamariba"
Hello, what is it Daisuke-kun?
It's Shigesuke.
Ah, hello!
You're father's made, isn't he?
Huh?
About Daisuke punching him.
Your father's a lawyer and
we thought we'd be sued for it.
No way. We're the ones
who cause the problem.
So it's okay?
Yes.
I'll drop by again.
Aren't you glad, Shige-san?
I'm off.
That Daisuke... How can
he sleep at a time like this.
He hasn't been
home since last night.
What?
- I'm off.
- Yeah.
He just left suddenly.
Didn't Daisuke have small luggage
with him?
One or two night trip?
Welcome.
Amazake.
(sweet rice wine)
Just a moment.
What's up? Where are you?
Kotohira.
Here, it's delicious.
Good morning.
Excuse me... umm...
I'm sorry for yesterday.
Sakurai.
You're fired.
Ah.. umm..
Anything but that...
I have to raise Hitomi.
Can you grant me a deferral?
I beg of you.
I understand.
Please get married.
Pardon?
Good idea.
Be my son-in-law.
What?
She's actually good at cooking.
She does all chores.
Wait, wait just a minute.
You mean I have to marry Urara?
That's right.
Come on, Sensei...
Call me 'Dad.'
But Urara is 19 years old.
Plenty girls get married at 19.
But that's...
She's better off not
marrying a divorced father like me.
Sakurai.
You're a good guy.
Urara loves kids.
Hitomi won't be
lonely anymore, and...
It'll be easier for you to focus on
studying for the bar exam.
Hello, Dad?
Ah, Urara?
Can you pick up...
...Hitomi-chan for Sakurai?
He needs to do overtime since
he has a lot of work to do.
Sure.
Make dinner for Hitomi-chan,
give her a bath then put her to
sleep.
Sure thing.
Ah, but I have to work
in Chaconne tonight...
Ah, it's fine, it's fine.
I'll contact Haruka-Mama.
Okay.
- Please do so.
- Urara-san.
I'm sorry.
I want to give you
the key for my home,
can we meet somewhere?
Ah, alright. I'll meet you in Ebisu.
Thank you very much.
You can leave it to me.
- Yes?
- I'm here to pick up Hitomi Sakurai.
I'm Urara Saeki.
- Written as "Rei" of "Kirei."
- Ok.
We're home...
Ah, the light switch..
light switch...
There we go.
Papa!
- Huh? Papa? Papa?
- Papa!
He'll be home soon. Okay?
Papa!
Oh yea, let's sing a song.
Okay? Come here.
Over the hills we go...
I don't know that song!
Of course, you don't.
Hey, okay then.
Teach me a song Hitomi knows.
The rain has stopped...
The sun came out...
What's that song?
Ah, sorry, sorry. And a one, two...
The rain has...
...stopped.
Ah.
Mama, give me a kiss.
Come on, Sensei!
Can't you act decently?
It's fine!
Sakurai!
Enjoy yourself!
Are you sure?
- 'Dad'
- 'Dad'?
Mama, stop calling me that.
Shouldn't you go home early?
To your cute daughter.
- Daughter?
- Cute? Cute?
She was cute as a baby.
She's still cute.
If she didn't talk.
One after another...
that mouth of hers spouts
some spiteful remark.
I'd like to pinch it.
Sensei, you're losing it.
Sakurai, you drink up as well!
I'm sorry, I'm going home.
Mama, we're going after this.
Sorry, I have a previous
engagement tonight.
Welcome. Let's drink up.
I'm home!
Hitomi?
Urara-san.
It was hectic.
Here we go.
I'm home.
Urara-san?
Urara!
Hmm?
Hmm.
Urara...
Urara, get me some water.
Papa!
It smells good!
Huh? What's up?
Papa woke up.
Ah, good morning.
Good morning.
Sorry for doing all this.
I'm sorry for ending up staying
for the night.
I got exhausted after playing with
Hitomi-chan.
Right?
Right.
Papa, it's delicious.
It really is.
A 100 times better than Papa's.
Around twice as good.
I see.
Thank you.
Your dad's cooking is filled with
over a hundred times more love
than mine, right?
Right.
It still turned out good.
It's really good.
I'm glad.
- It's good, isn't it?
- Yeah.
Good morning.
Okay, off you go.
I leave her in your care.
See you.
Bye bye, Hitomi-chan.
Umm...
Thank you for everything.
Not at all.
Ah, Hitomi-chan...
She was looking for her mom.
Yes.
Can't you work things out with
Hitomi's mom?
The reason for our divorce
was for not being able to pass the
bar exam.
Same with my dad.
We argued on who'd get custody of
Hitomi.
She wanted custody as well.
She was working in
the food industry,
and was just offered
a job in New York.
So that's why
she chose work over Hitomi-chan.
No, that's not it.
She wanted to take
Hitomi with her but...
I told her she'd be raised properly.
Once she returns to Japan,
I thought I'd talk it over with her.
Sakurai-san.
You want her back, right?
I don't know.
What?
I don't have time to think about it.
What I need to right now
is make sure Hitomi is raised well.
And I'll certainly pass
the next bar exam.
I'm rooting for you.
Okay.
Picking up and
cooking for Hitomi,
I'll be glad to anytime.
Please ask me anything.
Thank you.
It's all right.
I appreciate it.
It's not that of a big deal.
And actually...
Huh?
"Panel Discussion Materials"
Dad!
Dad?
Huh?
Dad, what are you playing at?
What is it? Coming home so soon.
Trying to marry me
off to Sakurai-san!
Ah that was just a small joke.
He took it seriously, I felt bad for
him.
Yeah, he's a serious person.
Isn't that...
"Powa Hara"?
Power harassment.
My bad.
Then?
You spent the night at Sakurai's?
Yes, I did.
Nothing...nothing happened?
Of course not!
What are you thinking?
I see.
Nothing happened.
Take out the trash.
Hey, I have briefing for a
symposium soon after this.
Ah, this stinks!
I've had it!
Thank you very much.
Sensei comes up with ridiculous
ideas.
Really.
I was wondering why you
didn't come yesterday,
but that's what happened?
Sorry for that.
But...
I think he was serious when
he asked if nothing happened.
Urara-san,
you were annoying so he
pushed you to Sakurai-san.
But hearing you spent the night,
he got worried about you.
If that's the case,
that's father's love, isn't it?
Yes, I think it is.
Good morning.
Urara-san was really a big help.
Hitomi also had fun with her.
She wants to play with her again,
so can I borrow Urara-san?
It's not you who wants to
play,right?
What?
Sure, I don't mind.
However...
No sleepovers, okay?
Of course.
No way.
I don't feel that even one bit.
You may not realize it,
but your heart remembers.
Remember?
My father's the same.
He was so strict to me that
I actually thought he hated me.
But the truth is
he was actually thinking
about me so dearly.
I realize it these days.
The fact you turned down
my dad yesterday.
It was for my sake, right?
I thought so.
Please be true to your feelings too.
My feelings...
If you feel like seeing my dad, go
ahead.
Are you free tonight?
I go to Aomori tomorrow.
So I have things to do.
Ah, how nice.
I guess it's for work?
No, I'm going home. My father's
been hospitalized.
- What?
- Ah, no...
He contacted me,
so I think it's not that serious.
How long will you be there?
I'm not sure.
I may not come back anymore.
I have think things over.
When does your train leave?
No, I'm flying there at 5:00 pm.
Welcome.
It's a liquidation sale.
You can have 3 for 500 yen.
Hey...!
Ah, what the hell
are you doing, Dad?
I wonder if he knows
Hanako-san is leaving.
Daisuke! What're you doing!
It's dangerous. Careful now.
Watch it. Watch it!
I'm sorry!
You idiot. Can't you even do this?
I'm sorry.
He's doing physical labor.
Never mind.
Go work over there!
Hello?
Hello?!
Is this a prank?
Ah, oh right.
Ah I'm sorry!
Umm... this is Urara.
Can you pass me to my father?
I've been trying to contact
his phone for a while.
I can't contact him.
Well, he went somewhere.
Huh? To where?
Sensei, you're working
hard, aren't you?
In case something happens,
I have to get in shape.
Yes, you should.
And so, how about it, after this?
No.
Ah, Ryota-kun, huh.
Yep.
If you're a nag,
you'll lose appeal.
You ought to be a dad
and lessen your libido.
I don't want to. That's why
I'm asking you out.
Tomorrow noon?
Tomorrow I have a symposium to
attend.
Too bad. Ask me out next time.
At 6:00 pm...
Ah, Yoko-chan.
Hello.
Listen, tonight...
What about tonight?
Never mind.
Work hard.
I think he was trying...
- to hit on me.
- Wait.. no.
- Good afternoon.
Hello?
It's Chaconne's Shimoyama.
Rei-chan, you can make your
shift for tonight, right?
What? I can't.
Don't "can't" me. You took yesterday
off.
What? Mama gave me permission.
I'm in charge of the girls.
Ah okay.
Don't mess up the shift on me.
I understand.
As long you understand.
I'll be waiting.
Urara-chan.
Ah, Daisuke-kun.
I saw you earlier.
Do you have time?
Well, just a little bit.
What's wrong?
I confessed to you, didn't I?
Yes, you did.
I take it back.
Sure, I don't mind.
- You don't mind?
- Yes.
Anyway, thanks.
For wiping the slate clean.
There wasn't anything on it.
And so...
I have a favor to ask.
What is it?
I want to work at Chaccone.
Can you refer me?
The pay's good?
I don't know the
hourly wage for men, but...
are you planning to
work day and night?
I'm fine with water.
I have to save some money.
Please.
Sure, but why?
Don't tell the folks in Tamariba.
What?
What is it? What is it?
We're having a baby.
Are you pregnant, Daisuke-kun?
Better tell everyone.
Why would a guy
get pregnant?
Then who is pregnant?
Aki-chan in Shikoku.
Huh?
Weren't you dumped then
came home crying?
No, I saw her yesterday.
- At Kotohira?
- Yes.
I took the night bus and went back.
You're so motivated.
You see, I'm gonne be a father.
Getting married?
Of course. I have to
do the right thing.
But are you doing it...
because you really love Aki-san?
Or is it because...
...she got pregnant?
Well, it's because
I love her, of course.
But...
does Aki love you, Daisuke-kun?
Didn't she dump you?
Thanks for waiting.
But she came to me. Doesn't
that
...mean she loves me?
I don't really know, but...
But you got on a bus and flew back
by plane.
Amazing.
I love her, that's why.
Somewhat... you look cool
...to me for the first time.
Really? Should I be happy
you told me that or not?
I'm home.
Welcome home.
Dad, did you know?
Hanako is going to her hometown
tomorrow.
No.
Hanako doesn't want
to come back to Tokyo anymore.
Why is that?
She was troubled.
She said she'll think things
over.
Is it my fault?
Of course it is.
Because you treated her
so vaguely.
Is that fine with you?
At this rate you'll lose her.
She'll be coming back.
That's just your guess, right?
Hanako's flight is tomorrow at 5pm.
Go stop her.
And act like guys in TV dramas?
You don't have to go
to the airport,
just talk to her before that.
I'll be at the symposium all
day tomorrow.
Which is important to you?
I'm in the discussion as a panelist.
You may never see
her again, you know.
Okay?
I'm preparing.
Get out.
Come on, Dad.
She's a grown woman.
If she decided to return to her
home, so be it.
You should learn from Daisuke-kun.
Who is Daisuke-kun?
Daisuke-kun,
he went to Shikoku for his ex
girlfriend.
She called and he got on a night
bus.
Look,
I'm not Daisuke-kun.
Tomorrow, Hanako...
5:00 pm flight!
Ah~ Today,
it's the 5:00pm flight.
You should...
I won't go.
Ah!
Early this morning,
she cleaned everything.
Really?
Hello, Hello.
Huh?
Where is Dad?
He's in a middle of a trial.
He's at a symposium today, right?
Doesn't he have a break?
No, it doesn't seem so.
A panel discussion follows the
trial.
All the way until 5:00?
A social gathering begins
before 5:00.
Oh, then he can sneak out.
No, people involved with
the compensation case
Sensei is supporting will be
there, so that's not possible.
Can't you attend in
his place, Sakurai-san?
I'm not even a lawyer.
Besides, no one can take
Sensei's place.
Dad.
It'll be my turn soon.
Don't attend the gathering,
and you'll make it.
You'll only be drinking with them.
No, it's part of my job.
No one can take my place.
No one can take your place for
Hanako-san as well.
Who cares if one person
- ...doesn't show up?
- I'm Takuya Suzuki.
Put this on me.
It's a social gathering.
I can't skip it.
What? Wait!
She's not invited.
Don't let her in.
Dad! Dad!
- Excuse me.
- Dad! Wait, Dad!
Why do people confess
to a crime they haven't
even commited?
The case of a PC that was
remotely operated.
It was caused by an influence of
peddling.
To counter that,
it's best to do investigations,
and prevent by observing the
suspect's explanation.
However, I was under pressure
when they interrogated me and that
they are willing to drop charges...
"Urara"
What are the fundamental
solutions we can think of?
Suzuki-sensei.
Yes?
Huh? Solutions... Ah..ah.
It's important to visualize in
this interrogation...
Ah, Excuse me.
- Umm.. Excuse me.
- Yes?
Is this the East Terminal?
Yes, right that way.
Thank you.
Ah, excuse me. Sorry.
Coming through.
Excuse me.
Did she board already?
Hanako-san!
Urara-san.
Are you here to see me off?
No, it's not me.
Umm, my father will be here soon.
Please wait until then.
Why is Sensei coming?
Isn't it obvious?
To stop you.
Why would he stop me?
I told Dad that you were
that you're going home
and may not be coming
back to Tokyo anymore.
It's because my father
treated you vaguely, right?
But you're a precious
person to my father.
So...
So I'm sure he's coming.
Passengers for Aomori...
- There won't be time to talk!
- Stop!
- What?
- ...board at Gate 36...
I have to go.
Please wait!
Maybe he mistakenly
went to the west terminal instead.
I beg of you, wait a little more.
Okay? Just wait.
Ah, excuse me!
Ah, I'm sorry!
Excuse me.
Excuse me, I'm coming through.
I'm sorry. Excuse me.
Dad. Dad.
Over there?
Huh? Hanako-san?
What?
"5:00 pm."
Oh, Rei-chan.
What?
You look down.
I wonder...
why are grownups so bothersome?
They're stuck on appearance,
they're obstinate...
It's all bothersome.
That's how grownups are.
Haven't you realized
that after working here?
They like to show off,
pretend to be tough,
Try to look so cool.
He's been working real hard.
Who?
Daisuke.
We're opening.
Yes!
I'm home.
Welcome home.
Dad, why didn't you come
to Haneda airport?
Didn't I say I won't go?
I'm asking why didn't you?
If I went, I'd have to
take responsibility for her life.
Why don't you just marry her?
I failed marriage once.
I know that well.
It will happen again.
Depends on the person,
can't it be different?
Yes, maybe so.
That's right, so...
If I can make sure of that,
I may marry again.
But now's not the time.
No harm trying.
It's not just Hanako.
Same goes for Okuno
and Haruka-Mama.
Sounds too convenient.
An excuse to play around?
That's not true.
But you like
Hanako the most, right?
I don't give ranks to women.
Then, that means the day you
become happy still have ways to go?
Marriage doesn't always equate to
happiness.
What does it take to make you happy?
I told I don't know, didn't I?
Grownups don't think about
whether they're happy or not.
Am I wrong to want Dad
to be happy?
You're not.
- See?
- But it's annoying.
I want you to think
of your own happiness.
- Don't worry about me.
- Find a boyfriend.
- A boyfriend?
- How about Sakurai?
- Ah come on, Dad.
- I'm serious.
You're not serious at all.
Dad, didn't you know?
Sakurai wants to get
back together with his ex wife.
Really?
How about the day's...
what's his name?
Dai...dai...
- Daisuke-kun?
- Yeah.
Daisuke-kun's girlfriend
is pregnant.
It's a secret.
Who am I going to tell?
- Then...
- Enough of me.
Enough of me too!
Think what's good for
- ...yourself.
- Think for yourself.
Hey, Dad! You'll be late!
Come on, wake up! Hurry!
No, no, no.
Dad, wake up.
Today's my day off.
Large garbage Saturday...
Ah... he's right.
Don't wake me until after noon.
Hey Dad, wake up!
I need to air out the sheets.
Thank you.
Need to pee.
Aren't you having too
much fun, Daisuke?
I'm not playing around.
Welcome.
Daisuke!
Aki-chan!
I came.
You should've called.
I would've picked you up.
You bought something again?
No, I didn't.
Dad, it's Hanako-san.
Isn't she in Aomori?
Hey, wait, wait, wait.
Huh?
Dad, Hanako-san chose
to be with you.
So, this time tell her about
your feelings.
Okay?
Off you go.
Hello.
What's up?
Where's Urara-san?
What are you talking about?
W-who's Urara-san?
I already know.
You don't have to hide.
Hello.
What?
- You knew Urara was my daughter?
- Yeah.
About living together
too, of course.
- Right?
- Right.
You didn't go home to Aomori?
Before I boarded,
I received a phone call.
Did you call her?
No, I didn't.
To tell you the truth,
I used my dad as an excuse
...to go back to Aomori.
See?
You planned to quit modeling?
I was happy to get scouted
by the industry, but...
all I get are jobs like fliers
for supermarkets, and stand-ins.
I was getting depressed.
But you see,
when I saw Urara at the
airport lobby trying to find Sensei
for me,
and running around desperately,
I remembered why I came to Tokyo.
I was reckless then.
But I believed in myself.
So in the past,
you were a trouble maker.
Maybe so.
I was reflecting on how much
I have become...
...quite a coward.
And then, a call from my
agency came.
They said to come for an audition.
It was an opportunity.
So, I called my father and
explained it to him.
He said "Don't come home."
Though he sounded lonely,
I'm sure he was happy for me.
Ah.
Thank you, Urara-san.
What?
Thanks to you,
I made up my mind.
If Urara-san didn't come,
I would have boarded the plane and
missed the call.
I'd be in Aomori by now,
taking care of my dad,
and would've forgotten about work.
See you later.
Huh? Ah, no, wait, wait a minute.
How do feel about my dad...
I'm glad he didn't come for me.
I was in a weak state,
I would've leapt into his arms.
Leap into his arms.
That's a different story.
See you.
Different story?
What was that?
That was it.
- Here you go.
- I'm sorry, thank you very much.
- Excuse me.
- Sure thing.
You dropped this.
Ah, thank you so much.
Welcome.
Did Hanako forget something?
What is it now?
What's this about?
Why is your mom here?
I don't know.
You told her you were renting
this room, right?
Ah, that's right.
I'm the one who should hide.
She'll find out.
No, no, no, no
Aren't you there?
Urara!
Geez, is she asleep?
- What should we do?
- What should we do...
I can't...
What?
It's Mom!
It's Mom, what should we do?
What's the plan?