- What, what?
- Just take a seat.
Plop, plop, plop.
Prologue begins
with anxiety and anticipation.
Ladies and gentlemen.
This is the summary so far.
Enjoy.
Summary?
- Urara's story.
- Huh?
Ta-da! This is Urara.
Urara lived with her father
who lived apart from each other...
..for 15 years.
But, one day...
...she thought she
is not needed by her father.
She went home in Kotohira.
Her father looked
for her everywhere.
He asked Hanako, a model,
Mama in Roppongi...
...and Ms Okuno at the gym,
but he couldn't find her.
- Why do they know that?
- Shush.
Her father asked Mr Sakurai
who works for him.
He finally realized she
went back to Kotohira.
There came Daisuke.
Whoo!
Me? What did I do?
As he realized Urara
was in Kotohira...
...he decided to visit
her by coach as usual.
Oh yes, that's true...
What? As usual?
But he gave his ticket
to her father...
...thinking she was waiting for him.
Her father went
to Kotohira by coach.
At the very moment, Urara
was heading to Tokyo by coach.
It is because she knew
her father cared for her.
The two coaches passed
each other on the highway.
Oh no.
But her father went back to Tokyo
soon, and they saw each other.
They lived happily ever after.
All's well that ends well.
- Oh? Is it an end?
- Not yet.
It has been two weeks since then.
Urara and her father
live in peace.
Mr Sakurai is taking a mock exam
for the Bar Exam.
Enjoy the rest online!
Or rather, on this channel.
Flat Out Tokyo Girl
The food is ready.
Wow! I'd love you
to cook for me every day.
Then, shall I be your Daddy's wife?
- No!
- Oh.
It's a joke. I won't steal
your Daddy from you.
- Really?
- Sure. Don't worry.
I'm just here to cook for you.
- Thank you so much.
- Not at all.
- Are you ready to eat?
- Yes, let's.
- Are you not eating with us?
- Sorry.
She eats with her dad.
Are you also going to be married...
...to your dad?
- Are you marrying to your Daddy?
- Yes!
It is lovely to hear in a way.
Of course, it must be.
I hope you do well
at tomorrow's exam.
Thank you so much.
Shall I start studying the law?
Oh? Do you mean
you want to be a lawyer?
Yes. You and my dad seem
to have a lot of fun with your job.
It's not fun.
Although it is a socially
meaningful profession.
Can I also take the Bar Exam?
- If I pass the preliminary exam.
- 25% pass the Bar Exam...
...but less than 3%
pass the preliminary exam.
What?
It is super difficult
to become a lawyer, then!
I'm home.
Welcome home.
What?
Urara?
- Urara!
- Yes?
What?
Is it mine?
It's Mr Sakurai's.
- Do you do washing for him?
- The workload is the same.
- Does that mean...
- Mean what?
Hey, please!
- Why do you put them in my drawers?
- So sorry.
They are clean anyway.
Hey, come here.
This is not what a 19 year old
would wear.
It's Hitomi's.
Mine is a lot sexier.
Stop joking.
Is it done?
What?
There.
Wow. That looks amazing.
It is done nicely.
Why did you roast two birds?
I'm practising.
I'm going to do a turkey roast
on Christmas Eve.
- Thanks for food.
- Here you are.
- Thanks.
What did you do for Christmas?
You've got three women.
Did you have three dates in one day?
- Huge risks!
- No, no!
- I spent Christmas on my own.
- Don't be silly.
I attended the mass...
- ...and quietly sung the hymns.
- And repent?
No! I spent Christmas
on my own.
- Good way to avoid conflicts?
- That's right.
This year, you'll spend Christmas
with your daughter.
Huh? Do you have a plan?
- Not really.
- I thought so.
Your girls seem to have
taken some distance.
Why don't you get back with my mum?
When I went back to Kotohira...
...my mum said she might call off
the marriage with Mr Sasaki.
She said so!
When I called her last week...
I broke up with Mr Sasaki.
What? Why?
Well, it is...
I don't like him jiggling his legs.
Jiggling the legs?
My mum won't...
...change her mind once she decides.
She certainly split up
with Mr Sasaki.
My mum is single.
Dad is kind of single too.
Why don't you
get back together?
- Urara...
- Well, it won't happen, will it?
You two had a big argument
the other time in Tokyo.
I wonder who will make you happy.
Hanako? Ms Okuno?
Haruka Mama?
Or... someone else
I don't know of?
Dad, you're not eating.
Have some more.
- We're home.
- Here are some...
...roast chicken for you.
It's nice.
Thank you.
It's nice!
Hey, Urara. Can you make it
for our Christmas party?
Ah, sorry. I'll celebrate
Christmas with my dad.
What?
- What?
- You seem like lovers.
That's not the case.
I'm home. I'm so hungry.
- Hello.
- Oh! Ah, I see.
- You arranged to meet then.
- With whom?
Mother.
- Whose mother?
- Yours.
- Huh? Where?
- Near where I work.
- She is in Kotohira.
- I'm sure I saw her.
Have you met her?
She came here once.
- You only had a glimpse of her.
- That's kind of true.
- What's this?
- Urara brought for us.
- Oh?
- What's up, Urara?
Hi mum. Where are you now?
- What do you mean, where?
- In Tokyo?
In Kotohira. I'm busy.
- See, she said she's in Kotohira.
- Really?
Yes, she is. You tell me lies
all the time.
- She might have seen me.
- Why didn't you tell her?
You couldn't tell her either!
So, what should we do?
(Mock Exam for the Bar Exam)
Good.
- Mr Sakurai.
- Urara.
- Were you waiting for me?
- Not really.
I came here for this.
Are you serious
about being a lawyer?
Yes.
I'll study hard from now,
and next year...
...pass the preliminary exam...
...and take the Bar Exam
the year after.
When I pass the exam,
you, my dad and I...
- ...can work together.
- Being lawyers...
- ...as dad and daughter. Nice.
- Will do my best.
Actually...
...I have a favor to ask you too.
- I'm home.
- Welcome home.
- Is Sakurai here?
- He finished the exam.
- Good evening.
- Hello, Hitomi.
- Hello.
- Good girl.
- How was it?
- Well.
- It went well.
- Are you sure?
Anyway, let's celebrate.
I made udon hot pot today.
Next May is going
to be the big exam.
- Keep your hard work.
- I know.
I'd like to ask you a favor.
- What?
- Let me support you.
No need for that.
Concentrate on your study.
But...
You know...
...keep studying may burn him out.
Our work is not a pass time.
But he can learn from it.
- No, I cannot help rely on him.
- Oh.
Then, like Chaconne for me...
- ...he can work part-time.
- Please consider that!
- Please consider.
- Please.
All right.
Let's eat for now.
Hitomi. I get it.
- I'll start from tomorrow.
- Good for you, Sakurai.
Oh, is Hitomi's mum coming back?
Just temporarily on Christmas Eve.
As her job in New York
has settled...
...she wants to have Hitomi.
- What? Will you let her go?
- I'll miss her.
You shouldn't.
How about Hitomi's feeling?
Of course, Hitomi wants
to stay with you.
She often cries, missing her mum.
It's hard for me to see that.
Dad.
How about getting together?
- Sure.
- For Hitomi, that'd be the best.
Don't you feel like
getting back together with her?
- I don't think it's possible.
- Is it so?
A child doesn't always
hold the marriage like a clamp.
A clamp?
A child is a clamp.
A clamp is a specific type
of nail to hold the wood.
Children can hold
the bond of a married couple.
I see.
So, Hitomi can glue Mr Sakurai
and his wife together.
Yes.
Isn't there a chance?
I fear we may not
get along well in the end.
How about you, sir?
- Well...
- I'm more than happy to be a glue.
Between my parents, there
is a long and deep rift.
As a daughter, I was happy
to hear they don't regret...
...their marriage itself.
- You know?
- Yeah.
That's true.
Without our marriage,
Hitomi wouldn't be here.
Sure.
- Hello.
- Yes.
- I see.
I made a packed lunch for all.
- This is for you.
- Thanks.
Here.
- This is yours.
- Yes.
And this is for my dad.
- Urara.
- Is my dad at the court?
- Isn't he at home?
- What?
- He left home as usual.
- He hasn't been here yet.
He hasn't got any trial today.
He said he'll work from home.
Did he say so?
Hello, it's T. Suzuki...
Oh, where are you now, sir?
Your client is dying to see you.
Sure. I will get in touch directly.
- Anything else?
- Where are you now?
I'm out of Tokyo.
Will be back tonight.
- Dad? Where are you?
- Oh.
- Where were you today?
- For work.
You hung me up.
- You didn't take my call.
- Ran out of battery.
- Suspicious.
- It's for work.
Ah, I'm tired.
I'll have a bath.
(Takamatsu - Haneda)
Takamatsu?
(Call from Urara)
- Hello. It is Urara?
- Hey.
- Did dad visit you?
- What?
I found a flight ticket
from Takamatsu.
Isn't it for the last visit?
It's from today.
I don't know about it.
Ask him. Bye.
(Takamatsu - Haneda)
- Hello.
Hello.
Is my dad meeting
with the client who called him?
I think that has been over.
He must be seeing someone.
Where was he yesterday?
I haven't heard about it.
Has he got a case in Shikoku?
No.
He is so suspicious...
...recently.
Do you know something?
- Is he suspicious?
- He is hiding something.
Hello. I'm busy.
I saw your mother again.
I told you that you haven't
seen her properly.
It is absolutely your mother.
Why can you say that?
Check it yourself then.
I am now at...
It's quite close from here.
What?
What is this?
Oh!
Mum, why are you in Tokyo?
Oh, well.
Why are you with dad?
Are you...
...discussing making me
return to Kotohira?
Is it so? Isn't it?
Say something.
- You say it.
So?
- Go on.
- What?
Say that.
What is it?
You are both acting weird.
Well, actually, I am thinking...
...of getting re-married.
What? You got back with Mr Sasaki?
It is not Mr Sasaki.
Then, who are you
going to marry?
- Otosan (Dad).
- Goto san?
- Otosan.
- Obosan (monk).
No. Him.
What?
We decided to be together again.
Oh you silly.
Stop joking like this.
It's not a joke.
But it sounds like a joke,
doesn't it?
What happened?
When I went to Kotohira
to pick you up...
- ...mum sent me to the airport.
- We had food before the flight.
- We talked then.
- Yes.
I spilled everything to him
after 15 years of separation.
Then, it cleared my mind.
- I could speak to Takuya honestly.
- Takuya?
Takuya Suzuki. Your dad.
We all know that.
Then, old embers of love
blazed anew...
Urara. Do you know what ember is?
It's not burning pinecone
but timber.
We don't need the explanation.
I thought I'd like to spend
the rest of my life with Takuya.
I feel in the same way.
Urara.
Will you be happy for us?
Of course. I said "why don't you
get back together?"
- See?
- Yes.
Why didn't you tell me earlier?
I thought so but I couldn't
find the moment to say it.
Mum, you should have told me
when I called you.
Sorry. I feared you would
disagree.
Disagree?
Why would I disagree?
I'll go to the toilet.
Oh, it wasn't here.
Your dad used to be so unreliable
before, but he grew up a lot.
He apologized to me, so I thought
I should reflect on myself.
I could have hung onto it
a bit longer 15 years ago.
Then, we didn't have to...
Urara! Are you listening?
- Yeah... I am.
- Are you?
Sorry, I'm sleepy.
Isn't it early for bedtime?
Oh?
- Oh, hey!
- Where's everyone?
They went out somewhere.
Then, you will do, Daisuke.
Re-marrying?
Your dad is cool.
- I'm not happy.
- Why?
You worked so hard
so that your dad will be happy.
- True.
- That was your purpose.
- What are you not happy about?
The person who can
make my dad happy...
- ...is my mum?
- Isn't it?
If your mum is marrying your dad...
...you can live with him.
- Don't treat me like a child.
- What do you want?
Are you no plotting something again?
- OK.
- Hey, wait. Wait!
What is "OK"?
What does that mean?
Pay for your tea.
Hanako, your acquaintance
is here to see you.
Sorry I couldn't take your call.
What was so urgent?
- Hey, what...
- Hanako.
- Please marry my dad.
- Oh.
- That again?
- It is urgent!
- What does it mean?
- Hanako.
- Please come along.
- Sure.
- Sorry.
- Wait!
I'll call you later. Bye!
- Shall we go, Ryota?
- Bye.
- Bye-bye.
- Bye, Ryota.
Bye-bye.
Oh, hello.
Was it...?
My ex-husband.
Today is the day for him
to see our son...
...but I was busy and
I asked them to come here.
You all look like a good family.
Just in front of Ryota.
How about getting back?
Can't imagine.
We may happen to think of that,
but it won't last.
I know!
But sometimes I feel...
...I can be together again
for Ryota.
A child holds the bond?
I don't think it'd be
the case for me.
It'll be father and mother of Ryota,
rather than a couple.
We may love someone else.
Is that the reason
you won't remarry with him?
Kind of.
- How about my dad?
- He seems...
...to be cumbersome to live with.
No, no, no.
Not so bad.
He doesn't want people to enter
the study, but no need to worry.
- He likes most...
- What?
- Are you pushing him?
- Yeah.
- Can you marry him?
- Sorry. Ask someone else.
Oh really.
- See you later.
- See you!
Oh.
Your dad was trying
to hook up with Yoko.
Yoko?
I'm new here.
My name is Yoko!
She is not new.
That's her strategy.
She got the most proceeds
last week.
What? Is it really so?
Thanks for bringing her.
She is not fit to be my dad's wife.
Are you coming tomorrow?
Oh, me? I am...
Thank you so much.
Oh really. Your dad
is re-marrying your mum.
I'm afraid so.
Mama!
- Will you marry him?
- Sorry.
- Here is today's takings.
- Thanks.
My club just started
to make profits.
I'd like to expand my business.
I'm hoping to open another place.
Of course I like him.
In terms of business too.
I'd like to be good friends.
I see.
Isn't he going
to get together with his ex...
...for you, Rei?
What?
He won't feel inconvenient
from being single.
It must be easy for him to find
someone young and pretty.
I see.
- Dad?
- Oh, Urara. Urara.
- Mum arrived in Kotohira.
- Hey, dad.
What?
Are you re-marrying
with mum for me?
Hey. Is it so?
It's partly true.
- Then, please don't.
- Huh?
Don't re-marry her.
Hey, Urara. Wait.
Aren't you be happy for us?
I don't like it to be for me.
You can't be happy with mum.
Huh? What are you talking about?
You should think
about it yourself.
Hey, wait.
Come here. Wait.
- Where are you going?
- Don't worry.
- I'm going to Yukari's.
- Wait.
Don't follow me.
What?
- See you later!
- Bye.
Bye, Urara.
- See you.
- Ah, dad.
Don't forget to take the medicine.
Mum will be angry at me
when you forget.
- OK.
- Bye.
- See you later.
- Welcome!
- Hello.
- Welcome.
Ah, Hanako.
Sorry for asking you to meet me
early in the morning.
- Not at all. Sorry about yesterday.
- Come with me.
Urara said she
is not happy about us.
Why is that?
She was happy before.
Yeah. I don't really know.
OK.
That's how it happened.
I see.
You are not happy about
your dad re-marrying?
No! Because...
...isn't it odd for him
to remarry not "for him"...
...but "for me"?
It shouldn't happen.
He won't be happy for that.
I think the one who can
make him happy...
...would be you, Hanako.
Hanako.
Get my dad from my mum.
Urara, do you not like your mum?
I love her. But...
Remarrying is not
the right decision.
Your mum will be sad
if I get your dad.
I know that.
Urara.
You don't want
your mum to take him.
You want to live
with your dad forever.
- That's not...
- You don't realize.
Don't judge me like that.
I can see.
I know how you feel.
I feel the same.
I love him.
Hello.
One Margherita and
two coffee.
Certainly.
What's up?
I heard about you and your ex-wife.
Ah, about that...
I was asked to take you from her.
Take me?
Urara always wanted you
to get married.
Yes.
But she wants you to herself.
Although she said
she was on my side...
...if I say I'd marry you...
...she'll oppose to it.
I know.
Do you?
- Yes.
- Do you know why?
Yes.
You should...
...properly speak to her.
Wait.
- What's up?
- What?
You called me.
What happened?
Is he re-marrying?
I don't know why I am not happy.
You don't think this would
make him unhappy, do you?
Did you part with your dad
at the age of four?
Yes.
Hitomi really likes me now.
She talks to me a lot.
She wants me to hold her.
But...
...in 15 years, she'll
have a boyfriend.
She'll be just thinking about him.
I'll miss her, but that's the life.
You are the same age as Hitomi.
That can't be helped.
There's a 15-year gap.
You're trying to fill the gap.
Why are you up this early?
Joanna is going back to France.
What? Really?
Yes, at the end of this year.
My dad just called me and
said he really misses me.
- Your dad?
- Can we come to France?
Of course. I'll treat you.
- Really?
- Actually...
- What?
- I have decided...
...to go to Cambodia.
- What?
- Cambodia? Where mum is?
- Yes.
- She's doing removal of landmine.
- Yes, she is.
We've been apart for so long.
I miss her.
It's fine, but what about this cafe?
- Daisuke. You take care of it.
- What, me?
- He can't do anything.
- Hey, I can do something.
- He studied economics at the uni.
- What?
- Did you go to the university?
- Yes.
- I'm not just a part-timer.
- A graduate, part-timer.
Oh yes! Why don't you
run this place together?
- Huh?
- You're good at cooking.
Ah.
That sounds good. I always wanted
to have a udon restaurant.
- Sure. Let's renovate it all.
- You can't!
- He is hitting on her now.
- Oh really?
Are you not going
to be a lawyer?
- Urara.
- That's another matter.
- I told you not to come.
- Let's go home.
- No.
- Let's talk.
I talked to you.
Listen to your dad!
Dad?
Sorry that my daughter
bothered you.
Take a seat.
15 years since I left
you and your mum...
...I lived as I wish.
But I reunited with you
and started to live with you.
At first, it was annoying.
See...
...I have no one else who
would comment on me.
But it was refreshing too.
Since you came to the house,
I started to have breakfast.
Now I have dinner at home
more often. I came to like udon too.
I felt I have a family.
- Family?
- Your cooking.
It's similar to your mum.
I started to see the good side
of family life.
I went to Kotohira the other day.
- I saw the flight ticket.
- Huh?
Your mum showed me the 15 years
of memory you spent in Kotohira.
Look. This is...
...Urara's hand print
at kindergarten and her score card.
- There.
- Wow.
Her essay at junior high school.
She showed me the photos.
Your mum neatly...
...sorted all the photos
on digital camera.
Just looking at them...
...won't fill the gap,
but I could feel it.
15 years of your life.
When I spoke to Daisuke
the other day...
...I said "Marriage is to
be responsible for someone's life."
But I want to change...
Not a change, an addition.
Marriage is...
...to share the time together.
Of course, you can't share the past,
but the present and the future.
When I was with her,
I thought she is perfect to me.
- But it didn't work out.
- I know. But...
...we've grown up.
Thanks to you.
So, Urara.
I'd like you to be happy
for us to re-marry.
Urara.
- Thank you so much. Sure.
- I'll be back on 14th.
OK.
So sorry. It's closed already...
Urara.
What did you show to dad?
- These.
- Huh? These?
Wow.
"Memory".
What's this?
I told you your dad is alive
on your birthday.
I wanted to show this to you then...
...but you got so angry
that I didn't have a moment.
What is this?
Your photos with your dad.
I didn't throw them away.
What?
Though you don't remember this.
I am sorry...
...for not telling you
about your dad.
If you don't want it,
I won't re-marry him.
Family.
I wonder who it is.
He thought you'd be here.
Urara.
Dad.
Mum.
I will...
...be happy for you!
- What?
What? Really? What?
There we go.
Cheese.
How's that?
It looks like the duck
is stuck on you.
Stuck on me?
However.
There is a condition
for my blessing.
A condition?
What? Oh no.
What would it be?