Let's go over the hills while
whistling songs.
Sky is blue.
Let's go to the farm.
Why did I sleep here?
Dad?
I know her dad.
I'll go home if you admit
you're my dad.
I don't know.
Do you remember me
when I was small?
You are my dad, right?
Why do you want me sent home?
Your mom must be worried.
She's getting remarried,
I have no place at home.
I don't want you to have
bad eating habits and sex life.
Get out. I want to take shower.
Let's go over the hills while
whistling songs.
Get out now. I am busy
in the morning.
Sky is blue...
Dad.
Why do you have a woman's
bathrobe?
Did you eat breakfast?
- I don't want it.
- You should.
It's not your business.
I'll cook breakfast now.
Did you go out?
Yes. It was all right.
That's like Tokyo.
What if other residents see you?
I'll say good morning.
No worries.
- Oh...
- What?
I forgot to buy miso.
I'll go buy it.
No, it's ok.
You don't want it?
Don't go dressed like that.
People wear pajamas.
No. I said no.
Get changed now.
Ok.
Let's go.
Wait a second.
Work again?
Sorry.
Good morning.
Today's lawsuit starts
at 3PM, right?
Yes. District court, Room 403.
Got an 11AM meeting with Wagner
Trading Co.
Move it to dinner.
I'll work at home today.
Ok.
Can you pick me up early today?
Sure. Let's go.
Mushroom, mushroom...
Oh. Are you good at cooking?
Mom taught me.
I'm sure you remember
how it tastes.
Thanks.
Hum...
Let's eat.
I have to leave home after lunch.
Let's make a decision by then.
Decision?
I'm sorry, but I can't
see you as my daughter.
I'm sure you can't see me
as your father.
You are different from who I thought
to be my dad.
I didn't have a photo of you,
so I drew a picture.
I asked mom how you look like.
Am I different?
Much better.
What I drew was a mean pig
with evil horns.
That's awful.
Because you are a devil.
You left mom and I.
So you can't see me as your father.
But you are my dad.
I am your daughter regardless
of what you think.
I can't understand because
I didn't see you grow.
So I think it's good to live
together and understand each other.
We spend time together,
talk and...
- Hey.
- Don't call me "Hey".
Call me Urara first.
You named me, right?
It means sunny and peaceful.
You wanted me to grow
as so named.
Your mom named you.
She said you two thought it up
together.
Call me Urara.
Sorry, but I have no...
Miss Urara.
I have no time to be together
and talk.
I am busy working.
You have time for the gym or a bar.
That's part of my job.
I don't see any relation between
bar and a job as a lawyer.
How about your job?
You said you graduated
high school.
Mom told me to go to
a beauty school.
But I don't think that suits me.
I did part-time at an Udon shop.
You have to go back, then.
I quit before I came here.
Mom wants me to take over
her beauty salon.
She says I should acquire technical
skills for the future.
But in Kotohira, she always
cut hair of the same customers.
Some patrons have been coming to
her salon for 10 years.
I hate being in a small world.
I can't do it for my life.
That's why I came to Tokyo.
Then you shouldn't live with me.
- Why?
You want to kick me out
somehow.
This apartment is too small
for two people.
This is big enough.
I can't sleep on the sofa.
You can sleep in my bed.
I can't live with others.
Daughter.
Why don't you live in
a different apartment?
Oh?
Don't you remember
what you said when we met?
You will have an experience
even worse than today.
You had your money stolen
and learnt a lesson.
You'll toss me out to the streets
knowing it's dangerous out there.
There is a safe place in Tokyo.
Are you a sophist,
or a lawyer?
Postman?
- Who?
- Nothing.
Look! There is a UFO.
Why is she here so early?
She comes in the morning?
No.
- Don't you open the door?
- No.
Wait a second.
I opened a door.
Go hide.
Why?
You understand?
No.
Yes.
Hurry up.
No.
Miss Urara.
Hurry up and hide.
Hurry up.
Huh? Whatever.
What are you doing?
Sorry. I know it's early.
You are always welcome.
I have a business trip to Hakone
tonight.
Sounds good.
But I heard it's cold there.
I left my blue coat last night.
- Hey!
- Huh?
Here it is.
Why did you come last night?
What's wrong?
It's late.
Well...
Are you ok?
You look down.
There was something I was
worrying about, you know.
But it's done.
Good.
What noise was that?
It was this clock.
It's acting strange these days.
Does the alarm go on and off
by itself?
It was close.
I'm off now.
Have a good day.
Good morning.
Good morning, my friends.
Please record your message
after the tone.
I'm off.
Take care.
Thanks.
It was close.
Why did you hide?
You will be in a trouble
if she sees me, Dad.
It's also better for me that
they don't know who I am.
I'll protect you.
I will find out why many women
come around you.
Why?
Haruta at Chaconne bar
is a gold digger.
He is a good customer.
He wouldn't say no if you ask.
Drink lots of bubblies.
How much have you spent
at Chaconne?
Ms. Okuno, a gym instructor.
I know about your weekend trip.
Are you available this weekend?
I booked the hotel you wanted.
She has another boyfriend.
I saw her calling.
Hi, Ryota.
What dinner do you want?
You didn't know that, right?
She is two-timing you.
So is Hanako.
A day trip to Hakone
can't be a business trip.
I'm sure she has a boyfriend.
Go back to Kotohira today.
I'll clean the house.
Let me find...
No.
But it's messy.
I have a helper coming
twice a week.
Ms. Mita?
Don't touch anything here.
Especially the library.
I have many court documents.
You will ruin my client's life
if you lose them.
See you later.
Don't touch anything.
When we are told
not to do something,
we are the more eager to do so .
What's this?
Hanako Serizawa.
Hello.
Is Henry here?
I think so. He always is.
I'm home.
Hello.
How are you?
Is Henry here?
You have a guest.
Would you like lunch?
I had a big breakfast.
It's good. Try next time.
Thank you.
Hello, Henry.
You're a model?
Yes, I am.
Do you know a model
named Hanako Serizawa?
Hanako Serizawa?
Zip Promotion... I know it.
But too many models
belong in here.
I'm sure most models have leisure
time.
Not all of them. There are
many types of people there.
Some of them are aggressive
about it.
I thought so.
I heard that some girls go for
one night stand just to get a job.
That's how it is?
Not around me.
I just know as a rumour.
Rumour.
Yeah, that's it.
Thank you for waiting.
Today's lunch is a Mongolian dish.
Steamed Udon with lamb
and vegetables.
I have to go.
See you later.
I don't want you to call me.
You ignored it.
Did you need to talk to me?
- Yes.
- What?
Guess why I called you.
I don't know.
Think.
I don't care.
Takuya Suzuki.
Do you want to know
where he is?
I met him already.
There are four candidates.
Did you find him?
Wait a minute.
Was it in Setagaya? Which was it?
Neither.
You must be joking.
Thanks for trying to find him.
Cute.
He likes that.
I'll come again.
See you.
Bye.
Wait a second.
FLAT OUT TOKYO GIRL
You can't be a detective.
Hello.
Hi. You came back.
Is he your friend?
No.
Introduce me.
I'm Hanako.
I am Daisuke Tamagawa.
I heard that you went home
yesterday.
I decided to stay in Tokyo
for a while?
I see.
Do you have enough money?
Yes.
Did you find your Dad?
- No.
- You just said...
What's wrong?
What are you doing?
Foot?
Good luck.
Tell me if you need me.
Thanks.
Can we exchange phone numbers?
Sure. I forgot to tell you mine.
Can I call you?
Sure.
Hanako.
Do you have a boyfriend?
You are rude.
What's your relationship to that
lawyer?
He helps me a lot.
Isn't he your boyfriend?
I don't know.
Are you interested in
anyone else?
Sorry, I have to close the store.
It's still noon.
I have to go to the office.
Until evening?
I have another job
tonight.
I wanted to sell them all today.
Another job?
I can stay here til you're back.
Really?
Will you come back before
your night job?
I rent this space until 6PM.
I will be back by then.
Let's help her.
Sure.
Will you help me, then?
No problem.
Thank you.
Use money in this box for change.
Then, I'll see you later.
Take care.
Nice smile.
Good.
You look wonderful.
That's great.
Come on.
Keep going.
Ok. That's all.
Changing spots.
Give me the basket.
Thank you.
Oh, no.
What's wrong?
I wanted to know what
a fashion model does
so I came to see you.
Daisuke is taking care of
your shop now.
Please don't worry.
Ok.
What are you shooting?
Ads for magazines.
- I see.
- Hi, Hana.
Long-time no see.
How have you been?
Somehow I survive.
Are you in love with someone now?
I don't know.
I wish you the best.
I like you so much.
Thank you.
Mr. Higashi, come check.
Ok.
Is he your ex?
No way.
But...
"From Kojima"
He is always like that to everyone.
Come with me.
See?
Please come in.
Ok.
I'll put them back.
See you later.
Kojima?
Yotsui Trading Company?
Please forgive me.
Hi, I am Kojima.
Come to the cafe at Akasaka
Celestine Hotel at 7PM.
Wanna go to a restaurant or do
room service?
Huh?
I thought she was going to Hakone.
Don't worry about the audition
for Clover magazine's cover.
I took care of everything.
Looking forward to
seeing you tonight.
Is this what Henry was
talking about?
I heard that some girls
go for one night stand
just to get a job, you know.
Are you ready?
Nice smile.
Wonderful.
Keep going.
I'll tell him.
Hello.
Ok, I'll be there
as soon as possible.
Is Dad here?
He is at the court now.
Sorry.
Hi, I am Sakurai.
Nursery called me that
Hitomi got a fever.
I'll be there as soon as possible.
Urara is here now.
Let's go.
- Hurry up.
- What?
Keep going.
See you tomorrow.
Are you leaving now?
- Have a wonderful night with him.
- Thanks.
Thank you.
From 2,000 yen, please.
I'll get the change.
Hurry up.
Hurry.
I'm Hitomi Sakurai's dad.
Thank you.
Mushroom...
Hello.
Huh?
Are you ok, Hitomi?
Daddy.
Her fever goes down now.
She needs rest.
Thank you.
You better sleep at home.
Are you going out again, Daddy?
No. I'll stay with you tonight.
Mr. Sakurai, you better
take her to see a doctor.
You are right.
Hitomi.
Doctor said you'll be fine soon.
Go to bed and sleep
and your cold will go away.
Dad is coming to bed soon.
Ok.
Get some sleep.
Thank you.
Oh, no.
I thank you for your help
yesterday.
No problem.
Did you stay at his home
last night?
Yes. Thank you.
That's good.
You are so busy.
Huh?
You work while raising a kid.
And you have to study for
your bar exam.
I think lawyer is an important
job in society.
So I don't think I'm busy.
I can do anything for Hitomi.
That's like a father.
Hitomi is the most important to me.
I'll go.
I almost forgot.
Remember that lady who left before
us?
Before us?
When we entered the nursery,
we came across a cute-looking
lady with a boy.
She is Ryota's mom.
Ryota?
Yes. She is a single mother.
Ryota was not her boy...
Yes, he is.
Right.
She works and raises her son
at the same time.
I guess so.
I see her sometimes but
we don't talk personally.
Is she dating my dad?
With him?
She works as an instructor at the
gym Dad goes to.
Didn't you know?
No.
He doesn't talk about
his private life.
Did you want to see him?
Oh, you are right.
Thank you.
See you.
I can't sell any.
What is Urara Saeki doing?
This is cute.
Hello, there.
Would you like to try this on?
Everything is 500 yen.
It's worn only once by
a cute model.
Please wait.
It smells nice.
What are you doing?
Huh?
I'm looking after the shop.
These are women's' clothes.
- This your shop?
- No. My friend's.
- Who?
- Hanako.
What's her family name?
You look after a shop of
a person you don't know?
Huh?
Are you suspicious of me?
Court
Left.
What is your eyesight?
I don't know.
You have several glasses.
Yes.
You have glasses with strong and
weak lenses and bifocals.
Hum...
Which glasses did you wear
on that day?
- Don't recall.
- Let me ask another question.
What's the optical power of your
lens?
Don't know exactly.
Hum... That's strange.
The court is adjourned today.
Excuse me.
- Trying to get in?
- Yes.
But it's finished.
No.
- Dad.
- Hush!
Ms. Okuno at Renascence
sports club has a child.
- I know.
- Huh?
His name is Ryota.
Then you know about Hanako?
What is it?
She said she has a business
trip to Hakone tonight,
but it's a lie.
Actually, she's going to an Akasaka
hotel
to have a one night stand
to get a job.
That's enough.
It's true.
It's Akasaka Celestine Hotel.
- With a man named...
- She's not like that.
I heard it.
From who?
Huh?
Well...
Why me?
- I'll find evidence!
- No.
Daisuke Tamagawa.
Hello.
Where are you?
I forgot about you.
The police came.
Huh? Did you act as
a molester or something?
No way.
The police wants to see you.
You!
The police wants to see me?
Yes. I am closing the shop.
Go to Shimokita Police Dept.
directly from there.
Ok.
You have to wait for Hanako
to close the shop.
She's already here.
She is going to meet with
Kojima at 7PM.
Huh?
Bye.
Darn it.
Thank you for looking after
my shop.
No problem. It was fun.
Um...
Would you like to go out
for dinner after this?
Huh?
You said you have another
job tonight. I'll wait for you.
The customer complains that
our hostess is going bad.
You must scout better talents.
I am trying.
Shimoyama.
Hello. This way please.
Hello.
I'll leave it to you.
Ok. I'll go back to the bar.
See you later.
I am hungry.
Order whatever you like.
I will unmask Hanako's
true nature.
Hello.
Hi, Rei.
Can you come today?
You are becoming popular.
Sorry, but I'm not
interested in hostess.
Wait a minute.
We can talk about your wage.
Hello. This is Kojima.
What's wrong?
Sorry, but I'm busy.
I am waiting for a girl now.
Yes, I talked about her.
Audition?
It's already taken by
another model.
Am I bad?
I can't push a girl whom
I slept with.
Hang on a second.
Here is a girl who wants to
hook up with me.
May I help you?
Why did you hit him?
He said he didn't know you
and had no idea why
you hit him.
You have to stay here
if you don't answer me.
Tell me your home number.
I'll call your folks.
I am already 19.
Your age doesn't matter.
Call a lawyer then.
Hey.
Are you coming to the bar
tonight?
Let me think about it.
- You're mean.
- Just kidding. I'll come.
Will you order two bottles of
champagne?
Huh?
Excuse me.
What is this number?
Hello.
Huh?
Ok.
I'll be there right away.
I can't believe this.
- Is that an urgent business?
- Yes.
Sorry about that.
I'm not done eating.
I can't believe this.
What are you doing?
- Ouch.
- Shut up.
Ouch.
How could you use violence?
I explained why.
Hanako is bad, but I can't
forgive a man who deceived her.
You're lucky he didn't file a claim,
but what you did was a crime.
- But...
- What are you doing from yesterday?
Snuck into a gym, had a job
at Chaconne...
you went out wearing a bath robe
this morning,
And look what you did just now.
This is enough.
Go back to Kotohira tomorrow.
They're not related.
Yes, they are.
Don't cause me any more trouble.
You mean that.
Yes. Go home.
No, I won't.
- Go home.
- No, I won't.
No, I won't.
I won't go home.
Ok. You stay in Tokyo.
But I won't take care of you.
I want us to live together
no matter what.
They you pay accommodation fee.
Huh?
All right then.
What?
3,000 yen for breakfast.
Pay me for breakfast if you ask me
to pay rent.
It's too expensive.
Hotel breakfast is expensive.
Then pay 10,000 yen per night.
That's unreasonable.
Go home if you can't pay.
I can be your guarantor.
All right.
I'll pay 10,000 yen per night.
What is it?
What's this?
621,000 yen.
It's gone. That was
all the money I had.
It was a luggage lifter
who stole your money.
A luggage lifter was arrested
and I got my money back.
Keep this as accommodation fee.
Hey! Don't touch it.
Hanako Serizawa.
I'm sorry for Hanako.
She couldn't be the magazine cover.
Hello?
I had a message from Mr. Kojima.
What did he say?
I've already told him that
I wouldn't need his help.
Did she...?
But he was hit by a girl
whom he didn't know.
Know anything about it?
No. Nothing.
All right.
I'm going to a hot spring then.
Sounds nice.
Many things come up
in my mind.
You're joking.
Bye.
Hanako went to Hakone.
She wasn't planning to go to
the hotel in Akasaka.
You heard us this morning.
Why did you come yesterday?
I needed your advice.
But the problem was solved.
Kojima has a bad reputation.
But it'll be a problem if she makes
waves.
She told him she had a business
trip and she wouldn't come.
Do you know what this means?
I made a lot of fuss for nothing.
Exactly.
I'm hungry.
That's what I wanted to say.
I cancelled my dinner.
Ok.
What is it?
Where are you going?
Are you going out to eat?
That's not fair.
All right then.
I'll have this.
"Tamagawa"
Yay! I won.
What's wrong with Daisuke?
It happens again.
He fell in love again.
Again?
It should be Urara.
You are right.
Hey.
I hear your secret talk.
I know.
Why do you always challenge
the hard one?
She should be even harder.
She is older than I.
It's not Urara.
He falls in love too quickly.
Is that my gene?
I'm hungry.
Cook me something.
You said you would eat out.
I thought I would.
But I couldn't wait for her
to come back from Hakone.
What now?
I dropped a box of flour.
What were you trying to do?
I wanted to cook
delicious Udon for you.
Udon?
Cook it from scratch?
I worked part-time at an Udon
restaurant.
But you didn't cook, right?
I can cook.
What are these tools?
I bought them at a home centre
nearby.
It has everything.
It's a big help.
I'm impressed.
I'll smash this with my feet.
Dad.
Knock first.
- Want to stomp on Udon?
- No.
I stomp on it several times,
let it rest...
and Udon will be done.
Oh.
Hey, isn't it done yet?
It's 3AM.
I need to let it rest to make
delicious Udon.
Do it tomorrow.
I'll be done soon. Just sit and
wait.
Hot.
Let's cook delicious Udon.
Thank you for waiting.
It's ready.
Here you go.
Let's eat.
Ok.
Isn't it delicious?
By the way...
Ryota, Ms. Okuno's son...
Is he yours?