Hey.
Are you OK?
I'm OK.
Driver! Pull over the bus.
She's not feeling well.
Dad, mum...
...I wish your happiness.
Oh no!
Don't go!
Urara, Urara!
Urara. Urara.
Urara.
Mum.
Oh good. I thought you're dead.
Where am I?
What are you talking about?
It's your room.
You talked asleep.
Talked asleep?
"Dad, mum, I wish your happiness."
So you said.
It's noon.
Come and eat.
Was it a dream?
(October)
Flat Out Tokyo Girl
Hey, mum! Mum, Listen!
It's great.
What is?
It's all dream.
- All?
- Yes.
On my 19th birthday...
- ...you celebrated it with me.
- And?
You finally told me...
...your secret.
"I told you your divorced
father was dead...
...but actually he is alive."
I was so surprised.
I was angry to hear you kept
such an important secret.
I went to Tokyo.
With all the savings I had.
To live in Tokyo,
not to search for my dad.
I said I wanted to go there.
I know.
And then...
...I had all the saving with me...
...on the day of arrival...
...it was stolen!
I got to know a model...
...who introduced me
to a person who...
...turns out to be my dad.
What he said to me first
was "Get me the underpants."
Can you believe that?
So funny!
And dad was a lawyer.
Really.
But as I get to know him,
he was dating with the model,...
...an instructor at the gym,...
...and mama of the bar in Roppongi.
Three women at once!
Three at once?
But he is kind of likable.
You said he was devilish...
...but it wasn't true.
I couldn't leave him alone
and started to live with him.
You got happy
by re-marrying Mr Sasaki.
So I wanted him to be happy
by finding someone.
As I wasn't sure who
he loved the most...
...actually he didn't
know himself...
...I called them all at once
to the flat.
All?
Three girlfriends.
But not all could come
so it didn't happen.
But they all started
to take some distance from him.
I thought Hanako, the model...
...was his love, and
I tried hard to put them together.
They are too proud maybe.
They didn't follow their hearts.
They just remained
cool to each other.
How about the other two?
They were more
of cool relationships...
...than lovers.
Even if they run into each other...
...I don't think they would fight.
Do you understand that?
Kind of.
Oh, yes!
You also came to Tokyo.
Oh really?
I didn't tell you...
...I met my dad
and lived with him...
...dad and I both
were in such a haste!
But you found it out
in the end.
You also worked as a hostess
in a club.
Well, you finally...
...approved that I lived with dad
and returned home.
What? Did I approve?
As you said good bye...
...you told me that he liked
freshly boiled udon noodle.
Is that the approval?
I don't think so.
I think so.
That's your interpretation.
Maybe.
It's only my dream.
I see.
Then, why did you come home?
I was planning to stay with my dad
until I made him happy...
...he doesn't seem to think
he needs me.
He asked Ms Shimizu
when he could ask me.
Who?
An admin person.
Dad makes such effort
about Mr Sakurai...
...but not me.
That's why...
...I got on the coach.
The lights of Tokyo in distance.
I briefly thought of my dad.
Good bye, dad!
As the bus approached
Kotohira...
...somehow I started to feel sick.
I had a fever and had a bad dream.
The bus was crossing
the Seto Ohashi Bridge.
In the coach...
...I wish the happiness...
...of dad and mum...
...as I died.
Dad, mum...
...I wish your happiness.
Are you done?
Thank you for food.
What was that?
It was a story of my dream.
You only slept a few hours.
Dreams can be really long.
I feel as if I saw eight episodes
of drama series.
Urara, are you still not awake?
I am awake.
I wonder why
I remember it so vividly.
Dreams are usually elusive.
It is because that wasn't a dream.
What?
On your 19th birthday...
...you went to Tokyo
as you heard your dad was alive.
I also went to Tokyo.
Where you die in the bus
is probably a dream.
But it's October.
- December!
- Really?
See? It's October.
See? It's December.
Why don't you look
at the bus ticket?
(30th November)
What a sleepy-head you are.
I see.
I knew it. It was too real.
You came home for such a reason.
Welcome home.
Thanks.
Oh no!
What?
I bought something online.
I couldn't receive it then.
They only keep it for me
until today.
What should I do?
Who knows?
Hello. T. Suzuki Law Firm.
Sure.
I will tell him.
Where from?
From Municipal Central Hospital.
Hospital?
About the check-up.
I was told not to cancel
the slot on the day after tomorrow.
We have postponed many times.
- Can't be bothered.
- You have to...
...be there at eight in the morning.
Sure.
Well. What shall I do
about Mr Sakurai?
Let him know.
Certainly.
(13:06)
Well, where are you?
When you hear this,
call me back immediately.
OK?
Don't put me in trouble.
Hello.
Are you going to see my dad today?
Not really. But why?
Well, I would like you
to tell something to my dad.
Will you take a note?
OK.
Just a second.
Oh, excuse me.
OK.
It's Penguin Delivery.
The receipt number is...
...19931225.
Will you tell him
to receive it within today?
Urara. Are you leaving home again?
Ah, well, how can I say...
Was there something
with your dad?
Um, well, not really.
Why don't we meet?
I can listen to you.
Thank you.
But...
(An interview sheet)
"Do you like spicy food?"
- "Neither."
- Hello. Come in.
- Hello.
- What's up?
Urara called me.
Here.
Receive that today.
So she is not coming home today?
Apparently so.
Where is she?
I don't know.
Really?
Urara sounded she wants
you to find out.
Find out?
Where is that?
Bye.
What, hey...
Did you come here for this?
Excuse me.
See you later.
Rudolf, the red-nosed reindeer
- Had a very shiny nose
- Hello.
- Hi!
- Wow, it's Christmas.
Yeah, let's make it fancy!
Sorry!
Hello.
Urara's father.
- Hello.
Isn't Urara here?
- She's not here, right?
- No.
Is there a Mongolian person?
I used to be one.
You let her stay before.
Yes! But she's not with me today.
You know where she is?
Um...well...
Perhaps...
What?
She can be in Daisuke's room!
I'm home.
- Hello.
What's happened?
Apparently, Urara is gone.
Do you know where she is?
- No.
- When did you see her last?
I went to the zoo
the day before yesterday.
The zoo?
It wasn't a date.
We went with Hitomi.
Wasn't she different?
Not really.
What did she say?
She repeated she wanted her dad
to be happy.
Ah, but I...
...advised her to think about
herself, which she didn't get.
I see.
- Thank you.
- Not at all.
Sorry for bothering you.
Ah, sorry.
Did you have an argument?
There were some days
when she didn't come home, but...
...unlike those times
we had no argument.
OK. I'll look for her too.
Thanks.
If you find anything...
- ...call me on my mobile.
- Sure.
Excuse me.
If she is not here...
(Haruka)
This is the voice message service.
After the beep...
Urara.
- Yes?
- Your friend is here.
That's cute.
Oh, actually.
Urara, do you know
Satomi got married?
With whom?
Takahashi senpai.
Really?
Although she was with Onishi before.
How about you, Urara?
Did you meet someone in Tokyo?
No.
Are there many handsome guys
in Tokyo?
Not really.
Tomochan!
Asuka!
Oh, Urara?
- Long time no see!
- I know.
Kotohira is such a small place.
- You went to Tokyo.
- Yes.
What do you do?
Various things.
Hello.
What are you doing here?
I am a member here.
Are you?
Well, yes. I didn't
know that at all.
We have different time schedules.
I called just now.
Urara didn't come
yesterday, did she?
I guess.
Do you know
where she is?
I don't know when she is off work.
I see.
Ask Shimoyama.
Tell me his number.
Oh, sure.
Hello.
Hi.
Have you got
used to it?
Yes. Thank you so much.
She's working for me.
I'd like to save up for a trip.
Ms Okuno introduced me to her.
- Okuno?
- Yes.
I did.
Precisely, she is
a substitute for Urara.
What a network.
She is mama.
- I'm Okuno.
- Hello.
Have I seen you somewhere?
Sorry.
Yes?
Okuno. Come.
Can I ask you something?
Come.
I heard...
... you often go to her bar.
Not really.
You are so close to her.
It's not true.
Shall I start working there?
Stop that.
You can't work
for the whole day for Ryota.
Why do you take it seriously?
I'm joking.
By the way...
...where is Urara?
Urara?
I saw at Mr Sakurai's.
Wasn't she different?
Not really.
Um, excuse me.
I just joined the gym.
Can I ask some questions?
Sure.
Bye.
Let's go.
I want to get fit.
There're plenty of things
we can work on!
Ah, thank you!
Come here.
Hello.
- Hello.
Who is that?
Who are you?
Hi, I'm Suzuki.
I'm so sorry.
I didn't know the number.
No worries.
I thought Rei was
not there yesterday.
Have you heard anything?
Anything?
Like where she stays.
No, not really.
OK.
(Sayuri Hairdresser)
Well.
Let's start eating.
Thanks for food!
They look lovely.
What is that reaction?
Your home cooking
is really good.
You can cook nice food too.
Dad always say it's good.
Sure.
What is he eating today?
You can call him.
Oh, yes.
No.
He probably eats out with someone.
Nice.
Nothing in here.
What did she buy online?
(Food)
Sounds good.
Good, good.
Dried bonito?
Urara.
What's up?
I need to talk to you.
What?
Sir.
I am sorry.
Stop doing that.
No.
When you're busy...
...I'm sorry for not
understanding your intention...
...or realizing why you proposed
to pay me until next September.
Sorry for saying I'd like to be
your assistant...
...if I fail the exam,
as I must have been helpful.
I am very sorry.
In addition...
...you already had an idea
for after the exam.
I cannot thank you enough.
Will you...
...decide based on the result
of mock exam of Kanto Law School?
If I fall short of the score...
...you can fire me.
Of course, I...
...need no retirement
allowance.
It is too good for me.
I see.
Really?
Do your best.
Thank you.
Urara made me awake.
Urara?
Didn't you know?
Urara came to my place
the day before yesterday.
He doesn't need an assistant.
He needs you, Sakurai,
as a lawyer and a partner.
Do respond dad's expectations.
Please.
(Pass the Exam)
Urara.
Urara. Wake up. Urara.
Oh.
- Wow, it's cold!
- Wake up.
- Wake up!
- It's cold.
I'm putting the sheets on washing.
It's cold!
- Wake up.
- Cold!
There you go.
It's so cold.
Hello. It's Daisuke.
Where are you?
None of your business.
- Morning.
Is there any update about Urara?
No clue.
Nothing.
Hello. Urara?
What are you doing?
Well...
You left the message.
What's up?
I mean, where are you?
It's not your business.
It is.
- Why?
- Your dad came here.
What? Did he go to Tamariba?
Urara. I'll be out for a while.
OK.
If my dad came again...
...tell him I am sorry
to have bothered him.
Say it yourself.
- Why?
- I won't help you.
Daisuke. Was it OK to hang up?
(Dad)
(Calling Dad)
(Missed call from Urara)
This is the voice message service.
After the beep,
please leave your message.
Hello.
Call me again.
OK?
- Hello.
I bought some taiyaki.
Please have some.
Thank you.
Then, thank you very much.
What's up?
I was around for shopping.
Sorry to bother you.
See you.
Welcome.
You're welcome to my flat
at night too.
- What is that?
- You know.
Urara is not here.
You're not nice.
I'm joking.
By the way, I came
to know why Urara left the house.
I see.
Urara never can replace Sakurai.
And I don't want her to.
She does know that.
But Urara wants you to feel
you need her.
Sir.
Do you need her?
You were enjoying being single.
Whether I need her
doesn't matter. I'm her father.
I see what you mean...
...but Urara wasn't
comfortable about it.
Do you know where she is?
I think it's Kotohira.
Why don't you go and see her?
I have a trial and a meeting today.
How about tomorrow?
Tomorrow, I have a medical check-up.
In which hospital?
Municipal Central Hospital.
You could cancel it.
Ms Shimizu will be cross.
Hey, do you want
to go and see her...
...or not?
Hey.
Why women are so dramatic?
Urara was behind when you said
you will go back to Aomori.
That's not an answer.
If she wants to come back...
...she can.
If not...
When her mother was here
she was...
...told to come back
to Kotohira at the end of the year.
It happened a bit earlier.
Between you and Urara...
...there is a gap of 15 years.
I think Urara...
...of all ages between
4 and 19 year old...
...are trying to fill the gap
all together.
That's how she is dealing with you.
But you feel it too much.
Letting her go back
to Kotohira means that...
...you make her leave her dad.
Like the archery...
...if you don't keep
her close to you...
...she can't make a move.
Really? Are you sure, mum?
I'm planning to cancel...
...getting married
to Mr Sasaki.
You love each other.
We do.
Why is that?
We can't have an argument.
Isn't it because...
...you're in good terms?
We're too old to get married
just because we love each other.
But somehow...
...I feel I'm too cool about it.
Although I'll give another thought.
Please do.
But Urara...
What?
I thought...
...you'd ask about Mr Sasaki
when you were back.
But you didn't.
You're thinking about Tokyo.
Stop talking about dad.
But...
Urara.
Go back to Tokyo.
You need your dad, don't you?
But...
...it's sad to be with someone
when you're not needed.
Doesn't dad really
need Urara at all?
Because...
(Voice message from Dad)
(Dad)
Urara.
Where are the bags
for flammable rubbish?
Urara. I'd like to clean
the bath tub. Where's the cleaner?
Urara. The automatic vacuum
cleaner disappeared.
Urara.
Have you not caught a cold?
Hello?
Is this Hanako?
I know it is.
Yes.
You sound happy.
Oh, really?
Well, I'm sorry.
I want you to tell
something to dad.
The bags for flammable
are on the...
Stop it.
I'm not your messenger.
Sorry. But...
Say it yourself to your dad.
Come back to Tokyo.
Are you hoping...
...he may come to see you?
What?
He wants to, if he can.
But he'll be at a trial today and...
...tomorrow at the hospital.
Hospital?
Is he ill or something?
No, it's just a...
Hanako?
He said it was just an ulcer.
It could be...
I'm stuffed.
I'm home.
Good evening.
What's up?
I know where Urara is.
Is it Kotohira?
- Did she get in touch?
- No.
How did you know
it's Kotohira?
I spoke to her on phone...
...and I heard
her mum's voice behind.
I see.
Take a seat.
Thank you.
I feel obliged to you both.
Urara and...
...you, father.
Father?
Oh, well, no.
Takuya Suzuki. No.
Mr Suzuki, sir.
No need
to call me "sir".
Sorry.
So I thought I'd go to Kotohira
to bring her back.
I bought a ticket too.
A ticket?
To Kotohira.
Do you...
Yes.
I love Urara.
But...
...the person Urara
is waiting for...
...isn't me.
It's you, father.
Don't call me father.
OK, we're not
talking about it.
So, father!
Please go and...
...see Urara.
Please.
Take this ticket.
Hey.
Sorry, I'll be back.
You'll be back?
Oh, sorry.
Thanks.
- Excuse me.
- Yes?
To Haneda Airport.
- The domestic flight.
- Certainly.
Oh, it might be Tokyo Station.
Just a second.
Why an express coach?
I'd better hurry.
Ah!
Ouch.
Urgh.
It was so far.
(Municipal Central Hospital)
Takuya Suzuki.
Please check again.
I have checked many times.
He is not in this hospital.
No way. He could have a cancer.
Well, I'm afraid I can't help.
All right.
I will look for him myself.
Don't run in the hospital.
Sorry.
- Good morning.
Urara?
Mr Sakurai.
You here to visit my dad...
...well, no.
Medical check-up.
Thank you for everything
about the Bar Exam.
Not at all.
I apologized to him yesterday.
I asked him to decide
based on the result...
...of the mock exam
in two weeks.
He kindly said yes.
That's great.
What do you mean I'm here
to visit him?
Don't you know?
He is admitted to the hospital.
For a cancer.
I think you misunderstood.
He was scheduled
to have a medical check-up with me.
He canceled it last night.
He doesn't have a cancer.
No.
Why did he cancel?
I don't know why.
Where is he at all?
I don't know.
Hello.
Are you here?
Thief!
- Thief! Thief! Thief!
- Stop. Stop.
Stop!
Not a thief, it's me.
Where's Urara?
In Tokyo.
She got on the bus,
so she should have arrived by now.
What?
It will be cold all day today.
Wrap up warm when going out.
That was Hanako's
Weather News.
Cut. OK.
Thank you so much.
Hanako, Hanako!
You're here, which probably means
you know that I lied.
Exactly.
Isn't that mean?
Sorry.
Didn't you manage
to make up with him?
I haven't seen him.
Didn't you go
to the hospital?
I did.
He canceled the medical check-up.
Why is that?
Hanako.
Don't you know where he is?
Oh no. If you have plotted...
...do it properly!
You passed each other.
You both felt in the same way...
...so you passed each other.
Thank you so much.
Sorry that I brought nothing.
Take a seat.
You came here only twice...
...asking for permission
to get married...
...and attending
my mother's funeral.
That's true.
When I came back with Urara...
...you didn't follow me.
A bit of grudge.
Did you come back if I followed?
No, I didn't, but...
I appreciate that...
...you didn't come.
What an irony.
I can't even imagine that...
...we three lived in that apartment.
We would have moved
to a bigger place if we were three.
I see.
Hey.
I never imagined to come here
for the third time.
We can restart our lives.
It's just one-off.
That's why we always regret.
Sorry.
I don't regret about our marriage.
What I regret is...
...that I told Urara a lie.
That I said to her you were dead.
If I didn't tell a lie...
...she wouldn't go to Tokyo...
...at the age of 19 to see you.
She'd have seen you earlier...
...and disillusioned by you.
I guess so.
Why did you send her to Tokyo again?
She just left by herself.
Really?
Urara...
...wants you to need her.
How about you?
That's why I came.
Well, I'll go.
Hey.
You must be tired.
Let me give you a lift.
- By car?
- Yes.
I don't fancy that.
What? I've got
a model driver license.
You're a paper driver.
In a way.
Why don't we talk more?
(I will be back shortly)
OK.
I'm home.
Welcome home!
You look fine.
Mum called me.
Why did you use coach?
If you flew, we could
see each other yesterday.
I don't know.
Anyway.
Hey.
Did you buy these?
Yes.
I cooked Kotohira's
local dish, Oden.
It's delicious.
I ate before my flight.
Oh.
I cooked something else as well.
I'm asking whether you bought it.
Isn't it for professional use?
Wow.
Mixed sushi in Kagawa...
...has boiled red kidney beans.
I had it even before that.
Oh. But I made it,
so it must taste better.
Why is this here in my study?
- IT was the only space.
- Why, why...
Why is sushi in my study?
Hey, listen.
Takuya welcomes you too!
- Takuya?
- Yes.
I named it.
Call the name and it will come.
- That's not true.
- It is.
I'm so hungry.
Takuya.
It doesn't react.
It's not as smart
as that.
Let me get a beer.
Here you are. You must be tired.
Let's eat.
Thanks for food!
Thanks for food.
See? It's really delicious.
I take back...
...the message
of the day before.
"Don't put me in trouble."
Can I bother you?
Instead...
...don't make me worry.
OK?
OK.
Right.
But I will visit Kotohira
from time to time.
Why?
Didn't you hear from mum?
- About Mr Sasaki.
- No.
Maybe a maternity blue.
She said she may not get married.
It's not maternity.
Marriage blue.
That too.
That one only.
But I want...
...both of you to be happy...
- ...so I can leave her.
- Sure, sure.
We won't finish this food.
What should we do?
It's all OK.
What did you eat while I was away?
I ate out a variety of things.
I saw a bite mark
on my dried bonito.
Was it there?
Don't know.
You bit it.
- Me?
- Yes. You did.
No way.
(Municipal Central Hospital)
Why are we here?
No worries.
Since we are here.
Thank you for taking us.
Foreigners are welcome too.
It's helpful.
Thanks for the ticket.
Ah, that ticket.
I'm glad she came back.
What's wrong?
Well, because...
Takuya Suzuki,
Rei Saeki.
Please come in.
Sorry. My name
is pronounced as "Urara".
Sorry for my mistake.
You do correct people.
- What's wrong?
- I'm scared.
I'm scared. Oh no.
- It's OK.
- I'm scared.
Until X-ray is taken,
do not burp.
Sure.
Do not burp.
Nor fart.
- Stop joking.
- Sorry.
Roll onto your right.
Right?
Father, can you be quiet?
Oh, sorry.
Can you be quick?
Can you hold the breath?
Quick! Quick!
Please! Be quick.