Oh, no...
Um...
What is it?
What's going on, Urara?
Why is Mom visiting us?
I don't know.
She may be sleeping.
Oh...
Mom...
Huh?
Um...
I'll hide.
Hey.
W... Wait.
I can't pretend.
Just try.
What are you doing?
What took you so long?
Sorry.
It's so heavy.
Here.
Bring them for me.
Hey, Mom...
She's here...
Go over there.
Go in this room.
Here you go.
I am so tired.
Why didn't you call me?
I wanted to go pick you up.
Do you have any problem if I come?
N... nothing, nothing.
I smell a rat.
Why?
You lie when you repeat phrases.
I'm not lying. Not lying.
Idiot.
Why did you bring a suitcase?
Are you going abroad?
I came to see you.
For how long?
I brought souvenirs for you.
Look.
I still haven't eaten all the food
you sent me.
This is for those who take care
of you in Tokyo.
I have to show my gratitude.
Do you want to meet them?
Yes, of course.
They love unnecessary things.
This is a stomach band for you.
I don't want it.
It's cold in Tokyo.
It will keep you warm.
No one wears a stomach band
in Tokyo.
You should wear it.
Look. I wear it, too.
That's lame.
This is a gorgeous apartment.
How many rooms do you have?
- What?
- It's messy.
Let's clean it up.
N... no.
Are you getting along well
with Sasaki?
I'm not young and
this is my second marriage.
So we are planning a small party
for Christmas.
Please come, Urara.
Ok.
Um... maybe something fell
because I put so much junk in there.
Let's take them all out.
No, it's dangerous.
No. Stop.
Hanako?
Did she leave something behind?
M... Mom.
What?
Hello, this is Penguin Express.
Great.
It's not her.
Why were you upset?
I wasn't
- Hello.
This is for Rei Saeki...
I'm Urara. Not Rei.
Actually, this is for Takuya Suzuki.
Huh?
It's for him.
No.
It says Room 1103.
Bring this back.
Sorry.
Excuse me, Rei Saeki.
What was it?
Wrong delivery.
Wrong?
I think it's for the next door.
What's this?
Why do you have a men's sock?
I don't know.
Maybe it's gotten here by mistake.
From a laundromat?
Right.
What's that, then?
What are those?
This is to avoid sexual perverts.
It's dangerous for girls
to live alone.
So I hang up men's clothes.
But this is 11th floor.
No one can see.
I heard there are perverts
with telescopes.
Liar.
Tokyo is a dangerous city.
There are even people who
want to buy used underwear.
Urara! I believe you are
not involved in such things.
Of course not.
Tell me the truth.
What?
You live with your boyfriend,
don't you?
She is pretty smart.
No, I don't.
But you called me and said
that you were with someone
who takes good care of you.
I was joking.
I won't be mad if you tell me
the truth.
You will be mad.
Are you doing something
to make me mad?
You can't talk back
because I am right.
No, you are not right. Not right.
Look at this sock.
It smells like someone's dad.
I am her dad.
Are you having an affair
with a married man?
No way.
Are you dating with compensation?
No!
Then what?
Ah, I am hungry.
You must be hungry, too.
Let's go out and eat.
You hiding something.
No, I'm not.
- Urara...
- What?
Urara...
What is it?
I remember...
I remember this smell.
Hey!
I know you are here. Show yourself.
Wait! Don't open it.
Long-time no see.
Um... Let me explain.
Urara. Let's get out of here.
You haven't seen him for 15 years.
Say hello.
Pack your stuff.
Dad.
Urara!
Don't talk to him.
You were lying to me.
I was trying to explain.
You said that you wouldn't try
to find him.
You are not trying to find Dad,
are you?
No. I'm not interested in him
at all.
I thought I would never
be able to find him.
How did you find him?
I was trying to explain.
It's a long story.
Explain in one minute.
I lost my wallet and was
taken to a mysterious shop.
Then I met Dad and he asked me
to sell my underwear.
You cut a story too short.
Actually, it was a joke that
he asked me to sell my underwear.
- No, it wasn't.
- No?
I mean...
Urara, I want you to explain.
He thought that I ran away
from home,
and tried to teach me that
Tokyo is a city full of danger.
That's right.
Then why do you live together?
You told me that my dad was dead,
but he is alive.
It was natural that I wanted
to live with him.
It wasn't natural.
You are related only by blood.
You don't know who he is.
What if he is a shady man?
He actually is a shady man.
Hey.
Dad got a decent job as a lawyer.
Decent, huh?
Even he didn't get a decent job,
even he was a swindler or
a murder, I'd want to live with him.
What are you talking about?
Because he is my dad.
Mom. You are happy to
get married with Sasaki.
Yes.
Dad is not happy.
But he lives in such a mansion.
He is single.
He must be womanizing a lot.
He has three girlfriends.
- Hey.
- He seems to have fun.
But he will break up with
all of them soon.
That's because of you.
So I have to be here with him.
He made us unhappy.
Why do you care about him?
Mom. Do you think we were unhappy?
- Let's just go home.
- No.
Yes!
No!
Hello.
Good morning.
Did you receive the document about
a claim on national compensation?
That was the Express Mail...
Huh?
Nothing. I'm going to
the office now.
I can't let you stay here.
Sorry, I have to go to the office.
Please pack up and leave
while I'm gone.
Yes, I will.
Dad, do you really mean it?
Listen to your mom.
Hey! Dad!
Hello. Is this Penguin Express?
I am Suzuki in Room 1103.
Can I ask for redelivery?
Dad!
Pack your stuff.
There is no place for me at home.
Sasaki said that he doesn't
mind living with you.
He's just saying that.
No.
I won't go back.
Let's do it now then
and get done with it.
- Do what?
- Make a visit.
To whom?
To those who take care of you
in Tokyo.
Those who take care of me?
I have to say hello to them.
Hmm...
Not them.
Huh?
Nothing.
Let's get out of here.
I feel like I'll choke
if I stay here any longer.
Oh, no...
FLAT OUT TOKYO GIRL
Episode 7
- Good morning.
Thank you for coming in
on a holiday.
It's ok.
What's wrong?
It's been a busy morning.
Sakurai.
Yes?
Do you meet your ex-wife often?
Not recently.
She is now in New York.
Was it awkward when you saw her?
Yes. I wish we could talk more.
Let's work.
Sure.
This place is familiar to me.
Why?
I used to live around here
before I got married.
I see... It's here.
Tamagawa?
It's Tamariba.
I see.
This way.
Hello.
This is my mom. She is Mika.
Hi.
I heard from Urara that
she comes here very often.
Thank you for taking care of her.
This is udon from my hometown.
Is it for us?
Thank you very much.
Dad, she is Urara's mom.
Hello.
Yes?
Dad, you are just like your son.
Huh?
Yes, it was a hereditary problem.
I am Shigesuke Tamagawa and
I am a restaurant manager.
Hi, I am Henry. I am Canadian.
Hi, I am Joanna from France.
Hello.
Udbal? What's wrong?
Hey!
Aren't you Yukari Yamamoto?
No, I'm not.
She is Udbal from Mongolia.
No. You must be Yukari.
Wait.
No, I'm not.
Sorry, Yukari.
See? She is Yukari.
Are you ok, Yukari?
Huh?
What's going on?
Hey, how are you?
This is Aki. She is Urara.
Hi.
- She is so cute.
- I know.
She is so cute.
I'm going out.
Ok. See you.
Excuse me.
See you later.
I like the interior.
Urara. Did you talk to my brother?
Yes. He said he is going
to get married.
She is pregnant.
Are you going to marry her?
Yes, of course.
I was surprised to hear
that she got pregnant.
Pregnant?
Did you hear that, Dad?
She said Aki is pregnant.
Daisuke hasn't told them yet.
Well... I think he would tell us
sooner or later.
Oh no...
Thank you.
(Audition)
The key is vaccination for virus
that hasn't been found in Japan.
Right.
(Hanako Serizawa)
In foreign countries...
Hang on a second.
Hi, how are you?
I've just got the audition.
How was it?
I did well.
That's great.
Will you treat me to dinner?
Sure. I would love to.
I've got a nice wine.
Can we eat at your home tonight?
Wine... That will be nice.
Dinner at my apartment?
Any problem?
Urara is home.
Let's go out to a restaurant.
I can't fix the time yet.
I don't mind eating with Urara.
Well... Urara is going out tonight.
We can have fun, then.
Hum... I don't know what time
I can go home yet.
Something's fishy.
Oh, no... she is coming.
Huh?
I am at my office now.
Do you want to say hi to Sakurai?
Huh?
All right. Maybe another time.
I'll call you.
Is everything ok?
Yep.
The problem with live vaccine is...
Excuse me. Do you have a second?
No.
Just one second.
Excuse me.
- Can we talk for a second?
- No.
- Just for a second.
- No, thanks.
Are you interested in
a part-time job?
(Shibuya station)
Hi, Rei.
Hi.
Can you work at the bar tonight?
I thought it's a holiday today.
No. Our staff are taking today off.
We are open tonight.
I need your help. Please.
My mom is visiting me.
Can you fix your schedule for me?
Part-time job?
Please.
- But...
- You should go.
Part-time job is a job.
You should be responsible.
See you tonight. Thanks.
Wait! Wait...
What kind of job is it?
Huh? Um... What should I say?
It's a diner.
Let's go then.
Can I have my check please?
- It's on me today.
- Thank you.
I have to say hello.
No, you don't have to.
Is the food good?
No, it's awful.
Go home and eat with Dad.
Why do I have to eat with that man?
Wait. I will go by myself.
Something's fishy.
No, it's nothing.
Hi, can we talk for a second?
No.
Do you know the bar "Chaconne"?
Maybe not.
I think we can win this case.
Thank you for your preparation.
It's my pleasure.
I will treat you to dinner.
Um...
Hitomi?
Yes. I have to go. Excuse me.
What should I do?
Urara, you should be more careful.
(Club Chaconne)
May I help you?
This is not a diner, is it?
Obviously, it's not a diner.
Are you sure?
Yes.
Hi, she is Sayuri, a newcomer.
Hi, I am Sayuri.
Sayuri?
Excuse me.
M... Mom?
This is not a diner.
Why are you working here?
It's a trial today.
Nice to meet you.
I wish you will have fun.
Hey.
Yes?
She looks pretty old.
She said she wanted to work
here no matter what.
It's ok if she does well...
Cheers.
Don't you have any children?
Huh?
Why don't you spend time
with your children
instead of coming to
a bar like this?
What?
I'm sorry. Mom!
Don't you think so?
Mom.
Is that how you call her?
She calls me Mom since
she was very little.
Very little?
Did you hear what I just said?
Mom.
Don't spend too much money
in here.
Save it and take your children
out for a dinner.
Huh?
What do you think?
Hello.
Let me take your jacket.
Are you single?
Oh...
I'm so sorry.
You are so careless.
I'm sorry.
Clean up table 7.
Ok.
Hello.
Hey, you are... Dai...
- Daisuke.
- Right.
Do you work part-time here?
Yes.
I see.
I'm so sorry.
It's ok.
What are you doing? I am so sorry.
Excuse me.
Why did he come here today?
That's nasty.
Sayuri.
Please.
Ok. Excuse me.
Where are you going?
Hey.
She is Sayuri, a newcomer.
Excuse me. I am Sayuri...
What?
What is it?
- Urara!
- What's going on?
What? What is it?
I want to go home.
What was that? Explain to me.
I have an assistant named Sakurai...
I sneaked in there to check on Dad,
and I ended up working part-time.
I don't get it.
I can't believe this.
How could you let your 19-year-old
daughter be a bar waitress
and visit her as a guest?
It's a decent job
and I know that bar well.
Don't worry.
You seemed to have fun
working there.
Because...
You should have told me that
Dad is alive.
She's right.
He dumped us.
You were only four years old.
I didn't dump you.
I wanted you to live with me.
But you went back to Kotohira
with Urara.
If I didn't go back, Urara and I
would have been ruined.
We were already at our limit.
You used the bar exam
as an excuse for not working.
I had no choice.
I had to pass the exam
to plan our future.
I worked instead.
Did you have an affair at that time?
No!
But Mom said that you were
always cheating on her.
That's when I was single.
I settled all the past
when I got married.
You can't settle anything yet now.
I swear I didn't cheat on her
after we got married.
I doubt it.
I didn't.
I don't care about it now.
Huh?
You know nothing about her
after we got divorced.
Nothing?
Nothing.
Do you know at what age
Urara could do pullover?
When did she get the mumps?
Which subject did she get
a perfect score for the first time?
At what age did she start
riding on a bicycle?
When did she have a fight against
a boy and chip her front tooth?
When did she become taller than
150 centimetres?
When did she make chocolate at
Valentine's day for the first time?
When did she put on lipstick
for the first time?
You know nothing.
We've gotten divorced 15 years ago
and I have been taking care
of Urara since then.
I have been thinking about
Urara all the times.
You know nothing about Urara.
How could you say
"It's a decent job"?
You don't care about Urara.
You just pretend to be
a nice father.
Mom.
What?
You know nothing about Dad
for 15 years.
He is working hard as a lawyer.
I'm sure he is making a lot of
money to go to a bar like that.
He is taking over the cases
that cannot make any profit
such as the injury case of Professor
at Joto who was falsely accused,
or a malpractice suit of
Kanto Medical Centre.
You know pretty well.
I am checking on you, Dad.
I don't know about the bar exam,
but he has been studying harder
since he became a lawyer.
Maybe he has been working
harder than you, Mom.
No way! I have been taking
care of you.
You are right.
I am sorry for not helping you
take care of Urara for 15 years.
What is it?
Urara became such a good girl
because you took great care of her.
Hello. How are you?
Is that tomorrow?
It's ok.
I am looking forward to
seeing you at 6PM.
Let's pack and go home, Urara.
I have a customer tomorrow.
You can't go home now.
It's too late for the last flight,
shinkansen or express bus.
I don't want to stay here.
Then find a hotel, Mom.
I am not going.
Sayuri...
Don't call me Sayuri.
Let Urara do what she wants.
I heard you will be getting
remarried.
So what?
Urara.
You can stay here.
Excuse me?
I will be responsible for her.
Can you?
Yes, I can.
Is that fine?
I don't care.
Are you messing with me?
I am sorry.
Shape up or get out.
This is your last chance.
Yes.
See you tomorrow.
Is Daisuke not home yet?
It's him.
Where did you go?
Part-time job.
I don't need to do it anymore.
Where is Aki?
She is not coming home.
She may go back to Shikoku.
But I heard she is pregnant...
Dad, what's wrong with him?
Let's wait until he explains.
Do you know at what age
Urara could do pullover?
When did she make chocolate on
Valentine's day for the first time?
When did she put on lipstick
for the first time?
You know nothing about her.
Ok.
Wake up, everyone.
Wake up!
Breakfast is ready.
Hmm...
Oops.
What's going on?
Again?
Breakfast will be ready soon.
Come to the table, please.
When will you come back to Kotohira?
When I make Dad happy.
It's not clear. Promise me to
come back by the end of this year.
By the end of this year?
No.
I will stay here then.
You have an appointment today.
Dad. Mom.
I think this is the first and
the last time
we have breakfast together.
So let's sit here together
and enjoy.
All right.
Sit here.
Mom, you sit here.
Let's eat.
Thank you.
Isn't it delicious?
By the way, Mom and Dad...
Do you regret that
you had gotten married?
It's cold there. Take care.
All right.
Say hello to Sasaki.
Ok.
I can go by myself from here.
Ok. Take care.
Come home by the end of this year.
I will, I will.
- You said it twice.
- Oops.
Dad likes Kamaage better
than normal udon.
Huh?
Don't cook it too long.
All right.
See you.
I never regret that
I've gotten married to him.
Because I had you, Urara.
Um... Aki?
Are you all right?
Hello.
(Daisuke Tamagawa)
Here you go. Enjoy.
Are you stressed out?
Huh?
You seemed to be fired up.
Maybe.
Hi.
Huh? You are... Um...
- Daisuke.
- Right. Daisuke.
I'm sorry about the mess last night.
Don't worry. Are you a member here?
Yes. I dropped by because
I work around here.
Work?
I work part-time at
a construction site during the day.
You work during the day also.
I don't need to anymore.
I just can't quit yet.
You work because your girlfriend
got pregnant, right?
Did you hear it from Urara?
I am her father. Sorry about that.
No.
I thought you liked Urara.
I thought so, too.
But you have no choice once
she got pregnant.
Actually...
You were not pregnant?
Did you think you were pregnant?
Then...
Did she lie to you? Why?
I don't know.
Did she want to marry you?
She said sorry yesterday
and disappeared.
She doesn't pick up my call.
She seems not to come home yet.
I came to Tokyo to become
a dog groomer.
Actually, I just wanted to
come to Tokyo.
A dog groomer was just an excuse.
I can understand.
Then I met Daisuke and
we started dating.
But I had to go back to Shikoku
due to my family situation.
I thought he would ask me to stay.
If I asked her to stay, it would
have meant that I would marry her.
Hmm... I guess you are right.
I couldn't make up my mind
so I didn't ask her to stay.
And she went back home.
I lived in Tokyo
only for a short while.
I was trying to forget everything
by thinking that it was a dream.
Then Daisuke came to visit you.
It didn't work out.
She didn't even listen to me.
I was trying to forget about him.
I met Daisuke on the bus
when he came back to Tokyo.
I see.
He was crying at that time.
Then she called me all of a sudden
and told me that she got pregnant.
So you went to see her right away.
Yes.
I don't know what I'm doing.
Why did you lie to him that
you were pregnant?
Because I was lonely.
I know it can't be an excuse.
But it's true.
So I made up my mind that
I would marry her and
become a father.
When I knew that
Daisuke made up his mind,
I found that I did something
that I shouldn't have done.
I came to Tokyo to apologize to him.
But I couldn't tell him the truth.
She told me the truth yesterday.
What will you do, then?
Just like you, my girlfriend told me
that she was pregnant.
It was Urara's mother.
Is that why you got married?
I married her when we found
that she wasn't pregnant.
Huh?
I married her because
she was not pregnant.
She didn't mean to lie. She believed
that she was pregnant by mistake.
Men have to be ready to be a father.
My situation at that time had
never allowed me to marry her.
However, I wanted to
be with her no matter what.
She is clumsy, but I wanted
to be responsible for her life.
I was surprised at how I felt.
Many things had happened
after we've gotten married
and eventually we divorced.
To be responsible for her life...
Yeah.
Thank you.
Wait a second.
I don't know where she has been
since last night. I must find her.
Think well.
Do you really love her?
Don't propose to her just
because you feel responsible
that you made her lie to you.
(Rei Saeki)
Hi, Daisuke.
Call me when you hear this message.
I am with Aki now.
Aki.
I thought you went home.
I wanted to say sorry again.
But...
It's for you.
I saved this money to be a father.
I can't take it.
Buy a shinkansen ticket.
You paid for a round-trip ticket,
too.
I want you to take it so that
I can give up.
You lied that you were pregnant but
you didn't want to marry me, right?
I'm sorry.
Take care.
You, too.
Hey, I didn't know you were here.
I called you to let you know
where she was.
You are right.
What did you do just now?
What?
Did you propose to her?
I was dumped.
Huh?
Cheer up.
Oh, no...
It's ok.
Let's go eat something.
Will you treat me?
Ok... well, no.
I'm home.
Huh? H... Hey!
What are you doing?
Hi.
You made a mess again.
You should have told me.
What?
I heard that you like Kamaage.
What's this? Did you buy this?
I can buy anything in Tokyo.
How much was it?
Answer me.
It will be ready soon.
Clean up the table.
Why don't you clean up and cook?
Kamaage has a firm texture
because it's not put in water.
This bucket is too huge.
Udon has to be cooked
with plenty of water to add texture.
But...
Let's eat.
Ok.
It looks delicious.
How is it?
Didn't you like it?
This can't be bad.
That's good.
Daisuke said that he met you.
Yeah.
Did you tell him to go to
Shinagawa station?
No. We just talked.
About what?
It's a secret.
- Tell me.
- No.
You are mean.
By the way, I want you to hurry.
What?
Remarriage.
Again?
Mom said she wanted me to
go home by the end of this year.
You won't go home anyway.
I want you to remarry.
I don't regret that
I've gotten married.
Great.
I thought she was the best match
but we didn't go well.
It doesn't have to be
the best match to marry.
Hanako, Okuno or Haruka...
You are saying the same thing.
You say the same thing.
- It's you, Urara.
- It's you, Dad.
Urara.
Dad.
U...
- Urara.
- Dad.