[Script Info]
; // 此字幕由PopSub生成  2011-10-11 21:30:30
; // MESSAGE ERROR 0.75
; // popgo_fansub@yahoo.co.jp
; // 欢迎访问漫游天下 http://bbs.popgo.net
Title:漫游字幕
Original Script:漫游字幕组
Synch Point:0
ScriptType:v4.00+
Collisions:Normal
PlayResX:640
PlayResY:480
Timer:100.0000

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,方正卡通简体,31,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H01750075,&HF0000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,1,0,2,30,30,10,134
Style: 日本語,MS Gothic,20,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&HF0000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,1,0,2,30,30,10,134
Style: staff,方正卡通简体,20,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&HF0000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,0,8,30,30,10,134

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Name, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:02:01.00,0:02:06.00,staff,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(1000,1000)}本字幕由天空树双语字幕组出品
Dialogue: 0,0:02:07.00,0:02:12.00,staff,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(1000,1000)}片源：小宁  中翻：小四 可乐  日翻：小四 可乐
Dialogue: 0,0:02:13.00,0:02:18.00,staff,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(1000,1000)}校对：小四 可乐   时间轴：可乐  压制：

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Actor, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:01:07.65,0:01:08.84,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,出航
Dialogue: 0,0:01:11.18,0:01:12.42,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,あいつら　何する気だ
Dialogue: 0,0:01:15.28,0:01:16.45,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,よーし　行くよ
Dialogue: 0,0:01:16.74,0:01:17.28,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,オット
Dialogue: 0,0:01:18.47,0:01:20.51,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,行けー
Dialogue: 0,0:01:22.24,0:01:23.44,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,オレにつかまって
Dialogue: 0,0:01:34.38,0:01:35.98,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大丈夫　おじさん
Dialogue: 0,0:01:36.32,0:01:39.22,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,おじさんじゃねぇー　レオリオさんだ
Dialogue: 0,0:01:43.64,0:01:47.88,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,どうやら今年もドーレに着くまで退屈しねぇで済みそうだぞ
Dialogue: 0,0:01:53.37,0:01:55.13,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,サヨナラ　クジラ島
Dialogue: 0,0:01:55.36,0:01:59.46,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,プライド　荒海　決闘
Dialogue: 0,0:02:28.51,0:02:30.73,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一万　一万一
Dialogue: 0,0:03:00.59,0:03:02.59,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,こんなベタ凪で船酔った
Dialogue: 0,0:03:02.84,0:03:04.49,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,でけぇ図体して情けねー
Dialogue: 0,0:03:04.85,0:03:07.97,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,毎度の事よ　ドーレ島に着くまでにや
Dialogue: 0,0:03:08.12,0:03:11.54,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吐くも荒くなって骨と歯だけになってるだろうぜ
Dialogue: 0,0:03:18.46,0:03:20.66,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今回は何人が待つかな
Dialogue: 0,0:03:25.52,0:03:28.38,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,見当たしたところ　骨のありそうなのは
Dialogue: 0,0:03:35.68,0:03:37.52,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,兄さん　取れるかな
Dialogue: 0,0:03:41.70,0:03:42.27,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,このヤロォー
Dialogue: 0,0:03:54.29,0:03:55.67,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,っつこいのに金塊がおまえだ
Dialogue: 0,0:03:55.83,0:03:57.20,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,よーし　勝利は１０枚だ
Dialogue: 0,0:04:06.72,0:04:09.27,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ヤロォー
Dialogue: 0,0:04:14.75,0:04:16.99,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,おお　なかなか
Dialogue: 0,0:04:17.59,0:04:19.26,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,そのぐらいにしておけ　カッツォ
Dialogue: 0,0:04:28.55,0:04:32.52,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,降りな　降りるんだ　この船から
Dialogue: 0,0:04:33.71,0:04:34.58,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,なんだと
Dialogue: 0,0:04:39.37,0:04:41.01,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,何を　放せ　おえ
Dialogue: 0,0:04:42.79,0:04:43.22,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,やれ
Dialogue: 0,0:04:43.70,0:04:44.47,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,セーノ
Dialogue: 0,0:04:52.52,0:04:53.84,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,この船に乗った以上
Dialogue: 0,0:04:54.46,0:04:56.91,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,全員がオレのやり方に従ってもらう
Dialogue: 0,0:04:57.58,0:05:01.74,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,気に入らねぇ奴は片っ端から放り出すから　そう思え
Dialogue: 0,0:05:02.63,0:05:04.92,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ふん　こちとら客だぜ
Dialogue: 0,0:05:07.61,0:05:08.47,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来た　来た
Dialogue: 0,0:05:26.96,0:05:28.27,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,そーれ
Dialogue: 0,0:05:35.67,0:05:38.10,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,坊主　大物釣り上がったな
Dialogue: 0,0:05:38.83,0:05:42.84,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,しかも　飛び骨は滅多にはお目にかかれない代物だ
Dialogue: 0,0:05:43.61,0:05:46.45,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,うん　クジラ島でもめったに見ないよ
Dialogue: 0,0:05:51.59,0:05:54.11,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,風が止んじまって　双翼でも吹きやしね
Dialogue: 0,0:05:54.72,0:05:57.86,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,この調子じゃいつドーレ島に着くんだろうね
Dialogue: 0,0:06:22.85,0:06:25.60,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来るよ　嵐がくる
Dialogue: 0,0:06:26.60,0:06:29.78,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,よーせー　波一つ立てねぇーぜ
Dialogue: 0,0:06:31.94,0:06:36.31,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,風が湿って来た　それに潮気が多い
Dialogue: 0,0:06:38.43,0:06:40.12,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ウミヅルも注意しあってるしね
Dialogue: 0,0:06:40.59,0:06:44.93,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ウミヅルだと　鳥の言葉がわかるってんのか
Dialogue: 0,0:06:45.69,0:06:47.77,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,うん　全部じゃないけどね
Dialogue: 0,0:06:48.34,0:06:51.50,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,へへ　オレを担ぐつもりかよ
Dialogue: 0,0:06:56.20,0:07:00.18,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ボウズ　クジラ島から上船したんだったな
Dialogue: 0,0:07:03.41,0:07:05.32,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,親父は何をしている
Dialogue: 0,0:07:05.51,0:07:09.10,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ハンターだよ　写真でしか知らないんだけどね
Dialogue: 0,0:07:10.87,0:07:11.91,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,尊敬してる
Dialogue: 0,0:07:12.88,0:07:16.81,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,そうか　おまえの親父もハンターか
Dialogue: 0,0:07:37.10,0:07:37.95,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ボウズ
Dialogue: 0,0:07:38.61,0:07:39.33,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,なんだい
Dialogue: 0,0:07:40.46,0:07:42.66,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嵐の規模とその刻限は
Dialogue: 0,0:07:43.37,0:07:45.73,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ウミヅルはかなり強いって言ってる
Dialogue: 0,0:07:46.31,0:07:50.12,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,この船和したと　後二時間
Dialogue: 0,0:07:51.75,0:07:53.68,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,この稼業も長い事やってきたが
Dialogue: 0,0:07:54.38,0:07:57.12,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,これ言いやってたのはボウズで二人目だぜ
Dialogue: 0,0:07:58.38,0:07:59.26,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,二人目
Dialogue: 0,0:08:00.16,0:08:03.24,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ヤロー共　帆下ろせ
Dialogue: 0,0:08:42.64,0:08:43.42,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,気を付けやがれー
Dialogue: 0,0:08:43.98,0:08:47.08,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,いいや悪い　ちりと手が滑ちかったな
Dialogue: 0,0:08:48.33,0:08:49.10,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,よく言うぜ
Dialogue: 0,0:08:49.69,0:08:53.06,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,こんなもんでオレを試そうなんだ　10年早いんだよ
Dialogue: 0,0:08:54.84,0:08:57.85,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今年やちった歯応えがありそうだな
Dialogue: 0,0:09:20.80,0:09:21.61,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,何や
Dialogue: 0,0:09:23.78,0:09:25.37,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,セント.エルモの火だ
Dialogue: 0,0:09:26.01,0:09:27.35,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,セント.エルモの火
Dialogue: 0,0:09:27.88,0:09:31.00,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,雷雲または帯電した雲が頭上に来ると
Dialogue: 0,0:09:31.41,0:09:34.64,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,マストの天辺など高所に集中した静電気が
Dialogue: 0,0:09:34.95,0:09:37.14,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,非常に強くなって起こる発光現象だ
Dialogue: 0,0:09:40.99,0:09:42.61,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,やっと口を聞いたと思えば
Dialogue: 0,0:09:43.24,0:09:46.39,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,百科事典に載ってるような解説　ありがとうよ
Dialogue: 0,0:09:47.69,0:09:49.64,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,船乗りの間じゃ
Dialogue: 0,0:09:49.92,0:09:51.44,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,セント.エルモの火を見た者は
Dialogue: 0,0:09:51.68,0:09:53.85,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,生きちゃ帰れれぇって言い伝えな
Dialogue: 0,0:09:56.19,0:09:57.51,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,おもしれぇじゃねぇか
Dialogue: 0,0:09:58.05,0:09:59.97,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,くるぞ　でっかい嵐が
Dialogue: 0,0:10:07.01,0:10:12.41,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今年は　ハンターとして震えるほどの素質を持って奴と出会えそうだぜ
Dialogue: 0,0:10:31.55,0:10:32.42,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,なんだよこれ
Dialogue: 0,0:10:57.17,0:11:05.39,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,風よー　うんと吹けよー　嵐の海にやよー
Dialogue: 0,0:11:05.81,0:11:08.10,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,船長　船底から浸水です
Dialogue: 0,0:11:08.37,0:11:13.44,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,けっ　その辺でダウンしてる役立たず共のケツでもつめとけ
Dialogue: 0,0:11:14.44,0:11:15.57,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,はいはい　サー
Dialogue: 0,0:11:17.14,0:11:18.68,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,取り舵一杯
Dialogue: 0,0:11:21.89,0:11:22.97,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,飛ぶぞー
Dialogue: 0,0:11:49.02,0:11:50.25,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,情けねぇ
Dialogue: 0,0:11:50.69,0:11:52.99,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,こんなんでハンター試験を受けようってんだから
Dialogue: 0,0:11:53.14,0:11:54.54,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,笑わせるぜ
Dialogue: 0,0:11:55.04,0:11:55.91,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,はい　水だよ
Dialogue: 0,0:11:56.93,0:11:59.91,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,この草も噛みなよ　楽になるよ
Dialogue: 0,0:12:09.95,0:12:12.42,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,結局　この３人だけのだようだな
Dialogue: 0,0:12:15.59,0:12:22.24,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沖野のクジラがー　おいらーを追うさー
Dialogue: 0,0:12:23.01,0:12:24.58,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,名前が聞きてぇだと
Dialogue: 0,0:12:25.14,0:12:25.87,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,そうだ
Dialogue: 0,0:12:26.79,0:12:27.75,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,オレ　ゴン
Dialogue: 0,0:12:30.77,0:12:31.63,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,クラピカという
Dialogue: 0,0:12:34.65,0:12:35.97,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,オレはレオリオだ
Dialogue: 0,0:12:36.55,0:12:39.13,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ゴン　クラピカ　レオリオか
Dialogue: 0,0:12:40.28,0:12:43.84,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,で　おまえ達　なぜハンターになりたいんだ
Dialogue: 0,0:12:44.42,0:12:46.74,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,おい　偉そうに聞くもんじゃねぇぜ
Dialogue: 0,0:12:47.14,0:12:48.91,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,面接官でもあるまいし
Dialogue: 0,0:12:49.31,0:12:50.59,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,いいから　答えろ
Dialogue: 0,0:12:50.79,0:12:51.79,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,なんだと
Dialogue: 0,0:12:51.94,0:12:54.34,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,オレ　父さんがやってた仕事だから
Dialogue: 0,0:12:54.92,0:12:57.04,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,だから　どんな物かやってみたくて
Dialogue: 0,0:12:57.42,0:12:59.27,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,おい　勝手に答えるんじゃねぇ
Dialogue: 0,0:12:59.84,0:13:02.40,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,オレが今この爺さんと話してるんだぜ
Dialogue: 0,0:13:02.63,0:13:04.38,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,いいじゃん　理由を話すぐらい
Dialogue: 0,0:13:04.57,0:13:07.99,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,オレは嫌んだ　オレは絶対に教えねぇ
Dialogue: 0,0:13:08.91,0:13:12.72,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,オレはな　嫌な事は決闘してでもやらねぇ主義なんだ
Dialogue: 0,0:13:13.35,0:13:15.13,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,わたしも同感だな　レオリオ
Dialogue: 0,0:13:17.15,0:13:19.80,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,おい　テメ年いくつだ
Dialogue: 0,0:13:20.44,0:13:23.01,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,馴れ馴れしく呼び捨てにするんじゃねぇ
Dialogue: 0,0:13:23.39,0:13:27.92,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最もらしい嘘をついて　嫌な質問を回避するのは容易い
Dialogue: 0,0:13:29.59,0:13:32.10,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,しかし　偽証は強欲と等しく
Dialogue: 0,0:13:32.30,0:13:34.93,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最も恥ずべき行為だとわたしは考える
Dialogue: 0,0:13:36.54,0:13:38.68,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,レオリオさんと訂正しろ
Dialogue: 0,0:13:39.31,0:13:43.90,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,かといって　初対面の人間の前で正直に告白するには
Dialogue: 0,0:13:44.62,0:13:48.38,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,わたしの志望理由は私の内面に深く関わりすぎている
Dialogue: 0,0:13:49.41,0:13:53.35,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,したがって　この場で質問に答える事はできない
Dialogue: 0,0:13:54.03,0:13:57.52,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,レオリオさんだ　レオリオさん
Dialogue: 0,0:14:03.34,0:14:06.97,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,答えん奴は今すぐこの船から降りな
Dialogue: 0,0:14:08.47,0:14:09.86,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,まだわからねぇのか
Dialogue: 0,0:14:10.52,0:14:12.62,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ハンター試験はもう始まってるんだよ
Dialogue: 0,0:14:13.43,0:14:15.60,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,この船に乗った瞬間からな
Dialogue: 0,0:14:20.74,0:14:22.75,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,そいつは　ハンター協会の
Dialogue: 0,0:14:26.47,0:14:27.41,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,知っての通り
Dialogue: 0,0:14:27.88,0:14:31.14,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ハンター資格をとりたい奴は星の数ほどいる
Dialogue: 0,0:14:31.75,0:14:34.50,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,だが　そいつの全員を審査できるほど
Dialogue: 0,0:14:34.71,0:14:36.38,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,試験官の余裕はねぇ
Dialogue: 0,0:14:37.20,0:14:39.35,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,そこで　オレ達みてぇのを雇われて
Dialogue: 0,0:14:39.67,0:14:41.40,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,志望者を篩にかけるのさ
Dialogue: 0,0:14:42.56,0:14:45.40,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,船を降ろされた奴らとここでへばってる奴は
Dialogue: 0,0:14:45.75,0:14:48.36,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,脱落者として　審査委員会に報告する
Dialogue: 0,0:14:49.93,0:14:53.23,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,審査会場へ行っても門前払いってわけだ
Dialogue: 0,0:14:54.87,0:14:59.61,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,お前らが本試験を受けれるかどうかはオレの判断次第って事さ
Dialogue: 0,0:15:00.26,0:15:03.48,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,細心の注意を払って　オレの質問に答えな
Dialogue: 0,0:15:04.01,0:15:06.95,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ち　しようがねぇ　答えるとするか
Dialogue: 0,0:15:08.08,0:15:10.15,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,オレがハンターになりてぇのはだな
Dialogue: 0,0:15:10.60,0:15:12.38,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,わたしはクルタ族の生き残りだ
Dialogue: 0,0:15:12.62,0:15:14.71,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,おい　オレが話そうとしてんだろう
Dialogue: 0,0:15:15.34,0:15:17.07,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,わたしの志望するハンターは
Dialogue: 0,0:15:17.36,0:15:21.33,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,賞金首になった罪人を捉える　ブラックリスト.ハントだ
Dialogue: 0,0:15:21.83,0:15:22.93,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,そのわけは
Dialogue: 0,0:15:23.47,0:15:26.71,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,４年前　わたしの同胞が皆殺しにされた
Dialogue: 0,0:15:27.04,0:15:30.07,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,犯人は殺人集団　幻影旅団
Dialogue: 0,0:15:30.65,0:15:32.96,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,わたしは奴らを捉えるそのために
Dialogue: 0,0:15:33.82,0:15:35.94,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ハンターになろうというのか
Dialogue: 0,0:15:38.33,0:15:41.59,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,幻影旅団といえば　一人残らずA級首だぞ
Dialogue: 0,0:15:42.20,0:15:44.66,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,熟練のハンターでもうかつに手を出せねぇ
Dialogue: 0,0:15:45.32,0:15:47.12,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,無駄死にするん事になるぜ
Dialogue: 0,0:15:48.17,0:15:49.52,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,死は全く怖くない
Dialogue: 0,0:15:50.30,0:15:51.58,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一番怖いのは
Dialogue: 0,0:15:52.11,0:15:55.07,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,この怒りがやがて風化してしまわないかという事だ
Dialogue: 0,0:15:57.72,0:15:59.67,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大層な御託を並べやがって
Dialogue: 0,0:16:00.36,0:16:03.98,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,仇討ちならわざわざハンターにならなくたって出来るじゃねーか
Dialogue: 0,0:16:04.79,0:16:07.49,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,この世で最も愚かな質問の一つだな
Dialogue: 0,0:16:08.35,0:16:11.34,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ハンターでなければ入れない場所　聞けない情報
Dialogue: 0,0:16:11.92,0:16:16.49,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,出来ない行動というものが山ほどあるのだよ　レオリオ
Dialogue: 0,0:16:16.79,0:16:18.70,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,レオリオさんだつってんだろう
Dialogue: 0,0:16:19.40,0:16:21.51,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,で　そのレオリオさんの動機は
Dialogue: 0,0:16:23.08,0:16:23.85,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,オレか
Dialogue: 0,0:16:24.48,0:16:28.63,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,オレはあんたの顔色をうかがって答えるなんて真っ平だから正直に言うぜ
Dialogue: 0,0:16:29.26,0:16:32.53,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,金さ　ハンターになって稼ぎまくるんだ
Dialogue: 0,0:16:32.96,0:16:35.08,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,金さえあれば何でも手に入る
Dialogue: 0,0:16:35.23,0:16:39.31,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,でかい家　いい車　うまい酒　女だって
Dialogue: 0,0:16:40.96,0:16:43.82,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,品性は金では買えないよ　レオリオ
Dialogue: 0,0:16:49.76,0:16:51.08,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,これで三度目だぜ
Dialogue: 0,0:16:53.10,0:16:54.10,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,表へ出な
Dialogue: 0,0:16:54.78,0:16:58.48,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,うす汚ねぇクルタ族ってやらは　礼儀を知らねぇらしい
Dialogue: 0,0:16:59.75,0:17:02.03,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,いまの言葉取り消せ　レオリオ
Dialogue: 0,0:17:02.46,0:17:03.81,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,レオリオさんだ
Dialogue: 0,0:17:07.28,0:17:08.21,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来な
Dialogue: 0,0:17:08.35,0:17:09.49,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,望むところ
Dialogue: 0,0:17:10.03,0:17:12.02,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,お　おい　ほら
Dialogue: 0,0:17:12.74,0:17:14.45,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,話はまだ終わってらんぞ
Dialogue: 0,0:17:14.79,0:17:15.64,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,おい　こら
Dialogue: 0,0:17:16.02,0:17:17.26,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,放っておこうよ
Dialogue: 0,0:17:18.59,0:17:20.10,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,その人を知りたければ
Dialogue: 0,0:17:20.25,0:17:23.46,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,その人が何に対して怒りを感じるかを知れ
Dialogue: 0,0:17:23.96,0:17:27.38,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ミトおばさんが教えてくれた　オレの好きな言葉なんだ
Dialogue: 0,0:17:29.63,0:17:32.41,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,オレには２人が怒ってる理由が
Dialogue: 0,0:17:32.60,0:17:34.92,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,とても大切な事に思えるんだ
Dialogue: 0,0:17:35.40,0:17:36.80,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,止めない方がいいよ
Dialogue: 0,0:17:41.49,0:17:43.85,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,何　メイン.マストに亀裂だと
Dialogue: 0,0:17:44.33,0:17:46.60,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,はい　速くホックはしやんねぇと
Dialogue: 0,0:17:50.73,0:17:53.79,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今すぐ訂正するなら許してやるぞ　レオリオ
Dialogue: 0,0:17:54.39,0:17:56.40,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,テメーの方が先だ　クラピカ
Dialogue: 0,0:17:57.21,0:17:58.70,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,オレから譲る気は全くねぇ
Dialogue: 0,0:18:08.08,0:18:08.86,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,行くぞ
Dialogue: 0,0:18:09.09,0:18:10.18,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,こりゃあ
Dialogue: 0,0:18:35.33,0:18:36.26,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,やるじゃねぇか
Dialogue: 0,0:18:37.01,0:18:38.18,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,あんたもな
Dialogue: 0,0:18:49.72,0:18:52.15,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,カッツォ　気をつけろよ
Dialogue: 0,0:19:16.81,0:19:17.90,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,カッツォ
Dialogue: 0,0:19:49.65,0:19:52.24,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,す　すまんねぇ　礼を言うぜ
Dialogue: 0,0:20:16.17,0:20:19.13,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ゴン　おめぇなんで無茶なマネしたんだよ
Dialogue: 0,0:20:19.82,0:20:20.78,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,確かに無謀だ
Dialogue: 0,0:20:21.65,0:20:22.98,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,オレ達がつかまえなかったら
Dialogue: 0,0:20:23.57,0:20:25.48,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,オメまで海のモクズだぞ
Dialogue: 0,0:20:26.46,0:20:28.50,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,でも　掴んでくれたじゃん
Dialogue: 0,0:20:32.32,0:20:34.41,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ね　決闘はどうしちゃったの
Dialogue: 0,0:20:34.89,0:20:38.58,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,決闘　ああ　そんな事はしてたっけかな
Dialogue: 0,0:20:40.63,0:20:42.24,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,先ほどの非礼をわびよう
Dialogue: 0,0:20:42.81,0:20:44.87,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,すまなかった　レオリオさん
Dialogue: 0,0:20:45.28,0:20:48.55,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,なんだよ　水くせ　レオリオでいいよ　クラピカ
Dialogue: 0,0:20:49.08,0:20:49.90,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,オレも謝る
Dialogue: 0,0:20:51.74,0:20:55.77,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,おまえの一族に対して言った言葉は　全面撤回する
Dialogue: 0,0:20:58.61,0:21:02.48,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,はははは　３人共合格だ
Dialogue: 0,0:21:04.28,0:21:05.10,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,本当かよ
Dialogue: 0,0:21:07.16,0:21:09.93,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,オレが責任持って　ドーレ島まで運んでやる
Dialogue: 0,0:21:10.62,0:21:11.65,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,れろれろー
Dialogue: 0,0:21:12.23,0:21:14.41,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,だけど　このポンコツ沈まねぇで行けんのかよ
Dialogue: 0,0:21:16.19,0:21:19.04,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,はははは　オレの腕を信じろ
Dialogue: 0,0:21:32.04,0:21:33.28,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,やった　ドーレ島だ
Dialogue: 0,0:21:33.75,0:21:35.83,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,でも　試験会場をやどう行くの
Dialogue: 0,0:21:36.18,0:21:38.50,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,バス　バスって何
Dialogue: 0,0:21:39.42,0:21:40.89,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,次回　ハンターハンター
Dialogue: 0,0:21:41.19,0:21:42.95,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,選択　近道　回り道
Dialogue: 0,0:21:43.27,0:21:44.17,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,面白いよ
Dialogue: 0,0:01:07.65,0:01:08.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,起航
Dialogue: 0,0:01:11.18,0:01:12.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那两个家伙 想干什么呀
Dialogue: 0,0:01:15.28,0:01:16.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好 开始了
Dialogue: 0,0:01:16.74,0:01:17.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,悠着点
Dialogue: 0,0:01:18.47,0:01:20.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,走
Dialogue: 0,0:01:22.24,0:01:23.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抓住我
Dialogue: 0,0:01:34.38,0:01:35.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没事吧 大叔
Dialogue: 0,0:01:36.32,0:01:39.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是大叔 是雷欧力先生
Dialogue: 0,0:01:43.64,0:01:47.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哼 看来今年到多利岛之前不会无聊了
Dialogue: 0,0:01:53.37,0:01:55.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再见了 鲸鱼岛
Dialogue: 0,0:01:55.36,0:01:59.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,尊严 波涛汹涌的大海 决斗
Dialogue: 0,0:02:28.51,0:02:30.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一万 一万零一
Dialogue: 0,0:03:00.59,0:03:02.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样小小的海浪就晕船了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:03:02.84,0:03:04.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,亏你这么大块头 真丢人啊
Dialogue: 0,0:03:04.85,0:03:07.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,到多利岛之前每年都是这样
Dialogue: 0,0:03:08.12,0:03:11.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最后吐到只剩下牙齿和骨头
Dialogue: 0,0:03:18.46,0:03:20.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这次有几个人能撑下来呢
Dialogue: 0,0:03:25.52,0:03:28.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看来看去 好像没有能行的啊
Dialogue: 0,0:03:35.68,0:03:37.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老兄 你能拿到吗
Dialogue: 0,0:03:41.70,0:03:42.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,混蛋
Dialogue: 0,0:03:54.29,0:03:55.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拿到的话 这个金块就是你的
Dialogue: 0,0:03:55.83,0:03:57.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好咧 我赌10枚金块
Dialogue: 0,0:04:06.72,0:04:09.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,混蛋
Dialogue: 0,0:04:14.75,0:04:16.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 还不错
Dialogue: 0,0:04:17.59,0:04:19.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,差不多行了 格斯
Dialogue: 0,0:04:28.55,0:04:32.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,下船 叫你下船
Dialogue: 0,0:04:33.71,0:04:34.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么
Dialogue: 0,0:04:39.37,0:04:41.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,干什么 放开我
Dialogue: 0,0:04:42.79,0:04:43.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,扔
Dialogue: 0,0:04:43.70,0:04:44.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,预备
Dialogue: 0,0:04:52.52,0:04:53.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,既然上了我的船
Dialogue: 0,0:04:54.46,0:04:56.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们就都要按照我说的来
Dialogue: 0,0:04:57.58,0:05:01.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只要我看不顺眼的统统扔下船
Dialogue: 0,0:05:02.63,0:05:04.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哼 我们可是客人啊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:07.61,0:05:08.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,上钩了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:26.96,0:05:28.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看我的
Dialogue: 0,0:05:35.67,0:05:38.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小弟弟 你钓上了大家伙啊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:38.83,0:05:42.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且是很少见的飞鱼
Dialogue: 0,0:05:43.61,0:05:46.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 在鲸鱼岛也很少见的
Dialogue: 0,0:05:51.59,0:05:54.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一点风也没有 船桅都不用一下
Dialogue: 0,0:05:54.72,0:05:57.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个样下去 什么时候才能到多利岛啊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:22.85,0:06:25.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,暴风雨要来了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:26.60,0:06:29.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么 一点迹象也没有啊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:31.94,0:06:36.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,风变得潮湿了 海上潮气也很大
Dialogue: 0,0:06:38.43,0:06:40.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,海鸥也在互相提醒呢
Dialogue: 0,0:06:40.59,0:06:44.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,海鸥 你能听懂鸟的语言吗
Dialogue: 0,0:06:45.69,0:06:47.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 能听懂一部分
Dialogue: 0,0:06:48.34,0:06:51.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘿嘿 你蒙我啊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:56.20,0:07:00.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小弟弟 你是在鲸鱼岛上船的吗
Dialogue: 0,0:07:03.41,0:07:05.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你父亲是做什么的
Dialogue: 0,0:07:05.51,0:07:09.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,猎人 虽然我只在照片上看过他
Dialogue: 0,0:07:10.87,0:07:11.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我很敬重他
Dialogue: 0,0:07:12.88,0:07:16.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吗 你的父亲也是猎人吗
Dialogue: 0,0:07:37.10,0:07:37.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小弟弟
Dialogue: 0,0:07:38.61,0:07:39.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么
Dialogue: 0,0:07:40.46,0:07:42.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你知道暴风雨的规模和来到的时间吗
Dialogue: 0,0:07:43.37,0:07:45.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,海鸥说 规模很大
Dialogue: 0,0:07:46.31,0:07:50.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,据船速来看 暴风雨在两小时后到来
Dialogue: 0,0:07:51.75,0:07:53.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我干这行这么久
Dialogue: 0,0:07:54.38,0:07:57.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小弟弟 你是第二个对我说这话的人
Dialogue: 0,0:07:58.38,0:07:59.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,第二个
Dialogue: 0,0:08:00.16,0:08:03.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小子们 收起船帆
Dialogue: 0,0:08:42.64,0:08:43.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给我小心点
Dialogue: 0,0:08:43.98,0:08:47.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不好意思 手滑了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:48.33,0:08:49.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说的好听
Dialogue: 0,0:08:49.69,0:08:53.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想用这种手段来试探我 做梦
Dialogue: 0,0:08:54.84,0:08:57.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今年可能会丰收啊
Dialogue: 0,0:09:20.80,0:09:21.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么
Dialogue: 0,0:09:23.78,0:09:25.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是圣爱尔摩之火
Dialogue: 0,0:09:26.01,0:09:27.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,圣爱尔摩之火
Dialogue: 0,0:09:27.88,0:09:31.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,即雷云或者带电云在上空聚集时
Dialogue: 0,0:09:31.41,0:09:34.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,集中在主帆等高处的电子
Dialogue: 0,0:09:34.95,0:09:37.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,产生的一种强烈的发光现象
Dialogue: 0,0:09:40.99,0:09:42.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还以为你要说啥呢
Dialogue: 0,0:09:43.24,0:09:46.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,原来就是照搬百科全书啊 真是谢了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:47.69,0:09:49.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,船员中流传着这样的传说
Dialogue: 0,0:09:49.92,0:09:51.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看到圣度艾鲁之火的人
Dialogue: 0,0:09:51.68,0:09:53.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都会成为不归人
Dialogue: 0,0:09:56.19,0:09:57.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是挺有意思的嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:09:58.05,0:09:59.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大暴风雨要来了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:07.01,0:10:12.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今年好像碰上了具有猎人素质的家伙了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:31.55,0:10:32.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,搞神马
Dialogue: 0,0:10:57.17,0:11:05.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让暴风雨来得更猛烈些吧
Dialogue: 0,0:11:05.81,0:11:08.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,船长 船底漏水了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:08.37,0:11:13.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,交给那帮没用的东西去办吧
Dialogue: 0,0:11:14.44,0:11:15.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是 sir
Dialogue: 0,0:11:17.14,0:11:18.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,左满舵
Dialogue: 0,0:11:21.89,0:11:22.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,起飞
Dialogue: 0,0:11:49.02,0:11:50.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是丢人
Dialogue: 0,0:11:50.69,0:11:52.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就凭你们这素质还想让猎人
Dialogue: 0,0:11:53.14,0:11:54.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,搞笑
Dialogue: 0,0:11:55.04,0:11:55.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,水来了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:56.93,0:11:59.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吃了这个草吧 会舒服些的
Dialogue: 0,0:12:09.95,0:12:12.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最后 好像只剩下了这三个人
Dialogue: 0,0:12:15.59,0:12:22.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,冲野的鲸鱼追逐着我
Dialogue: 0,0:12:23.01,0:12:24.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想知道我们的名字
Dialogue: 0,0:12:25.14,0:12:25.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的
Dialogue: 0,0:12:26.79,0:12:27.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是小杰
Dialogue: 0,0:12:30.77,0:12:31.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我叫酷拉皮卡
Dialogue: 0,0:12:34.65,0:12:35.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是雷欧力
Dialogue: 0,0:12:36.55,0:12:39.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小杰 酷拉皮卡 雷欧力吗
Dialogue: 0,0:12:40.28,0:12:43.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么 你们为什么想成为猎人
Dialogue: 0,0:12:44.42,0:12:46.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂 少给我摆高姿态
Dialogue: 0,0:12:47.14,0:12:48.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你又不是面试官
Dialogue: 0,0:12:49.31,0:12:50.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了 快回答
Dialogue: 0,0:12:50.79,0:12:51.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么
Dialogue: 0,0:12:51.94,0:12:54.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为我父亲就是个猎人
Dialogue: 0,0:12:54.92,0:12:57.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以我想看看猎人是个什么样的工作
Dialogue: 0,0:12:57.42,0:12:59.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂 不要随便就回答
Dialogue: 0,0:12:59.84,0:13:02.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在是我在和这个老头子说话
Dialogue: 0,0:13:02.63,0:13:04.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只是说了一下理由嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:13:04.57,0:13:07.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不想说 我绝对不会说的
Dialogue: 0,0:13:08.91,0:13:12.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,即使是要决斗 我也不会做讨厌的事情
Dialogue: 0,0:13:13.35,0:13:15.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我有同感 雷欧力
Dialogue: 0,0:13:17.15,0:13:19.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂 你多大啊
Dialogue: 0,0:13:20.44,0:13:23.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要这么没大没小的称呼我
Dialogue: 0,0:13:23.39,0:13:27.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,编个像样的答案来回避讨厌的问题很简单
Dialogue: 0,0:13:29.59,0:13:32.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我认为说假话和强盗一样
Dialogue: 0,0:13:32.30,0:13:34.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是最可耻的行为
Dialogue: 0,0:13:36.54,0:13:38.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说了让你叫我雷欧力先生
Dialogue: 0,0:13:39.31,0:13:43.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,话虽如此 我也不想对初逢的人说心里话
Dialogue: 0,0:13:44.62,0:13:48.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为我想当猎人的理由是很私人的
Dialogue: 0,0:13:49.41,0:13:53.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以 现在我无法回答你的问题
Dialogue: 0,0:13:54.03,0:13:57.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是雷欧力先生 雷欧力先生
Dialogue: 0,0:14:03.34,0:14:06.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不回答的话 现在就把你们扔下船
Dialogue: 0,0:14:08.47,0:14:09.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还不明白吗
Dialogue: 0,0:14:10.52,0:14:12.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,猎人考试已经开始了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:13.43,0:14:15.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,从你们登上这艘船时开始的
Dialogue: 0,0:14:20.74,0:14:22.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是猎人协会的
Dialogue: 0,0:14:26.47,0:14:27.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,正如你们所知
Dialogue: 0,0:14:27.88,0:14:31.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想当猎人的人像星星那么多
Dialogue: 0,0:14:31.75,0:14:34.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是 要一一审查他们
Dialogue: 0,0:14:34.71,0:14:36.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,考官可没有那个美国时间
Dialogue: 0,0:14:37.20,0:14:39.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以 他们雇用了我们这样的人
Dialogue: 0,0:14:39.67,0:14:41.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对考生进行筛选
Dialogue: 0,0:14:42.56,0:14:45.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那些被扔下船的和晕船的人
Dialogue: 0,0:14:45.75,0:14:48.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们会向审查委员会报告他们的落选
Dialogue: 0,0:14:49.93,0:14:53.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,即使他们到达考试会场也无法参加考试
Dialogue: 0,0:14:54.87,0:14:59.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们能否参加考试取决于我的判断
Dialogue: 0,0:15:00.26,0:15:03.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以还是仔细回答我的问题吧
Dialogue: 0,0:15:04.01,0:15:06.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,切 没办法 只能回答了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:08.08,0:15:10.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想成为猎人的原因是
Dialogue: 0,0:15:10.60,0:15:12.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是窟卢塔族的幸存者
Dialogue: 0,0:15:12.62,0:15:14.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂 我正在说呢好不好
Dialogue: 0,0:15:15.34,0:15:17.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想当的猎人种类是
Dialogue: 0,0:15:17.36,0:15:21.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抓捕罪犯赚取赏金的赏金猎人
Dialogue: 0,0:15:21.83,0:15:22.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,原因呢
Dialogue: 0,0:15:23.47,0:15:26.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,4年前 我的族人全部被杀了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:27.04,0:15:30.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,犯人就是杀人组织 幻影旅团
Dialogue: 0,0:15:30.65,0:15:32.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我就是为了抓住他们
Dialogue: 0,0:15:33.82,0:15:35.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,才想当猎人的吗
Dialogue: 0,0:15:38.33,0:15:41.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,幻影旅团啊 每个成员都是A级通缉犯
Dialogue: 0,0:15:42.20,0:15:44.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,即使是熟练的猎人也不会轻易出手
Dialogue: 0,0:15:45.32,0:15:47.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你这样只会白白送死
Dialogue: 0,0:15:48.17,0:15:49.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我根本不怕死
Dialogue: 0,0:15:50.30,0:15:51.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最怕的是
Dialogue: 0,0:15:52.11,0:15:55.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我会渐渐遗忘这仇恨
Dialogue: 0,0:15:57.72,0:15:59.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哼 说什么大话
Dialogue: 0,0:16:00.36,0:16:03.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只是为了复仇吗 不当猎人也可以复仇呀
Dialogue: 0,0:16:04.79,0:16:07.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这真是世界上最愚蠢的问题之一
Dialogue: 0,0:16:08.35,0:16:11.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很多特权和情报是只有猎人才能得到的
Dialogue: 0,0:16:11.92,0:16:16.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是猎人便无法享受雷欧力
Dialogue: 0,0:16:16.79,0:16:18.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说了让你叫我雷欧力先生
Dialogue: 0,0:16:19.40,0:16:21.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么 雷欧力先生想当猎人的原因是
Dialogue: 0,0:16:23.08,0:16:23.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我吗
Dialogue: 0,0:16:24.48,0:16:28.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我可不会看你脸色来说话 实话实说吧
Dialogue: 0,0:16:29.26,0:16:32.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,金钱 当了猎人就可以赚很多钱
Dialogue: 0,0:16:32.96,0:16:35.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有了钱什么都可以到手了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:35.23,0:16:39.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大房子 好车 美酒 还有女人
Dialogue: 0,0:16:40.96,0:16:43.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,金钱是买不到人品的 雷欧力
Dialogue: 0,0:16:49.76,0:16:51.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这已经是第三次了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:53.10,0:16:54.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们出去谈谈
Dialogue: 0,0:16:54.78,0:16:58.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,貌似肮脏的窟卢塔族人根本不懂礼节
Dialogue: 0,0:16:59.75,0:17:02.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,收回你刚才的话 雷欧力
Dialogue: 0,0:17:02.46,0:17:03.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是雷欧力先生
Dialogue: 0,0:17:07.28,0:17:08.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,走吧
Dialogue: 0,0:17:08.35,0:17:09.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,求之不得
Dialogue: 0,0:17:10.03,0:17:12.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂 喂 你们
Dialogue: 0,0:17:12.74,0:17:14.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,话还没说完呢
Dialogue: 0,0:17:14.79,0:17:15.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂
Dialogue: 0,0:17:16.02,0:17:17.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,随他们去吧
Dialogue: 0,0:17:18.59,0:17:20.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果想了解一个人
Dialogue: 0,0:17:20.25,0:17:23.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就要知道他的愤怒所在
Dialogue: 0,0:17:23.96,0:17:27.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我很喜欢米特阿姨教给我的这句话
Dialogue: 0,0:17:29.63,0:17:32.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我认为 他们之所以生气
Dialogue: 0,0:17:32.60,0:17:34.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是因为那些是对他们很重要的事
Dialogue: 0,0:17:35.40,0:17:36.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还是不要阻拦他们了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:41.49,0:17:43.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么 桅杆裂开了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:44.33,0:17:46.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 如果不赶快修补的话
Dialogue: 0,0:17:50.73,0:17:53.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在收回你的话还来得及 雷欧力
Dialogue: 0,0:17:54.39,0:17:56.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你才是呢 酷拉皮卡
Dialogue: 0,0:17:57.21,0:17:58.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我一点也不想让步
Dialogue: 0,0:18:08.08,0:18:08.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来吧
Dialogue: 0,0:18:09.09,0:18:10.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,放马过来
Dialogue: 0,0:18:35.33,0:18:36.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,身手不错嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:18:37.01,0:18:38.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你也是
Dialogue: 0,0:18:49.72,0:18:52.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,格斯 注意
Dialogue: 0,0:19:16.81,0:19:17.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,格斯
Dialogue: 0,0:19:49.65,0:19:52.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢 谢谢
Dialogue: 0,0:20:16.17,0:20:19.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小杰 你为什么做那么傻的事啊
Dialogue: 0,0:20:19.82,0:20:20.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,确实很没大脑
Dialogue: 0,0:20:21.65,0:20:22.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果我们没有抓住你的话
Dialogue: 0,0:20:23.57,0:20:25.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,连你也要被大海吞噬了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:26.46,0:20:28.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是 你们抓住我了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:20:32.32,0:20:34.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂 决斗怎么样了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:34.89,0:20:38.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,决斗 好像是有这回事啊
Dialogue: 0,0:20:40.63,0:20:42.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想为刚才的无礼道歉
Dialogue: 0,0:20:42.81,0:20:44.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不起 雷欧力先生
Dialogue: 0,0:20:45.28,0:20:48.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么呀 别客气了 叫我雷欧力就行了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:49.08,0:20:49.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也要道歉
Dialogue: 0,0:20:51.74,0:20:55.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,关于你族人的那些话 我全部收回
Dialogue: 0,0:20:58.61,0:21:02.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哈哈哈 你们3个都合格了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:04.28,0:21:05.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的吗
Dialogue: 0,0:21:07.16,0:21:09.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我负责把你们送到多利岛
Dialogue: 0,0:21:10.62,0:21:11.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,船神保佑
Dialogue: 0,0:21:12.23,0:21:14.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就这破船能撑到会场不
Dialogue: 0,0:21:16.19,0:21:19.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哈哈哈 就交给我吧
Dialogue: 0,0:21:32.04,0:21:33.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,总算到多利岛了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:33.75,0:21:35.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是怎么样才能到考试会场呢
Dialogue: 0,0:21:36.18,0:21:38.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,巴士 巴士是什么呀
Dialogue: 0,0:21:39.42,0:21:40.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,下集 Hunter×Hunter
Dialogue: 0,0:21:41.19,0:21:42.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,选择 近路 远路
Dialogue: 0,0:21:43.27,0:21:44.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很有趣哦


