[Script Info]
; // 此字幕由PopSub生成  2011-10-10 22:41:18
; // MESSAGE ERROR 0.75
; // popgo_fansub@yahoo.co.jp
; // 欢迎访问漫游天下 http://bbs.popgo.net
Title:漫游字幕
Original Script:漫游字幕组
Synch Point:0
ScriptType:v4.00+
Collisions:Normal
PlayResX:640
PlayResY:480
Timer:100.0000

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,方正卡通简体,31,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H016A006A,&H146C006C,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,1,0,2,30,30,10,134
Style: 日本語,MS Gothic,19,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H01000000,&HF0000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,1,0,2,30,30,10,134
Style: staff,方正卡通简体,20,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&HF0000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,0,8,30,30,10,134

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Name, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:02:01.00,0:02:06.00,staff,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(1000,1000)}本字幕由天空树双语字幕组出品
Dialogue: 0,0:02:07.00,0:02:12.00,staff,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(1000,1000)}片源：小宁  中翻：小四 可乐  日翻：小四 可乐
Dialogue: 0,0:02:13.00,0:02:18.00,staff,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(1000,1000)}校对：小四 可乐   时间轴：可乐  压制：秋水

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Actor, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:01:49.59,0:01:54.87,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,旅ゆく少年 風の音を残して
Dialogue: 0,0:02:09.48,0:02:11.83,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大分風が強くなって来とり
Dialogue: 0,0:02:12.24,0:02:13.65,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嵐になるかもしれんかね
Dialogue: 0,0:02:14.22,0:02:17.78,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ええ　こんな日ぐらい早く帰ってくればいいのに　あの子ったら
Dialogue: 0,0:02:18.20,0:02:20.03,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,楽しくてしょうがないんだよ
Dialogue: 0,0:02:20.33,0:02:23.77,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,あの子には野山が父親替わりみたいなもんだからね
Dialogue: 0,0:02:24.04,0:02:25.28,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,だって　約束したのよ
Dialogue: 0,0:02:25.48,0:02:27.45,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,日暮までには帰ってくるようにって
Dialogue: 0,0:02:28.14,0:02:31.95,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,約束を守れないような人間にはなって欲しくないの　あの子
Dialogue: 0,0:02:32.19,0:02:33.07,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ゴンだけは
Dialogue: 0,0:02:33.59,0:02:37.26,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,心配せんでも大丈夫さ　ゴンはしっかりした子だよ
Dialogue: 0,0:02:37.62,0:02:40.25,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,でもまだ１０歳にも満たない子供なのよ
Dialogue: 0,0:02:40.52,0:02:41.41,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,なにかあったら
Dialogue: 0,0:02:41.59,0:02:45.34,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,忘れちゃダメだよ　あんたは母親替りにはなれても
Dialogue: 0,0:02:45.49,0:02:49.17,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ゴンの父親の替りにはなれないんだって事をね
Dialogue: 0,0:03:47.12,0:03:51.36,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,悪い　人を傷つけちまった巨獣は処分する決まりだ
Dialogue: 0,0:04:11.00,0:04:12.03,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,立てるか
Dialogue: 0,0:04:16.51,0:04:19.39,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,こんな時期に　ヘビブナの群生地に入る奴があるか
Dialogue: 0,0:04:19.78,0:04:21.41,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,見ろ 縄張りの信号だろう
Dialogue: 0,0:04:21.64,0:04:23.63,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,あれを見たら　どんな呑気な動物でも
Dialogue: 0,0:04:23.75,0:04:25.15,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,逃げちまうほどやばいもんだ
Dialogue: 0,0:04:25.89,0:04:28.11,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,おまえの親父はそんな事も教えてくれなかったのか
Dialogue: 0,0:04:30.32,0:04:32.84,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,マダラリスの警戒音なんて無視すりゃよかったぜ
Dialogue: 0,0:04:33.21,0:04:35.70,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,久々に胸くその悪い殺しをやっちまった
Dialogue: 0,0:04:36.72,0:04:39.07,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,父さんはいない　母さんも
Dialogue: 0,0:04:40.18,0:04:42.78,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,オレが生まれてすぐ　事故に遭って死んだって
Dialogue: 0,0:04:43.35,0:04:45.93,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,オレ　おばさんの世話になってるんだ
Dialogue: 0,0:04:46.54,0:04:47.73,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,そいつは悪かったな
Dialogue: 0,0:04:48.19,0:04:50.73,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,いいんだ　助けてくれて　ありがとう
Dialogue: 0,0:04:53.95,0:04:55.28,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,その子供はどうする
Dialogue: 0,0:04:55.79,0:04:56.68,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,処分する
Dialogue: 0,0:04:57.25,0:04:58.59,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,じきに飢えて死ぬだけだ
Dialogue: 0,0:04:58.81,0:04:59.89,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,仮に生き延びても
Dialogue: 0,0:05:00.01,0:05:02.77,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,親を殺された恨みで人間を襲う危険が高い
Dialogue: 0,0:05:05.82,0:05:06.55,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,何を
Dialogue: 0,0:05:06.59,0:05:07.22,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,オレが育てる
Dialogue: 0,0:05:07.59,0:05:09.70,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,無理だ　狐熊は人には懐かない
Dialogue: 0,0:05:11.05,0:05:11.75,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,それでも
Dialogue: 0,0:05:16.20,0:05:17.39,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,おまえ
Dialogue: 0,0:05:23.25,0:05:25.65,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ゴン　遅いじゃないの　あれほど
Dialogue: 0,0:05:27.69,0:05:29.79,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ごめんなさい　ミトさん
Dialogue: 0,0:05:30.69,0:05:33.84,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ゴン　この傷はどうしたの
Dialogue: 0,0:05:34.52,0:05:36.65,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,そのー　森で転んじゃって
Dialogue: 0,0:05:40.33,0:05:41.12,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ミトさん
Dialogue: 0,0:05:41.33,0:05:43.23,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,その傷は転んだ傷じゃないわ
Dialogue: 0,0:05:43.55,0:05:46.73,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,本当の事を言わないなら　一晩中外にいるのね
Dialogue: 0,0:05:48.37,0:05:49.72,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,わかったよ　ミトさん
Dialogue: 0,0:05:50.05,0:05:52.48,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘘ついて　ごめんなさい
Dialogue: 0,0:05:54.30,0:05:57.63,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,親と逸れた狐熊の子供見つけて
Dialogue: 0,0:05:58.42,0:06:01.46,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,それで　捕まようとして 引っ掻れたんだ
Dialogue: 0,0:06:05.03,0:06:07.95,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,いいわ　入りなさい
Dialogue: 0,0:06:11.16,0:06:13.18,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,食事の前に　けがの手当ね
Dialogue: 0,0:06:26.88,0:06:29.20,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,おい　チビ　いつまでそこにいるんだ
Dialogue: 0,0:06:32.08,0:06:33.33,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,勝手にしろ
Dialogue: 0,0:06:55.25,0:06:56.82,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ほら　力入れろ
Dialogue: 0,0:06:58.29,0:06:59.50,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,セーノ
Dialogue: 0,0:07:01.27,0:07:03.72,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,オレの名はカイト　ハンターさ
Dialogue: 0,0:07:04.86,0:07:06.53,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,あのー　ハンターって
Dialogue: 0,0:07:07.22,0:07:09.38,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,世の中は　不思議な事だらけだ
Dialogue: 0,0:07:10.30,0:07:14.26,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,その謎や貴重で入手困難なアイテムを追いかけてる奴の事さ
Dialogue: 0,0:07:15.79,0:07:17.78,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ね　ここにはどうして来たの
Dialogue: 0,0:07:18.32,0:07:19.69,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,オレの先生を探してな
Dialogue: 0,0:07:19.98,0:07:20.79,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,先生
Dialogue: 0,0:07:21.66,0:07:25.76,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ああ　先生に認めてもらうための最終試験が
Dialogue: 0,0:07:26.32,0:07:28.79,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,彼を探し当てる事　なのさ
Dialogue: 0,0:07:30.04,0:07:32.59,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,まあ　これがどんなハントよりもやったら難しい
Dialogue: 0,0:07:36.84,0:07:40.09,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ゴン　昨日　両親は死んだって言ってたな
Dialogue: 0,0:07:40.51,0:07:41.22,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,うん
Dialogue: 0,0:07:41.59,0:07:42.82,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,親父の事は知ってるか
Dialogue: 0,0:07:43.25,0:07:46.55,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,うん　あまりミトさん教えてくれないし
Dialogue: 0,0:07:46.91,0:07:48.91,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,そうか　名前は
Dialogue: 0,0:07:49.48,0:07:51.52,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ジン·フリークスって言うんだ
Dialogue: 0,0:07:53.13,0:07:55.80,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ゴン　おまえの親父は生きている
Dialogue: 0,0:07:56.37,0:07:59.07,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,生きて　今も世界のどこかにいる
Dialogue: 0,0:07:59.91,0:08:03.15,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,おまえの親父　ジン·フリークスはオレの先生だ
Dialogue: 0,0:08:04.11,0:08:05.80,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,つまり　ハンターだ
Dialogue: 0,0:08:07.28,0:08:08.96,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ハンター
Dialogue: 0,0:08:09.34,0:08:12.78,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,そう　この世で最高のハンターだ
Dialogue: 0,0:08:15.13,0:08:16.36,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,何を言い出すの ゴン
Dialogue: 0,0:08:20.14,0:08:22.33,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,オレ　知りたいんだ　父さんの事
Dialogue: 0,0:08:23.08,0:08:24.11,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,教えてよ　ミトさん
Dialogue: 0,0:08:25.35,0:08:27.80,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,教えてって　極普通の人よ
Dialogue: 0,0:08:28.71,0:08:32.16,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,この店をやっていて　あなたが生まれる前に事故で死んだの
Dialogue: 0,0:08:32.67,0:08:34.98,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,それ以外に教えられる事なんてないのよ
Dialogue: 0,0:08:37.01,0:08:40.81,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,つらいようだけど　死んだ人の事は速く忘れて欲しかったの
Dialogue: 0,0:08:41.28,0:08:44.17,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,わたしは父親替わりにはなれないかもしれないけど
Dialogue: 0,0:08:44.44,0:08:46.90,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,あなたに寂しい思いはさせてないつもりよ
Dialogue: 0,0:08:48.12,0:08:49.14,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,うん
Dialogue: 0,0:08:49.97,0:08:51.69,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,わかってもらって　嬉しいわ
Dialogue: 0,0:08:57.76,0:09:00.23,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ミトさんが嘘をつくわけってなんだろう
Dialogue: 0,0:09:00.79,0:09:04.51,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,それに　父さんが生きてるなら　なんで会いに来てくれないのかな
Dialogue: 0,0:09:05.75,0:09:10.17,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,それで　やっぱり捨てられたって事なのかな
Dialogue: 0,0:09:49.13,0:09:50.95,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,あっ　お店はまだですよ
Dialogue: 0,0:09:51.53,0:09:53.50,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,すまんない　急いでるんだ
Dialogue: 0,0:09:55.17,0:09:56.21,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,それでいいのかい
Dialogue: 0,0:09:57.49,0:09:59.39,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,あ　これが気に入ってるんだ
Dialogue: 0,0:09:59.99,0:10:01.00,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,じゃ　もらっていく
Dialogue: 0,0:10:04.03,0:10:05.94,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,お母さん　ごめんなさい　遅れちゃって
Dialogue: 0,0:10:07.01,0:10:08.07,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ゴンがどこに
Dialogue: 0,0:10:08.22,0:10:09.80,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,あっ　お客さんだったのね
Dialogue: 0,0:10:10.45,0:10:12.16,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,すいません　お構いもせず
Dialogue: 0,0:10:12.45,0:10:15.16,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,いや　こっちこそ迷惑をかけたからな
Dialogue: 0,0:10:24.09,0:10:26.93,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,オレは余計な事をしちまったのかもしれん
Dialogue: 0,0:10:27.78,0:10:29.27,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,だが　あいつは
Dialogue: 0,0:10:31.54,0:10:32.59,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,後悔するよ
Dialogue: 0,0:10:33.30,0:10:35.49,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,燃やすつもりならいつでもできたろう
Dialogue: 0,0:10:35.79,0:10:37.16,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,それをなんで今更
Dialogue: 0,0:10:37.52,0:10:41.00,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,母さん　わたし怖いの
Dialogue: 0,0:10:42.39,0:10:43.79,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ゴンがあんな事を言い出して
Dialogue: 0,0:10:44.69,0:10:48.38,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,いつかわたしの元を離れて行きやしないかと
Dialogue: 0,0:10:49.43,0:10:51.94,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,母親替わりなら　わかっておやり
Dialogue: 0,0:10:52.11,0:10:55.33,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,男の子はいつかは親の元を旅立って行くんだよ
Dialogue: 0,0:10:55.73,0:10:57.52,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,それは仕方ない事なのさ
Dialogue: 0,0:10:58.46,0:10:59.91,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,あいつと同じように
Dialogue: 0,0:11:01.85,0:11:05.04,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,あの子の目が持つ光は父親そっくりだ
Dialogue: 0,0:11:06.09,0:11:07.62,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,血は争えないのさ
Dialogue: 0,0:11:08.17,0:11:11.64,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,そう　あいつは優秀なハンターの器量だ
Dialogue: 0,0:11:12.30,0:11:14.02,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,何よりいいハンターってのは
Dialogue: 0,0:11:14.20,0:11:15.98,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,動物に好かれちまうんだ
Dialogue: 0,0:11:34.69,0:11:37.21,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ハンター試験は12歳になれば受けられる
Dialogue: 0,0:11:38.11,0:11:40.35,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,それまでどう過ごそうと　勝手だがな
Dialogue: 0,0:11:42.40,0:11:43.21,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,これは
Dialogue: 0,0:11:43.61,0:11:45.44,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ハンター試験の応募カード
Dialogue: 0,0:11:45.88,0:11:47.72,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,オレ　ハンター試験を受けたい
Dialogue: 0,0:11:48.27,0:11:49.32,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ど　どうして
Dialogue: 0,0:11:49.66,0:11:51.09,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,オレ知ってたんだ　全部
Dialogue: 0,0:11:51.82,0:11:53.26,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,父さんが生きてるって事も
Dialogue: 0,0:11:53.68,0:11:54.78,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ハンターだって事も
Dialogue: 0,0:11:55.79,0:11:57.01,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,オレ　ハンターになって
Dialogue: 0,0:11:57.22,0:11:58.59,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,父さんを見つけ出したいんだ
Dialogue: 0,0:11:59.00,0:11:59.96,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,わかってよ　ミトさん
Dialogue: 0,0:12:01.82,0:12:02.71,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,この三年
Dialogue: 0,0:12:03.94,0:12:05.50,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ゴンを見ててわかったよ
Dialogue: 0,0:12:06.52,0:12:09.15,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,いつかはそう言い出すんじゃないかってね
Dialogue: 0,0:12:09.86,0:12:12.00,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,じゃあ　ダメよ　ハンターなんて
Dialogue: 0,0:12:12.89,0:12:15.30,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ミト　わかっておやりよ
Dialogue: 0,0:12:19.42,0:12:21.19,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一つ条件があるわ
Dialogue: 0,0:12:28.81,0:12:30.73,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ゴンが沼の主を釣るんだと
Dialogue: 0,0:12:31.02,0:12:32.98,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ああ　一週間でだと
Dialogue: 0,0:12:34.23,0:12:36.91,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,あんな小さいなりで　釣り上げられんのかね
Dialogue: 0,0:12:37.55,0:12:42.04,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,いや　大の大人が５人目も...ミトちゃんがずいぶん難しい問題出したな
Dialogue: 0,0:12:43.04,0:12:46.02,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,あれぐらいできなきゃ　ハンターなんか一生なれないわ
Dialogue: 0,0:12:57.58,0:12:59.69,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来た　この引きは
Dialogue: 0,0:13:26.14,0:13:27.38,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,また失敗ね
Dialogue: 0,0:13:28.58,0:13:32.22,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ミトさん　ごめん　服破いちゃった
Dialogue: 0,0:13:32.40,0:13:35.48,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,そうまでして　いい加減諦めたら
Dialogue: 0,0:13:35.90,0:13:40.64,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嫌だ　絶対釣る　約束だからね　オレハンターになるんだから
Dialogue: 0,0:13:41.06,0:13:43.19,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ハンターになって　父さんを探すんだ
Dialogue: 0,0:13:44.34,0:13:45.76,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,探してどうするのよ
Dialogue: 0,0:13:46.20,0:13:49.28,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,あいつはまだ赤ん坊だったあんたを捨てたのよ
Dialogue: 0,0:13:54.11,0:13:56.68,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,そうよ　ジンはハンターだった
Dialogue: 0,0:13:57.37,0:14:00.02,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,長いこと旅に出ては偶に戻るだけ
Dialogue: 0,0:14:00.56,0:14:03.50,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ジンがいない間　姉さんは寂しい思いをしてたわ
Dialogue: 0,0:14:04.03,0:14:06.74,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,わたしはそんな姉さんを見てるのはつらかった
Dialogue: 0,0:14:07.00,0:14:08.68,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,そして　ジンが憎らしかったわ
Dialogue: 0,0:14:08.86,0:14:10.46,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ハンターが何を追って思ってた
Dialogue: 0,0:14:11.09,0:14:13.06,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,家族も子供まで捨てて
Dialogue: 0,0:14:13.29,0:14:16.77,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,そんなあいつを探すために　あなたハンターになるつもりなの
Dialogue: 0,0:14:17.96,0:14:22.54,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,でも　子供を捨ててまで続けたいと思う仕事なんだね
Dialogue: 0,0:14:24.09,0:14:26.60,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,それだけすごい仕事なんだ　ハンターって
Dialogue: 0,0:14:29.70,0:14:33.25,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,あなた　やっぱりあいつの子供だわ
Dialogue: 0,0:14:54.48,0:14:56.17,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,あのー　ミトさんは
Dialogue: 0,0:14:57.63,0:15:02.02,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今日で約束の日最後だろう　早く食べちまいな
Dialogue: 0,0:15:06.69,0:15:07.85,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,開けてみなさい
Dialogue: 0,0:15:12.72,0:15:13.64,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,これ
Dialogue: 0,0:15:13.95,0:15:16.00,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,そのロットは　ジンが使っていた物よ
Dialogue: 0,0:15:18.15,0:15:19.78,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,それで釣れなかったら
Dialogue: 0,0:15:21.58,0:15:23.65,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ミトさん　ありがとう
Dialogue: 0,0:15:24.27,0:15:27.48,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,オレ　この釣り竿で沼の主を絶対釣って見せるよ
Dialogue: 0,0:16:14.05,0:16:17.47,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来た　来た　主が
Dialogue: 0,0:16:46.51,0:16:50.20,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,これじゃ　あいつを釣り上げられない　どうする
Dialogue: 0,0:16:51.05,0:16:51.95,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,父さんなら
Dialogue: 0,0:16:52.68,0:16:56.02,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,そうだ　もう一度主は力を緩めるかもしれない
Dialogue: 0,0:16:56.48,0:16:57.57,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,その時に
Dialogue: 0,0:17:01.08,0:17:03.04,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今だー
Dialogue: 0,0:17:21.69,0:17:23.15,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,やったー
Dialogue: 0,0:17:30.86,0:17:32.59,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,約束だよ　ミトさん
Dialogue: 0,0:17:32.96,0:17:35.42,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,これでハンター試験を受けてもいいね
Dialogue: 0,0:17:36.21,0:17:40.63,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,約束を守れないような人間になるなって教えくれたのはミトさんだよ
Dialogue: 0,0:17:41.67,0:17:43.45,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,本物の沼の主かよ
Dialogue: 0,0:17:57.94,0:17:59.14,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好きにしなさい
Dialogue: 0,0:18:02.61,0:18:03.67,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ありがとう
Dialogue: 0,0:19:03.55,0:19:04.88,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ごめんなさい　ゴン
Dialogue: 0,0:19:05.94,0:19:08.23,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,わたし　ゴンに嘘ついてた
Dialogue: 0,0:19:09.40,0:19:11.15,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ジンがゴンを捨てたんじゃないの
Dialogue: 0,0:19:12.10,0:19:16.24,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,私が裁判であなたの養育権をジンから奪い取ったの
Dialogue: 0,0:19:18.84,0:19:21.90,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,うん　嘘だって　気づいてた
Dialogue: 0,0:19:23.62,0:19:25.56,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,だって　ミトさん　オレに嘘つく時
Dialogue: 0,0:19:26.06,0:19:28.45,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,絶対にオレの顔見ないもんね
Dialogue: 0,0:19:32.46,0:19:33.52,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ゴン
Dialogue: 0,0:19:35.96,0:19:39.81,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ミトさんの匂い　本当のお母さんの匂いは知らないけど
Dialogue: 0,0:19:40.25,0:19:42.42,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ミトさんの匂いは母さんのに匂いだ
Dialogue: 0,0:19:43.29,0:19:45.99,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,オレ　どこへ行っても忘れない
Dialogue: 0,0:19:47.35,0:19:49.93,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ミトさんは母さんと一緒だ
Dialogue: 0,0:19:54.03,0:19:56.93,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最終試験は　彼を探し当てる事
Dialogue: 0,0:19:57.58,0:19:59.33,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,これがどんなハントより難しい
Dialogue: 0,0:20:00.71,0:20:03.08,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,彼は　最高のハンターだ
Dialogue: 0,0:20:24.07,0:20:26.68,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,父さん　会いに行くよ
Dialogue: 0,0:21:13.31,0:21:14.42,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,いってらっしゃい
Dialogue: 0,0:21:32.16,0:21:34.57,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,さあ　いよいよハンター試験に挑戦だ
Dialogue: 0,0:21:34.87,0:21:36.79,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,試験会場に向かう港町で
Dialogue: 0,0:21:37.06,0:21:38.66,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,変なおじさんに出会ったんだ
Dialogue: 0,0:21:39.40,0:21:40.96,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,次回　ハンターハンター
Dialogue: 0,0:21:41.42,0:21:43.41,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,出会い　とまどい　出航
Dialogue: 0,0:21:43.91,0:21:45.07,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,面白いよ
Dialogue: 0,0:01:49.59,0:01:54.87,日本語,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去旅行的少年 残留的风声
Dialogue: 0,0:02:09.48,0:02:11.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,风越来越大了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:12.24,0:02:13.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说不定会发展成暴风雨啊
Dialogue: 0,0:02:14.22,0:02:17.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那孩子真是的 这种日子该早点回来才对
Dialogue: 0,0:02:18.20,0:02:20.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,玩得太开心了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:02:20.33,0:02:23.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对他来说 山林就好像父亲一样
Dialogue: 0,0:02:24.04,0:02:25.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是我都跟他约定好了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:02:25.48,0:02:27.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太阳下山之前必须回来
Dialogue: 0,0:02:28.14,0:02:31.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我只是不希望小杰变成不守信用的人
Dialogue: 0,0:02:32.19,0:02:33.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只有他不可以
Dialogue: 0,0:02:33.59,0:02:37.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不用担心 小杰是一个很机灵的孩子哟
Dialogue: 0,0:02:37.62,0:02:40.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但他只是一个不满十岁的孩子啊
Dialogue: 0,0:02:40.52,0:02:41.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要是出了什么事的话
Dialogue: 0,0:02:41.59,0:02:45.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别忘了 即使你能代替小杰的母亲
Dialogue: 0,0:02:45.49,0:02:49.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,却不可能代替他的父亲啊
Dialogue: 0,0:03:47.12,0:03:51.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不起 我决不允许伤害人类的巨兽存活
Dialogue: 0,0:04:11.00,0:04:12.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能站起来吗
Dialogue: 0,0:04:16.51,0:04:19.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这种时候 哪有人会进入野猪的群居森林啊
Dialogue: 0,0:04:19.78,0:04:21.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看到这个选张领地的记号了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:04:21.64,0:04:23.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不管多么迟钝的动物看到这个记号
Dialogue: 0,0:04:23.75,0:04:25.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都会赶紧逃走
Dialogue: 0,0:04:25.89,0:04:28.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你父亲难道没有告诉你过吗
Dialogue: 0,0:04:30.32,0:04:32.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要是我无视斑松鼠的叫声就好了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:33.21,0:04:35.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那样就不用杀生了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:36.72,0:04:39.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我没有父亲 也没有母亲
Dialogue: 0,0:04:40.18,0:04:42.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我刚生下来 他们就遭遇意外死掉了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:43.35,0:04:45.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是阿姨把我养大的
Dialogue: 0,0:04:46.54,0:04:47.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉
Dialogue: 0,0:04:48.19,0:04:50.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没关系 谢谢你救了我
Dialogue: 0,0:04:53.95,0:04:55.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个小狐熊 你打算怎么处理
Dialogue: 0,0:04:55.79,0:04:56.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,杀掉
Dialogue: 0,0:04:57.25,0:04:58.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有母亲 它很快会饿死的
Dialogue: 0,0:04:58.81,0:04:59.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,即使侥幸活下来了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:00.01,0:05:02.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也可能会为了给母亲报仇而袭击人类
Dialogue: 0,0:05:05.82,0:05:06.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你干什么
Dialogue: 0,0:05:06.59,0:05:07.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我来养它
Dialogue: 0,0:05:07.59,0:05:09.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不可能 狐熊是不能被人类驯服的
Dialogue: 0,0:05:11.05,0:05:11.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就算那样我也要养
Dialogue: 0,0:05:16.20,0:05:17.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你
Dialogue: 0,0:05:23.25,0:05:25.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小杰 怎么回来得这么晚
Dialogue: 0,0:05:27.69,0:05:29.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不起 米特阿姨
Dialogue: 0,0:05:30.69,0:05:33.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小杰 这些伤是怎么回事
Dialogue: 0,0:05:34.52,0:05:36.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是 在森林里摔的
Dialogue: 0,0:05:40.33,0:05:41.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,米特阿姨
Dialogue: 0,0:05:41.33,0:05:43.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那些不是摔伤
Dialogue: 0,0:05:43.55,0:05:46.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果你不说实话的话 今晚就呆在外面好了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:48.37,0:05:49.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道了 米特阿姨
Dialogue: 0,0:05:50.05,0:05:52.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不起 我说谎了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:54.30,0:05:57.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我发现了一个失去了母亲的小狐熊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:58.42,0:06:01.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想抓住它 所以被它抓伤了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:05.03,0:06:07.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了 进来吧
Dialogue: 0,0:06:11.16,0:06:13.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吃饭前先处理一下伤口吧
Dialogue: 0,0:06:26.88,0:06:29.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂 小不点 你想在那里呆多久
Dialogue: 0,0:06:32.08,0:06:33.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,随便你好了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:55.25,0:06:56.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来 用力推
Dialogue: 0,0:06:58.29,0:06:59.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,预备
Dialogue: 0,0:07:01.27,0:07:03.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的名字叫卡尔多 是个猎人
Dialogue: 0,0:07:04.86,0:07:06.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,猎人是什么
Dialogue: 0,0:07:07.22,0:07:09.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个世界上有很多不可思议的事情
Dialogue: 0,0:07:10.30,0:07:14.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,猎人便需要揭开那些谜题 寻找罕有稀少的资源
Dialogue: 0,0:07:15.79,0:07:17.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那你为什么到这里来
Dialogue: 0,0:07:18.32,0:07:19.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为了找我的老师
Dialogue: 0,0:07:19.98,0:07:20.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老师
Dialogue: 0,0:07:21.66,0:07:25.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的老师给我出的最后一道测试题
Dialogue: 0,0:07:26.32,0:07:28.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是 找到他
Dialogue: 0,0:07:30.04,0:07:32.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,其实这比任何狩猎都要艰难
Dialogue: 0,0:07:36.84,0:07:40.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小杰 昨天你说你的父母都死了是吗
Dialogue: 0,0:07:40.51,0:07:41.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:07:41.59,0:07:42.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你知道你父亲的事吗
Dialogue: 0,0:07:43.25,0:07:46.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 米特阿姨没怎么对我说过
Dialogue: 0,0:07:46.91,0:07:48.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吗 你知道他的名字吗
Dialogue: 0,0:07:49.48,0:07:51.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他叫金·富力士
Dialogue: 0,0:07:53.13,0:07:55.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小杰 你的父亲还活着
Dialogue: 0,0:07:56.37,0:07:59.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,生活在世界的某个地方
Dialogue: 0,0:07:59.91,0:08:03.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你的父亲金·富力士就是我的老师
Dialogue: 0,0:08:04.11,0:08:05.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也就是说 他是一个猎人
Dialogue: 0,0:08:07.28,0:08:08.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,猎人
Dialogue: 0,0:08:09.34,0:08:12.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没错 是这个世界上最好的猎人
Dialogue: 0,0:08:15.13,0:08:16.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你说什么 小杰
Dialogue: 0,0:08:20.14,0:08:22.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想知道关于父亲的事情
Dialogue: 0,0:08:23.08,0:08:24.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,告诉我吧 米特阿姨
Dialogue: 0,0:08:25.35,0:08:27.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,已经告诉你了 他只是一个普通人
Dialogue: 0,0:08:28.71,0:08:32.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他开了这家店 但是在你出生之前就出意外死了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:32.67,0:08:34.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别的就没有什么可说的了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:37.01,0:08:40.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道你很伤心 但是还是早点忘记吧
Dialogue: 0,0:08:41.28,0:08:44.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我虽然不能代替你的父亲
Dialogue: 0,0:08:44.44,0:08:46.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但也不会让你觉得孤单的
Dialogue: 0,0:08:48.12,0:08:49.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:08:49.97,0:08:51.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你能明白 我很欣慰
Dialogue: 0,0:08:57.76,0:09:00.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,米特阿姨为什么骗我呢
Dialogue: 0,0:09:00.79,0:09:04.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还有 要是父亲还活着的话 为什么不来见我呢
Dialogue: 0,0:09:05.75,0:09:10.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,难道 我真是被抛弃了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:09:49.13,0:09:50.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 商店还没有开门呢
Dialogue: 0,0:09:51.53,0:09:53.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不起 因为我赶时间
Dialogue: 0,0:09:55.17,0:09:56.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个就够了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:09:57.49,0:09:59.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 我比较喜欢这个
Dialogue: 0,0:09:59.99,0:10:01.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么 告辞了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:04.03,0:10:05.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妈妈 对不起 我来晚了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:07.01,0:10:08.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你知道小杰在哪里吗
Dialogue: 0,0:10:08.22,0:10:09.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 有客人啊
Dialogue: 0,0:10:10.45,0:10:12.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不好意思 没有什么好东西招待您
Dialogue: 0,0:10:12.45,0:10:15.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不 是我打扰了才对
Dialogue: 0,0:10:24.09,0:10:26.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是不是做了多余的事
Dialogue: 0,0:10:27.78,0:10:29.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是 他
Dialogue: 0,0:10:31.54,0:10:32.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你会后悔的
Dialogue: 0,0:10:33.30,0:10:35.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想烧的话随时可以烧的
Dialogue: 0,0:10:35.79,0:10:37.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么等到现在
Dialogue: 0,0:10:37.52,0:10:41.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妈妈 我很害怕
Dialogue: 0,0:10:42.39,0:10:43.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小杰那样说
Dialogue: 0,0:10:44.69,0:10:48.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我担心有一天他会离开我
Dialogue: 0,0:10:49.43,0:10:51.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,作为母亲 你一定要明白
Dialogue: 0,0:10:52.11,0:10:55.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,男孩子总是会离开父母去远行的
Dialogue: 0,0:10:55.73,0:10:57.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是不能避免的
Dialogue: 0,0:10:58.46,0:10:59.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就像他一样吗
Dialogue: 0,0:11:01.85,0:11:05.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小杰的眼神和他父亲一摸一样
Dialogue: 0,0:11:06.09,0:11:07.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有道是虎父无犬子啊
Dialogue: 0,0:11:08.17,0:11:11.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没错 他会成为优秀的猎人
Dialogue: 0,0:11:12.30,0:11:14.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为成为一个好猎人的基本条件
Dialogue: 0,0:11:14.20,0:11:15.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是要受到动物的喜爱
Dialogue: 0,0:11:34.69,0:11:37.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,12岁后就可以参加猎人考试
Dialogue: 0,0:11:38.11,0:11:40.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,到那时为止 你自己决定吧
Dialogue: 0,0:11:42.40,0:11:43.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个是
Dialogue: 0,0:11:43.61,0:11:45.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,猎人考试的申请卡
Dialogue: 0,0:11:45.88,0:11:47.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想参加猎人考试
Dialogue: 0,0:11:48.27,0:11:49.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么
Dialogue: 0,0:11:49.66,0:11:51.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我都知道了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:51.82,0:11:53.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,父亲还活着的事情
Dialogue: 0,0:11:53.68,0:11:54.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他是个猎人的事情
Dialogue: 0,0:11:55.79,0:11:57.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要成为猎人
Dialogue: 0,0:11:57.22,0:11:58.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后找出父亲
Dialogue: 0,0:11:59.00,0:11:59.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,希望你能明白 米特阿姨
Dialogue: 0,0:12:01.82,0:12:02.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这三年来
Dialogue: 0,0:12:03.94,0:12:05.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只要看看小杰就明白了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:06.52,0:12:09.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他早晚有一天会这样说的
Dialogue: 0,0:12:09.86,0:12:12.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么 不行 我不答应你当猎人
Dialogue: 0,0:12:12.89,0:12:15.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,米特 理解他吧
Dialogue: 0,0:12:19.42,0:12:21.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧 我有一个条件
Dialogue: 0,0:12:28.81,0:12:30.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听说小杰要去钓沼泽之主
Dialogue: 0,0:12:31.02,0:12:32.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 时间是一星期
Dialogue: 0,0:12:34.23,0:12:36.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这么小小年纪 能钓到吗
Dialogue: 0,0:12:37.55,0:12:42.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊 连5个大人都拿它没辙 米特你可是出了个大难题啊
Dialogue: 0,0:12:43.04,0:12:46.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果连这点小事都办不到 那这辈子也当不了猎人
Dialogue: 0,0:12:57.58,0:12:59.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,上钩了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:26.14,0:13:27.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,又失败了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:13:28.58,0:13:32.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,米特阿姨 对不起 我把衣服弄破了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:32.40,0:13:35.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都这样了 还是放弃吧
Dialogue: 0,0:13:35.90,0:13:40.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不 我一定要钓到 我们说好的啊 我一定要当猎人
Dialogue: 0,0:13:41.06,0:13:43.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,成为猎人 找到父亲
Dialogue: 0,0:13:44.34,0:13:45.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,找到又怎么样呢
Dialogue: 0,0:13:46.20,0:13:49.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他丢下还是个婴儿的你
Dialogue: 0,0:13:54.11,0:13:56.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的 金是猎人
Dialogue: 0,0:13:57.37,0:14:00.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,常年在外旅行 很少回家
Dialogue: 0,0:14:00.56,0:14:03.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,金不在的时候 姐姐过着很寂寞的生活
Dialogue: 0,0:14:04.03,0:14:06.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看到姐姐那样 我很难过
Dialogue: 0,0:14:07.00,0:14:08.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以 我讨厌金
Dialogue: 0,0:14:08.86,0:14:10.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,猎人追求的到底是什么
Dialogue: 0,0:14:11.09,0:14:13.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,连家人和孩子都可以抛下
Dialogue: 0,0:14:13.29,0:14:16.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你当猎人就是为了找那样的家伙吗
Dialogue: 0,0:14:17.96,0:14:22.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是 即使是丢下孩子也要去做的工作
Dialogue: 0,0:14:24.09,0:14:26.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,猎人肯定是很了不起的工作啊
Dialogue: 0,0:14:29.70,0:14:33.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你果然是金的孩子啊
Dialogue: 0,0:14:54.48,0:14:56.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个 米特阿姨呢
Dialogue: 0,0:14:57.63,0:15:02.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天是约定期限的最后一天了 快点吃饭吧
Dialogue: 0,0:15:06.69,0:15:07.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,打开看看
Dialogue: 0,0:15:12.72,0:15:13.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是
Dialogue: 0,0:15:13.95,0:15:16.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这根鱼竿 是金用过的
Dialogue: 0,0:15:18.15,0:15:19.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,用这根鱼竿还是钓不到的话
Dialogue: 0,0:15:21.58,0:15:23.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢你 米特阿姨
Dialogue: 0,0:15:24.27,0:15:27.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我一定用这根鱼竿把沼泽之主钓给你看
Dialogue: 0,0:16:14.05,0:16:17.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,上钩了 沼泽之主
Dialogue: 0,0:16:46.51,0:16:50.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样 不可能钓上它来 怎么办
Dialogue: 0,0:16:51.05,0:16:51.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要是父亲的话
Dialogue: 0,0:16:52.68,0:16:56.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对了 它在下一次冲刺之前一定会有一个缓冲期
Dialogue: 0,0:16:56.48,0:16:57.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就趁那时
Dialogue: 0,0:17:01.08,0:17:03.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是现在
Dialogue: 0,0:17:21.69,0:17:23.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,成功了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:30.86,0:17:32.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们说好的 米特阿姨
Dialogue: 0,0:17:32.96,0:17:35.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样我就能够参加猎人考试了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:17:36.21,0:17:40.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是米特阿姨教给我的 不能再做不讲信用的人
Dialogue: 0,0:17:41.67,0:17:43.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哇塞 这真的是沼泽之主啊
Dialogue: 0,0:17:57.94,0:17:59.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,随便你好了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:02.61,0:18:03.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢
Dialogue: 0,0:19:03.55,0:19:04.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不起 小杰
Dialogue: 0,0:19:05.94,0:19:08.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我骗了你
Dialogue: 0,0:19:09.40,0:19:11.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,金没有丢下你
Dialogue: 0,0:19:12.10,0:19:16.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是我通过法院抢到了你的养育权
Dialogue: 0,0:19:18.84,0:19:21.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 我知道
Dialogue: 0,0:19:23.62,0:19:25.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为米特阿姨对我说谎的时候
Dialogue: 0,0:19:26.06,0:19:28.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,总是不会看我的脸的
Dialogue: 0,0:19:32.46,0:19:33.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小杰
Dialogue: 0,0:19:35.96,0:19:39.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然不知道母亲的味道是什么样的
Dialogue: 0,0:19:40.25,0:19:42.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我觉得就是米特阿姨的味道就是妈妈的味道
Dialogue: 0,0:19:43.29,0:19:45.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我永远不会忘记的
Dialogue: 0,0:19:47.35,0:19:49.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,米特阿姨就是我的母亲
Dialogue: 0,0:19:54.03,0:19:56.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最终考试就是找到他
Dialogue: 0,0:19:57.58,0:19:59.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个比任何工作都难
Dialogue: 0,0:20:00.71,0:20:03.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他是最棒的猎人
Dialogue: 0,0:20:24.07,0:20:26.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,父亲 我来见你了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:13.31,0:21:14.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一路顺风
Dialogue: 0,0:21:32.16,0:21:34.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,终于要开始挑战猎人考试了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:34.87,0:21:36.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在通往考场的港口城市
Dialogue: 0,0:21:37.06,0:21:38.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我遇见了一个奇怪的大叔
Dialogue: 0,0:21:39.40,0:21:40.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,下集 Hunter×Hunter
Dialogue: 0,0:21:41.42,0:21:43.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,相遇 慌张 出航
Dialogue: 0,0:21:43.91,0:21:45.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很有趣哦


