[Script Info]
; // 此字幕由PopSub生成  2011-11-06 20:48:14
; // MESSAGE ERROR 0.75
; // popgo_fansub@yahoo.co.jp
; // 欢迎访问漫游天下 http://bbs.popgo.net
Title:漫游字幕
Original Script:漫游字幕组
Synch Point:0
ScriptType:v4.00+
Collisions:Normal
PlayResX:640
PlayResY:480
Timer:100.0000

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,MS Gothic,18,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&HF0000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,1,0,2,30,30,10,134
Style: 1,方正粗倩简体,30,&H02FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H01FF0080,&HF0000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,1,0,2,30,30,10,134
Style: staff,方正卡通简体,20,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&HF0000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,1,0,8,30,30,10,134

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Actor, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:02:01.00,0:02:06.00,staff,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(1000,1000)}本字幕由天空树双语字幕组出品
Dialogue: 0,0:02:07.00,0:02:12.00,staff,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(1000,1000)}片源：小宁  中翻&日翻：小眠
Dialogue: 0,0:02:13.00,0:02:18.00,staff,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(1000,1000)}校对&时间轴：可乐  压制：往观四荒
Dialogue: 0,0:02:21.00,0:02:55.00,staff,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(1000,1000)}更多精彩视频请访问【天空树BBS】
Dialogue: 0,0:01:07.04,0:01:10.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ここトリックタワーが三次試験の会場でございます
Dialogue: 0,0:01:11.63,0:01:12.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ルールは簡単
Dialogue: 0,0:01:12.88,0:01:14.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,生きて下までおりること
Dialogue: 0,0:01:15.02,0:01:16.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,制限時間は七十二時間
Dialogue: 0,0:01:17.34,0:01:18.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,それではスタート
Dialogue: 0,0:01:19.84,0:01:20.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,三日
Dialogue: 0,0:01:21.52,0:01:23.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,たかが通り一本に三日とは
Dialogue: 0,0:01:24.15,0:01:26.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,それほどの障害なのかよ
Dialogue: 0,0:01:27.34,0:01:29.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,二次試験より困難のことは間違いない
Dialogue: 0,0:01:30.13,0:01:31.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,油断は禁物だ
Dialogue: 0,0:01:43.56,0:01:44.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,テスト開始
Dialogue: 0,0:01:46.19,0:01:50.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,賛成　反対　おとし穴
Dialogue: 0,0:01:51.46,0:01:52.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,どうするの
Dialogue: 0,0:01:52.85,0:01:54.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,側面には窓一つない
Dialogue: 0,0:01:55.16,0:01:56.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ああ　只の壁だ
Dialogue: 0,0:01:57.38,0:01:59.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ここから下りるのは自殺行為だぜ
Dialogue: 0,0:02:00.08,0:02:01.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,普通の人間ならばな
Dialogue: 0,0:02:04.18,0:02:06.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,だが　一流のロッククライマーが
Dialogue: 0,0:02:07.57,0:02:09.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,このぐらいの取っ掛かりがあれば
Dialogue: 0,0:02:09.34,0:02:10.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,難なくクリア出来るぜ
Dialogue: 0,0:02:10.86,0:02:12.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,う―わぁ　スッゲー
Dialogue: 0,0:02:12.71,0:02:14.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,もうあんなり下りてる
Dialogue: 0,0:02:14.59,0:02:16.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,見てるだけでけつがむずいぜ
Dialogue: 0,0:02:21.27,0:02:21.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,あれ
Dialogue: 0,0:02:23.74,0:02:26.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,どうやら　三次試験合格一番乗りは
Dialogue: 0,0:02:26.26,0:02:27.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,オレ様のようだ
Dialogue: 0,0:02:40.40,0:02:42.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,外壁を伝うのはやめた方がいいな
Dialogue: 0,0:02:43.41,0:02:46.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,きっとどこかに　下に通じる扉があるはずだ
Dialogue: 0,0:02:49.02,0:02:51.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,考える事は皆同じか
Dialogue: 0,0:02:51.85,0:02:55.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我々も遅れを取らぬよう　手分けして扉を捜すんだ
Dialogue: 0,0:03:19.98,0:03:22.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,人数が減ったな　何
Dialogue: 0,0:03:24.10,0:03:29.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,五　十　十五　二十　二十三人
Dialogue: 0,0:03:30.25,0:03:31.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,何時の間に
Dialogue: 0,0:03:31.46,0:03:33.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,半数近くが扉を見つけ
Dialogue: 0,0:03:34.20,0:03:36.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,すでに下に下りていた事になる
Dialogue: 0,0:03:38.22,0:03:41.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,その全員が同じ扉を潜ったとは考え難い
Dialogue: 0,0:03:43.71,0:03:47.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,複数の隠し扉が存在すると考えのが順当だろう
Dialogue: 0,0:03:48.30,0:03:50.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,レオリオ　クラピカ
Dialogue: 0,0:03:51.96,0:03:52.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,見つけたのか
Dialogue: 0,0:03:53.31,0:03:54.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,でかしたぞ　ゴン
Dialogue: 0,0:03:54.99,0:03:57.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所長　ガキが二つもいますが
Dialogue: 0,0:03:58.27,0:03:59.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,まぐれでしょうか
Dialogue: 0,0:03:59.72,0:04:02.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ハンター試験はそんなに甘くない
Dialogue: 0,0:04:02.42,0:04:03.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,よし　開けるぞ
Dialogue: 0,0:04:08.07,0:04:09.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,なんだ　これや
Dialogue: 0,0:04:10.79,0:04:12.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,オートロックになてるようだ
Dialogue: 0,0:04:12.87,0:04:14.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,じゃ　もうこの扉
Dialogue: 0,0:04:14.93,0:04:16.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ほかを探すしかないだろ
Dialogue: 0,0:04:16.86,0:04:18.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ちぇ　お一人様専用
Dialogue: 0,0:04:19.15,0:04:21.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,それも一回こっきりって事か
Dialogue: 0,0:04:22.49,0:04:26.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,そして各々の扉は別のルートに繋がっている物と考えた方がいい
Dialogue: 0,0:04:26.60,0:04:29.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ああ　落ち着いて分析してる場合か
Dialogue: 0,0:04:29.57,0:04:32.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,扉が人数分以上あるかどうかも分かんねぇのによ
Dialogue: 0,0:04:32.90,0:04:33.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,あるよ
Dialogue: 0,0:04:34.41,0:04:36.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,あるよって　扉がか
Dialogue: 0,0:04:36.53,0:04:39.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,うん　見つけたのは六つ　お釣りが来るよ
Dialogue: 0,0:04:40.30,0:04:43.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ディンゴだ　それぞれ配置につき
Dialogue: 0,0:04:43.41,0:04:44.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,はぁ
Dialogue: 0,0:04:47.08,0:04:52.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,受験者を一時間を仕留めする事に一年分の刑期出し
Dialogue: 0,0:04:52.45,0:04:54.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,連中には願ってもない条件だ
Dialogue: 0,0:04:55.07,0:04:57.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,感謝する事だ　このオレに
Dialogue: 0,0:04:58.81,0:05:01.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,こことここ　後こっちにも三つ
Dialogue: 0,0:05:02.45,0:05:04.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,こんなに近くに五つもあるなんて
Dialogue: 0,0:05:05.05,0:05:07.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,何とも胡散くさいぜ
Dialogue: 0,0:05:07.46,0:05:09.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,このうちのいくつか罠かもしれない
Dialogue: 0,0:05:11.55,0:05:13.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,運も実力のうちって事か
Dialogue: 0,0:05:14.80,0:05:16.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,罠にかかっても恨みっこなし
Dialogue: 0,0:05:16.79,0:05:17.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,無し無し
Dialogue: 0,0:05:18.17,0:05:20.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,じゃ　扉の選択順を決めよう
Dialogue: 0,0:05:21.31,0:05:23.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ジャンケンポン
Dialogue: 0,0:05:24.95,0:05:27.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一二の三で　全員で行こうね
Dialogue: 0,0:05:28.72,0:05:30.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ここで一旦お別れだ
Dialogue: 0,0:05:31.25,0:05:32.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,地上でまた会おう
Dialogue: 0,0:05:33.18,0:05:33.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,あ
Dialogue: 0,0:05:34.58,0:05:35.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,じゃ　行くよ
Dialogue: 0,0:05:36.39,0:05:38.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一二の三
Dialogue: 0,0:06:04.27,0:06:05.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,短い別れだったな
Dialogue: 0,0:06:06.04,0:06:06.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,全く
Dialogue: 0,0:06:07.44,0:06:09.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,この部屋も出口がないよ
Dialogue: 0,0:06:09.58,0:06:11.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,また隠し扉かよ
Dialogue: 0,0:06:11.84,0:06:12.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,何かある
Dialogue: 0,0:06:17.07,0:06:18.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,多数決の道
Dialogue: 0,0:06:19.29,0:06:22.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,君たち五人はここからゴールまでの道のりを
Dialogue: 0,0:06:22.94,0:06:25.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,多数決で乗り越えなければならない
Dialogue: 0,0:06:26.83,0:06:27.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,多数決
Dialogue: 0,0:06:27.99,0:06:28.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,これって
Dialogue: 0,0:06:29.42,0:06:30.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,タイマーだな
Dialogue: 0,0:06:30.90,0:06:32.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,○と×のボタンが付いている
Dialogue: 0,0:06:34.00,0:06:35.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,もしかしてあと一人
Dialogue: 0,0:06:36.73,0:06:38.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,誰かがこの部屋で下りて来ないと
Dialogue: 0,0:06:40.03,0:06:42.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,オレ達はここから出なれないという事か
Dialogue: 0,0:06:43.20,0:06:44.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,その通り
Dialogue: 0,0:06:45.02,0:06:48.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,このタワーには幾通りもルートが用意されており
Dialogue: 0,0:06:48.69,0:06:51.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,それぞれにクリア条件が異なっている
Dialogue: 0,0:06:52.17,0:06:55.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,君達には多数決の道が巡ってきたというわけだ
Dialogue: 0,0:06:56.42,0:07:00.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,互いの協力が絶対強条件となる難コース
Dialogue: 0,0:07:00.61,0:07:03.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,それでは　諸君らの健闘を祈る
Dialogue: 0,0:07:06.11,0:07:10.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,残り七十一時間十八分　待つしかないな
Dialogue: 0,0:07:34.75,0:07:35.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,あれから二時間
Dialogue: 0,0:07:36.56,0:07:40.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,もしかしてもう全員別ルートで行っちまったんじゃないのか
Dialogue: 0,0:07:41.18,0:07:45.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,いま頂上に残ってるようなヤツはよっぽどの間抜けだぜ
Dialogue: 0,0:07:46.60,0:07:48.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,その間抜けが来た見たいだぜ
Dialogue: 0,0:07:52.70,0:07:53.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,て　てめえ
Dialogue: 0,0:07:54.21,0:07:54.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ドンパさん
Dialogue: 0,0:07:56.21,0:07:57.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,皆さんを揃いて
Dialogue: 0,0:07:59.37,0:08:02.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,おめえと仲良く多数決のこなんて　オレごめんだぜ
Dialogue: 0,0:08:06.31,0:08:08.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,これでよしと
Dialogue: 0,0:08:10.12,0:08:11.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,よしゃ　行こうぜ
Dialogue: 0,0:08:12.51,0:08:14.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,よしゃじゃねぇよ　最後にノコノコ来といて
Dialogue: 0,0:08:15.18,0:08:16.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,偉そうに
Dialogue: 0,0:08:19.83,0:08:20.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最初の選択だ
Dialogue: 0,0:08:21.48,0:08:23.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,そのドアを開けるなら?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:23.44,0:08:25.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,開けないなら?のボタンを押せ
Dialogue: 0,0:08:26.21,0:08:27.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ここからもう多数決かよ
Dialogue: 0,0:08:28.27,0:08:30.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,こんなものは答えが決まったろうが
Dialogue: 0,0:08:34.71,0:08:35.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,あれ
Dialogue: 0,0:08:35.91,0:08:38.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,だれだ　×のボタンを押したのは
Dialogue: 0,0:08:38.43,0:08:41.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ああ　スマンスマン　オレが間違いで押しまった
Dialogue: 0,0:08:42.23,0:08:44.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,おい　ふざけんじゃねぇーぜ　オッサン
Dialogue: 0,0:08:44.59,0:08:47.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,どうやったら　○と×を間違えられるんだ　うーん
Dialogue: 0,0:08:48.19,0:08:49.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,だがら　謝ってんだろう
Dialogue: 0,0:08:50.03,0:08:52.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,なんで間違ったか聞いてんだよ
Dialogue: 0,0:08:52.36,0:08:55.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,もういいから　行こうよ　ちゃんと開いたし
Dialogue: 0,0:08:55.28,0:08:58.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,いや　よくねぇーな　コイツはわぜと×を押したんだ
Dialogue: 0,0:08:58.82,0:09:02.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,既に　二時間浪費している　争っている時間が惜しい
Dialogue: 0,0:09:03.70,0:09:07.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,そうそう　仮にそいつが全部わざと逆らってもさ
Dialogue: 0,0:09:08.12,0:09:10.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,オレ達がまとまってりゃいいわけだろう
Dialogue: 0,0:09:11.22,0:09:12.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,それでも足でまといなら
Dialogue: 0,0:09:15.69,0:09:18.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ちぇ　分かったよ　さっさと行こうぜ
Dialogue: 0,0:09:19.79,0:09:22.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,だがよ　また同じ事やったら　グーって殴るからな
Dialogue: 0,0:09:35.66,0:09:36.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,またかよ
Dialogue: 0,0:09:37.29,0:09:40.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,右に行くなら○　左なら×だ
Dialogue: 0,0:09:41.52,0:09:42.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,へいへい
Dialogue: 0,0:09:44.65,0:09:48.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,右　普通こう言う時や左を選べるだろう
Dialogue: 0,0:09:49.02,0:09:51.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,つーか　オレはこんな場合左じゃねぇと
Dialogue: 0,0:09:51.87,0:09:53.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,なんか落ち着かねぇんだよな
Dialogue: 0,0:09:55.67,0:09:57.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,確かに　行動学の検知からも
Dialogue: 0,0:09:58.47,0:10:01.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,人は迷ったり道のルート選ぶ時には
Dialogue: 0,0:10:01.31,0:10:04.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,無意識に左を選択ケースが多いらしい
Dialogue: 0,0:10:05.16,0:10:06.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,オレもそれ聞いた事ある
Dialogue: 0,0:10:07.23,0:10:09.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,あ　ちょっと待って　それだと計算合わねぇぞ
Dialogue: 0,0:10:09.79,0:10:11.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,お前らどっち押したんだよ
Dialogue: 0,0:10:11.98,0:10:13.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,右　右
Dialogue: 0,0:10:13.68,0:10:15.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,お前らな
Dialogue: 0,0:10:15.65,0:10:18.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,左を選び易いからこそ　右なんだよ
Dialogue: 0,0:10:18.79,0:10:21.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,試験官なら　その法則を知り抜いていて
Dialogue: 0,0:10:21.50,0:10:24.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,左に難度の高い課題を設けるはずだからな
Dialogue: 0,0:10:25.05,0:10:25.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,そういう事だ
Dialogue: 0,0:10:26.29,0:10:29.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ケッ　どうせオレ達が単純だよ　なあ　ゴン
Dialogue: 0,0:10:31.27,0:10:34.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ヤッバリ　レオリオと同じレベルなんだ　オレ
Dialogue: 0,0:10:47.23,0:10:49.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,なんじゃ　こりゃー
Dialogue: 0,0:11:04.84,0:11:05.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,見ろよ
Dialogue: 0,0:11:09.72,0:11:12.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,リッポン所長　テスト生が来たぜ
Dialogue: 0,0:11:12.86,0:11:14.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,コイツを外してくれよ
Dialogue: 0,0:11:22.86,0:11:27.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我々は貴様らテスト生を試すために雇われたものだ
Dialogue: 0,0:11:27.60,0:11:31.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ここでおまえ達は我々五人と戦わなければならない
Dialogue: 0,0:11:32.62,0:11:34.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,あの人強そうだね
Dialogue: 0,0:11:34.66,0:11:36.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,だからオレは左に行きたかったんだ
Dialogue: 0,0:11:37.42,0:11:39.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,左はもっと厳しかったかもしれないぞ
Dialogue: 0,0:11:40.23,0:11:43.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,勝負は一対一　一度きりしか戦えん
Dialogue: 0,0:11:44.07,0:11:47.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,順番は自由だ　おまえ達は多数決
Dialogue: 0,0:11:48.18,0:11:51.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,すなわち　三勝以上すればここを通過できる
Dialogue: 0,0:11:51.82,0:11:54.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,戦い方は自由　引き分けはなし
Dialogue: 0,0:11:55.41,0:11:57.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,片方が負けを認めた場合において
Dialogue: 0,0:11:58.12,0:12:00.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,残された片方を勝者とする
Dialogue: 0,0:12:02.30,0:12:05.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,この勝負受けるか否か採決されよ
Dialogue: 0,0:12:05.48,0:12:08.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,受けるなら○　受けないなら×をされよ
Dialogue: 0,0:12:09.10,0:12:12.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,また採決かよ　一々時間の無駄だぜ
Dialogue: 0,0:12:13.07,0:12:16.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,どうせ合格するにやこの勝負うけなきゃならないんだ
Dialogue: 0,0:12:17.12,0:12:18.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,全員○に決まってんだろうが
Dialogue: 0,0:12:19.95,0:12:23.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,どっかの間抜けが足並乱さなきゃな
Dialogue: 0,0:12:25.15,0:12:27.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,へいへい　分かってますよ
Dialogue: 0,0:12:29.77,0:12:31.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,どうだ　全員一致だぜ
Dialogue: 0,0:12:31.77,0:12:34.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,よかろう　こちらの一番手はこのオレだ
Dialogue: 0,0:12:35.31,0:12:36.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,そっちは誰が出る
Dialogue: 0,0:12:37.51,0:12:39.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,どうする　誰が行く
Dialogue: 0,0:12:41.45,0:12:44.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,セッティング完了しました　後六十九時間
Dialogue: 0,0:12:45.26,0:12:48.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ヤツらはもう三年分の刑期を稼ぎましたね
Dialogue: 0,0:12:48.70,0:12:50.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,さーて　見物と行こうか
Dialogue: 0,0:12:51.44,0:12:52.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,じゃ　オレが行くよ
Dialogue: 0,0:12:53.19,0:12:54.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,いや　私が行こう
Dialogue: 0,0:12:55.59,0:12:58.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,見たところヤツは腕力で押してきそうなタイプだ
Dialogue: 0,0:12:58.93,0:13:01.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,まともにぶつかったら　ゴンにや不利だ
Dialogue: 0,0:13:01.41,0:13:04.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,待て待て　ゴンで無理なら　お前だって無理だぜ
Dialogue: 0,0:13:05.23,0:13:07.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,しかし　私には武器がある
Dialogue: 0,0:13:07.40,0:13:09.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,そんなもん取り上げられたらアウトじゃねぇか
Dialogue: 0,0:13:10.23,0:13:11.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,じゃ　レオリオが行くのか
Dialogue: 0,0:13:15.62,0:13:17.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,あら　なんという筋肉してやがんだよ
Dialogue: 0,0:13:18.46,0:13:19.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,びびってんなら　オレが行くぜ
Dialogue: 0,0:13:20.42,0:13:21.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,キルア
Dialogue: 0,0:13:21.41,0:13:23.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,決まりだな　待って
Dialogue: 0,0:13:24.94,0:13:25.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,オレが行こう
Dialogue: 0,0:13:28.87,0:13:29.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,バカ言えよ
Dialogue: 0,0:13:30.10,0:13:32.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,オメエみてぇな小悪党に適う相手じゃねぇよ
Dialogue: 0,0:13:33.76,0:13:34.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,そうでもない
Dialogue: 0,0:13:35.99,0:13:39.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,戦い方が自由って事は　裏をかえせば何でもあり
Dialogue: 0,0:13:40.34,0:13:42.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,何を仕掛けてくるか分からんって事だ
Dialogue: 0,0:13:43.27,0:13:44.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,見た目が屈強だからと言って
Dialogue: 0,0:13:44.88,0:13:47.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,力合せだけで押してくるとは限らない
Dialogue: 0,0:13:47.90,0:13:51.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,つまり　今重要なのは　腕力ではなく
Dialogue: 0,0:13:51.54,0:13:54.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,何が起きても　対処出来る経験と感だ
Dialogue: 0,0:13:55.23,0:13:58.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,オレが毒味役として　相手の出方を伺う
Dialogue: 0,0:14:01.27,0:14:04.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,これまでの事　わびをさしてくれ　この通りだ
Dialogue: 0,0:14:05.32,0:14:07.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今さら　信用できるかよ
Dialogue: 0,0:14:08.39,0:14:09.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,そこなんだ
Dialogue: 0,0:14:09.70,0:14:12.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,オレが先鋒をかっててる大きな理由は
Dialogue: 0,0:14:13.07,0:14:16.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,おまえ達はオレを今一つ信用仕切れていないだろ
Dialogue: 0,0:14:16.85,0:14:18.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今一つどころじゃねぇ
Dialogue: 0,0:14:18.89,0:14:19.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,まあ　聞け
Dialogue: 0,0:14:20.16,0:14:21.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,この先もしかすると
Dialogue: 0,0:14:21.67,0:14:24.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,二勝二敗の局面が来るかもしれない
Dialogue: 0,0:14:24.64,0:14:26.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,そんな時に信用してないオレなんかに
Dialogue: 0,0:14:26.90,0:14:29.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,勝負を託す事ができるか
Dialogue: 0,0:14:33.92,0:14:35.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,やらせりゃいいじゃん
Dialogue: 0,0:14:35.51,0:14:38.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,オッサンの言い分にも一理あるし
Dialogue: 0,0:14:39.35,0:14:41.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,き　決まりだな
Dialogue: 0,0:14:47.41,0:14:50.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,先鋒かっててからにゃ　絶対負けんじゃねぇぞ
Dialogue: 0,0:14:50.83,0:14:54.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,まあ　見てな　一番手はオレだ
Dialogue: 0,0:14:54.86,0:14:55.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,オーケー
Dialogue: 0,0:15:14.06,0:15:16.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,さて　勝負の方法を決めようか
Dialogue: 0,0:15:17.32,0:15:20.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,オレはデスマッチを提案する
Dialogue: 0,0:15:23.21,0:15:25.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最悪じゃねぇか　どうすんだ　クラピカ
Dialogue: 0,0:15:26.18,0:15:28.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,マズイな　裏を読みすぎた
Dialogue: 0,0:15:28.94,0:15:31.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,でも　トンパさん自信ありそうだったじゃない
Dialogue: 0,0:15:32.05,0:15:34.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,きっと　すごい作戦があるんだよ
Dialogue: 0,0:15:34.44,0:15:35.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,見てれば分かる
Dialogue: 0,0:15:37.86,0:15:41.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一方が負けを認めるか　または死ぬかするまで戦う
Dialogue: 0,0:15:42.55,0:15:43.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,どうだ
Dialogue: 0,0:15:47.27,0:15:49.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,アイツなかなか返事しませんぜ
Dialogue: 0,0:15:50.44,0:15:52.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,囚人共には好都合だな
Dialogue: 0,0:15:54.25,0:15:58.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,全くです　あの連中の刑期は皆百年以上
Dialogue: 0,0:15:59.15,0:16:01.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,そう　重犯罪者ばかりだ
Dialogue: 0,0:16:02.10,0:16:04.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,こうでもしなけりゃ　刑期なんて減るもんじゃない
Dialogue: 0,0:16:05.30,0:16:09.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ベンドットは強盗殺人で懲役百九十九年
Dialogue: 0,0:16:09.98,0:16:12.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,さぜや張り切ってるに違いありません
Dialogue: 0,0:16:13.09,0:16:16.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,公然と人殺しができて　しかも減刑されるわけですから
Dialogue: 0,0:16:17.71,0:16:21.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,どうした　デスマッチをするのか　しないのか
Dialogue: 0,0:16:21.56,0:16:23.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,お前がグズグズ迷ってると
Dialogue: 0,0:16:23.82,0:16:26.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,仲間の持ち時間までどんどん減っていくぞ
Dialogue: 0,0:16:28.20,0:16:31.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,その分　オレ達の刑期は減って行ってくれる
Dialogue: 0,0:16:31.59,0:16:32.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ありがたいっこだぜ
Dialogue: 0,0:16:34.54,0:16:37.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,いいだろ　その勝負 受けた
Dialogue: 0,0:16:37.60,0:16:38.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,トンパ
Dialogue: 0,0:16:40.07,0:16:41.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,トンパさん
Dialogue: 0,0:16:42.16,0:16:44.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,その覚悟　見事なり
Dialogue: 0,0:16:46.95,0:16:49.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,では　勝負
Dialogue: 0,0:16:51.97,0:16:53.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,逃げて　トンパさん
Dialogue: 0,0:16:59.66,0:17:00.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,まいった
Dialogue: 0,0:17:12.10,0:17:14.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ね　今まいったって
Dialogue: 0,0:17:15.14,0:17:16.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,まさか
Dialogue: 0,0:17:16.25,0:17:17.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,「待った」の間違いだろ
Dialogue: 0,0:17:18.50,0:17:21.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,あ　今　なんと
Dialogue: 0,0:17:23.38,0:17:24.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,降参です
Dialogue: 0,0:17:26.46,0:17:28.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,まいりました　オレの負けです
Dialogue: 0,0:17:33.27,0:17:37.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,全く息は付く攻撃だ　こら　笑える
Dialogue: 0,0:17:37.44,0:17:40.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,先鋒があれじゃ　後は知れたもんですな
Dialogue: 0,0:17:43.04,0:17:44.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,いやー　面目ない
Dialogue: 0,0:17:45.33,0:17:52.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,てめぇー　なんで様だ　改めてよーく分かったぜ
Dialogue: 0,0:17:53.33,0:17:55.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,テメェが他人の足を引っ張ってばかりの
Dialogue: 0,0:17:55.55,0:17:57.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,どうしようもない野郎だってな
Dialogue: 0,0:17:58.40,0:18:00.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我々が後二勝すればおまえ達の負けだ
Dialogue: 0,0:18:01.83,0:18:06.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,先にも後に行けず　時間切れまでここで過ごす事になる
Dialogue: 0,0:18:07.23,0:18:10.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,勝つには私達四人で三勝しなければならない
Dialogue: 0,0:18:11.62,0:18:13.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,やってくれるじゃん　オッサン
Dialogue: 0,0:18:22.50,0:18:24.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ああ　オレは卑劣なヤツさ
Dialogue: 0,0:18:25.14,0:18:26.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,オレはずーっとそうして来た
Dialogue: 0,0:18:27.56,0:18:28.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,そして　これからもな
Dialogue: 0,0:18:29.87,0:18:30.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,何だと
Dialogue: 0,0:18:31.36,0:18:34.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,だからこそ今まで生き残って来れたんだ
Dialogue: 0,0:18:34.91,0:18:36.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,いいか　よく聞きな
Dialogue: 0,0:18:36.97,0:18:39.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,オレはな　お前らと違って
Dialogue: 0,0:18:40.36,0:18:41.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ハンターになる気なんか
Dialogue: 0,0:18:42.30,0:18:44.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,これっぱかしもないんだよ
Dialogue: 0,0:18:47.02,0:18:49.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,オレがハンター試験に求めているのは
Dialogue: 0,0:18:49.63,0:18:52.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,合格じゃない　ほど良い刺激さ
Dialogue: 0,0:18:53.60,0:18:57.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,常にベテラン側にいて　彼らの動きに目を配り
Dialogue: 0,0:18:57.77,0:19:01.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,危険を察する感覚を磨けば　自分の安全は確保できる
Dialogue: 0,0:19:03.20,0:19:05.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,自分の命は堅守しながら　すぐ側で
Dialogue: 0,0:19:06.34,0:19:09.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,死の瞬間を見物できるしょう
Dialogue: 0,0:19:12.00,0:19:16.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夢多い前途ある若者が食いつぶされていく修羅の場
Dialogue: 0,0:19:18.47,0:19:22.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,野心や希望が永遠に絶たれる一瞬な表情
Dialogue: 0,0:19:23.10,0:19:26.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,次第にそれを見るのがなによりの楽しみとなった
Dialogue: 0,0:19:26.88,0:19:31.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,オレ自身が積極的に加担して新人の夢を摘み取ったんだ
Dialogue: 0,0:19:31.79,0:19:35.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ハンターになるよりも素晴らしい生き甲斐を見つけちまったのさ
Dialogue: 0,0:19:43.09,0:19:47.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今回の試験もオレにしてみれば　ここら辺が潮時なのさ
Dialogue: 0,0:19:48.11,0:19:52.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,第三次試験からは人数も少なくなり　反面　危険は大きくなる
Dialogue: 0,0:19:53.52,0:19:54.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,もう無理はしねぇ
Dialogue: 0,0:19:55.69,0:19:59.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,つまり　オレはもう何時負けたって構わないんだよ
Dialogue: 0,0:20:00.24,0:20:02.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,だが　ここは多数決の道
Dialogue: 0,0:20:03.02,0:20:06.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,おまえ達四人が頑張れば　四対一で勝ち進める
Dialogue: 0,0:20:08.49,0:20:10.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,そう捨てたもんじゃないだろ
Dialogue: 0,0:20:10.86,0:20:11.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ひどいものだな
Dialogue: 0,0:20:12.49,0:20:17.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,テメェー　覚えとけよ　必ず下まで連れて行く
Dialogue: 0,0:20:17.45,0:20:19.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ボコボコにしてやるためにな
Dialogue: 0,0:20:19.90,0:20:22.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,オッサン　あんたまるでバグだぜ
Dialogue: 0,0:20:24.30,0:20:26.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,オレバグルゲーム嫌いなんだ
Dialogue: 0,0:20:27.44,0:20:31.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,おい　そんな事したら　そく失格に
Dialogue: 0,0:20:31.77,0:20:32.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,構わない
Dialogue: 0,0:20:32.83,0:20:33.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,そうか
Dialogue: 0,0:20:34.27,0:20:36.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,そうだよ　トンパさんの言う通りだ
Dialogue: 0,0:20:37.28,0:20:39.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,四対一なら勝ち進めるじゃん
Dialogue: 0,0:20:39.60,0:20:43.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,仲間割るしなくても勝てるんだ　ね　クラピカそうでしょう
Dialogue: 0,0:20:43.71,0:20:44.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,確かにそうだが
Dialogue: 0,0:20:45.69,0:20:47.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,お前　オレより単純な
Dialogue: 0,0:20:49.58,0:20:51.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ゴンに感謝しな　オッサン
Dialogue: 0,0:20:53.67,0:20:56.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ぼちぼちのようだが　セドカン二番手はお前だ
Dialogue: 0,0:20:57.44,0:20:58.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所長　ロックを
Dialogue: 0,0:21:07.89,0:21:10.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,向こうの二番手が出てきたぜ　こっちはどうする
Dialogue: 0,0:21:12.34,0:21:14.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,はーい　オレが行くよ
Dialogue: 0,0:21:14.75,0:21:15.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,本当に大丈夫か
Dialogue: 0,0:21:16.19,0:21:17.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大丈夫　任せて
Dialogue: 0,0:21:19.98,0:21:22.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,オレ達きっと勝ってるよ　大丈夫
Dialogue: 0,0:21:25.12,0:21:27.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,さあ　二回戦　LET’S BEGIN
Dialogue: 0,0:21:33.43,0:21:34.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,次はオレだからね
Dialogue: 0,0:21:34.90,0:21:37.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,向こうは何だか弱そうだし　心配しないでよ
Dialogue: 0,0:21:38.84,0:21:40.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,次回　ハンターハンター
Dialogue: 0,0:21:40.28,0:21:42.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ローソク　ポリシー　　仲間割れ
Dialogue: 0,0:21:42.40,0:21:44.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ローソク勝負に風が吹く
Dialogue: 0,0:01:07.04,0:01:10.20,1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这里是第三次考试的考场陷阱塔
Dialogue: 0,0:01:11.63,0:01:12.69,1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,规则很简单
Dialogue: 0,0:01:12.88,0:01:14.44,1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只要活着走到塔底就行
Dialogue: 0,0:01:15.02,0:01:16.72,1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要求要是不超过72小时
Dialogue: 0,0:01:17.34,0:01:18.74,1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么就开始吧
Dialogue: 0,0:01:19.84,0:01:20.53,1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,三天啊
Dialogue: 0,0:01:21.52,0:01:23.45,1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只要走下这座塔就要三天的话
Dialogue: 0,0:01:24.15,0:01:26.23,1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一定有许多障碍
Dialogue: 0,0:01:27.34,0:01:29.71,1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看来绝对比第二次考试要难
Dialogue: 0,0:01:30.13,0:01:31.17,1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,绝对不能掉以轻心
Dialogue: 0,0:01:43.56,0:01:44.66,1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,开始考试
Dialogue: 0,0:01:46.19,0:01:50.81,1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,赞成 反对 陷阱
Dialogue: 0,0:01:51.46,0:01:52.34,1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么办
Dialogue: 0,0:01:52.85,0:01:54.77,1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,四面没有一扇窗户
Dialogue: 0,0:01:55.16,0:01:56.58,1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 只是墙壁而已
Dialogue: 0,0:01:57.38,0:01:59.37,1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,从这里下去简直是自杀行为
Dialogue: 0,0:02:00.08,0:02:01.78,1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那只是对普通人而言
Dialogue: 0,0:02:04.18,0:02:06.70,1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是 对于一流的攀岩达人而言
Dialogue: 0,0:02:07.57,0:02:09.04,1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只要有这样的大小的缝隙
Dialogue: 0,0:02:09.34,0:02:10.46,1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就可以轻而易举地做到
Dialogue: 0,0:02:10.86,0:02:12.40,1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哇  好厉害
Dialogue: 0,0:02:12.71,0:02:14.01,1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,已经爬到哪里了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:02:14.59,0:02:16.81,1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,光是看着就觉得头皮发麻
Dialogue: 0,0:02:21.27,0:02:21.90,1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是
Dialogue: 0,0:02:23.74,0:02:26.02,1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看来第三次考试第一个合格的人
Dialogue: 0,0:02:26.26,0:02:27.55,1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,非我莫属了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:40.40,0:02:42.83,1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看样子还是不要从外墙爬了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:43.41,0:02:46.31,1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我觉得 一定有通往下面的暗门
Dialogue: 0,0:02:49.02,0:02:51.20,1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看来大家想的都一样
Dialogue: 0,0:02:51.85,0:02:55.47,1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们也不能浪费时间 分头去找暗门吧
Dialogue: 0,0:03:19.98,0:03:22.10,1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,人数减少了 神马
Dialogue: 0,0:03:24.10,0:03:29.64,1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,五   十   十五     二十 只剩二十三个人了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:30.25,0:03:31.11,1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,才过了一会就只剩这么点了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:31.46,0:03:33.62,1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大概半数以上的人已经找到暗门
Dialogue: 0,0:03:34.20,0:03:36.22,1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,到下面去了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:38.22,0:03:41.67,1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所有人不可能都是进入的同一个暗门
Dialogue: 0,0:03:43.71,0:03:47.51,1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只可能是这里藏着很多暗门
Dialogue: 0,0:03:48.30,0:03:50.15,1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,雷欧力  酷拉皮卡
Dialogue: 0,0:03:51.96,0:03:52.80,1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你找到了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:03:53.31,0:03:54.54,1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,干得好啊  小杰
Dialogue: 0,0:03:54.99,0:03:57.19,1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,监狱长 居然还有两个小鬼
Dialogue: 0,0:03:58.27,0:03:59.31,1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,运气不错嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:03:59.72,0:04:02.10,1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,猎人考试可没那么简单
Dialogue: 0,0:04:02.42,0:04:03.66,1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好 那就要打开了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:08.07,0:04:09.66,1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是怎么回事
Dialogue: 0,0:04:10.79,0:04:12.23,1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个暗门自己锁上了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:12.87,0:04:14.44,1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也就是 已经有人从这扇门走过了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:14.93,0:04:16.52,1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们只能寻找其他的暗门了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:16.86,0:04:18.88,1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,切   一个暗门只能进一个人
Dialogue: 0,0:04:19.15,0:04:21.15,1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只要有人用过一会就锁上了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:22.49,0:04:26.16,1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且可能每个暗门下去之后有不同的路
Dialogue: 0,0:04:26.60,0:04:29.30,1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在还能冷静的分析吗
Dialogue: 0,0:04:29.57,0:04:32.53,1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还不知道这些暗门够不够所有人都下去呢
Dialogue: 0,0:04:32.90,0:04:33.37,1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有的啊
Dialogue: 0,0:04:34.41,0:04:36.29,1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有什么  暗门吗
Dialogue: 0,0:04:36.53,0:04:39.93,1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 我找到了6个 我们四个用还有多的
Dialogue: 0,0:04:40.30,0:04:43.19,1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,答对了 你们各就各位
Dialogue: 0,0:04:43.41,0:04:44.12,1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是
Dialogue: 0,0:04:47.08,0:04:52.24,1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,囚犯们消磨考生一个小时即可免去一年刑期
Dialogue: 0,0:04:52.45,0:04:54.73,1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这可是他们梦寐以求的大好事
Dialogue: 0,0:04:55.07,0:04:57.83,1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好好感谢我吧
Dialogue: 0,0:04:58.81,0:05:01.71,1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这里和这里 还有这里还有三个
Dialogue: 0,0:05:02.45,0:05:04.44,1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这么小的范围里就有5个
Dialogue: 0,0:05:05.05,0:05:07.05,1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,总觉得很可疑
Dialogue: 0,0:05:07.46,0:05:09.74,1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这些里头可能有陷阱
Dialogue: 0,0:05:11.55,0:05:13.71,1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这要看个人的运气和实力了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:14.80,0:05:16.63,1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不管谁掉到陷阱里都不可以有怨言哦
Dialogue: 0,0:05:16.79,0:05:17.67,1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有没有
Dialogue: 0,0:05:18.17,0:05:20.27,1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么就先来决定一下每个人选择暗门的顺序
Dialogue: 0,0:05:21.31,0:05:23.10,1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,石头 剪刀  布
Dialogue: 0,0:05:24.95,0:05:27.65,1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,数着1 2 3 大家一起下去
Dialogue: 0,0:05:28.72,0:05:30.09,1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大家在这里暂时分手
Dialogue: 0,0:05:31.25,0:05:32.55,1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在地面再见了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:33.18,0:05:33.80,1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:05:34.58,0:05:35.71,1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么 走吧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:36.39,0:05:38.99,1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,1 2 3
Dialogue: 0,0:06:04.27,0:06:05.61,1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是短暂的分别啊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:06.04,0:06:06.89,1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的
Dialogue: 0,0:06:07.44,0:06:09.29,1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个房间也没有出口
Dialogue: 0,0:06:09.58,0:06:11.14,1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不会又是暗门吧
Dialogue: 0,0:06:11.84,0:06:12.71,1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好像有什么字
Dialogue: 0,0:06:17.07,0:06:18.50,1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,多数表决之路
Dialogue: 0,0:06:19.29,0:06:22.74,1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们5个人  从这里开始一直到结束
Dialogue: 0,0:06:22.94,0:06:25.29,1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都要必须按照多数表决的规定
Dialogue: 0,0:06:26.83,0:06:27.73,1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,多数表决
Dialogue: 0,0:06:27.99,0:06:28.64,1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个是
Dialogue: 0,0:06:29.42,0:06:30.38,1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是计时器吧
Dialogue: 0,0:06:30.90,0:06:32.60,1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,上面还有圈圈和叉叉的按钮
Dialogue: 0,0:06:34.00,0:06:35.44,1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,恐怕我们还要在等一个人
Dialogue: 0,0:06:36.73,0:06:38.83,1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要是没有人从这个暗门下来的话
Dialogue: 0,0:06:40.03,0:06:42.43,1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们就没法从这里出去了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:06:43.20,0:06:44.19,1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是这样
Dialogue: 0,0:06:45.02,0:06:48.18,1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这座塔里预设了许多不同的路径
Dialogue: 0,0:06:48.69,0:06:51.58,1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,每一条路的过关条件都不同
Dialogue: 0,0:06:52.17,0:06:55.82,1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们选择的是多数表决之路
Dialogue: 0,0:06:56.42,0:07:00.20,1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是一个需要同心协力才能通过的难关
Dialogue: 0,0:07:00.61,0:07:03.06,1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么 就祝你们好运
Dialogue: 0,0:07:06.11,0:07:10.99,1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还剩下71小时18分 我们只能等了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:34.75,0:07:35.88,1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,已经过了两个小时了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:36.56,0:07:40.21,1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,会不会所有人都从别的路上走了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:07:41.18,0:07:45.22,1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在还留在顶上的都是白痴了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:07:46.60,0:07:48.45,1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好像那个白痴来了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:52.70,0:07:53.78,1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,居然是你
Dialogue: 0,0:07:54.21,0:07:54.88,1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,东巴先生
Dialogue: 0,0:07:56.21,0:07:57.54,1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们都在这里啊
Dialogue: 0,0:07:59.37,0:08:02.84,1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和你这种人玩多数表决 我才不要呢
Dialogue: 0,0:08:06.31,0:08:08.02,1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样就好了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:10.12,0:08:11.55,1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好嘞 走吧
Dialogue: 0,0:08:12.51,0:08:14.73,1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好个毛啊  最后才慢吞吞的过来
Dialogue: 0,0:08:15.18,0:08:16.17,1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,神奇什么
Dialogue: 0,0:08:19.83,0:08:20.98,1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,第一道选择
Dialogue: 0,0:08:21.48,0:08:23.18,1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想打开这座门的就按圈圈
Dialogue: 0,0:08:23.44,0:08:25.71,1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不想打开的就按叉叉
Dialogue: 0,0:08:26.21,0:08:27.79,1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这里就要开始多数表决了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:08:28.27,0:08:30.12,1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这种问题答案是肯定的
Dialogue: 0,0:08:34.71,0:08:35.35,1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咦
Dialogue: 0,0:08:35.91,0:08:38.02,1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谁按了叉叉的按钮
Dialogue: 0,0:08:38.43,0:08:41.93,1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,呃 抱歉抱歉 我一不小心按错了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:42.23,0:08:44.23,1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂 大叔 别乱搞
Dialogue: 0,0:08:44.59,0:08:47.62,1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么可能把圈和叉弄错呢
Dialogue: 0,0:08:48.19,0:08:49.85,1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是我已经道过谦了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:50.03,0:08:52.08,1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我在问你为毛会弄错按钮
Dialogue: 0,0:08:52.36,0:08:55.11,1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了 别吵了 走吧 反正门已经打开了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:55.28,0:08:58.58,1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不 不行 这家伙一定是估计按叉的
Dialogue: 0,0:08:58.82,0:09:02.56,1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们已经浪费了两小时了 争吵更是浪费时间
Dialogue: 0,0:09:03.70,0:09:07.50,1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没错 就算这家伙一直和我们作对
Dialogue: 0,0:09:08.12,0:09:10.24,1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们4个团结就没问题
Dialogue: 0,0:09:11.22,0:09:12.79,1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还是有人想要扯后腿
Dialogue: 0,0:09:15.69,0:09:18.82,1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧 我知道了 大家快走吧
Dialogue: 0,0:09:19.79,0:09:22.97,1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过 如果你还做这种事的话 我就揍死你
Dialogue: 0,0:09:35.66,0:09:36.47,1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,又来了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:37.29,0:09:40.48,1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想往右边走的安全 左边的话按叉
Dialogue: 0,0:09:41.52,0:09:42.28,1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的好的
Dialogue: 0,0:09:44.65,0:09:48.29,1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,居然是右边 一种情况一般都是走左边的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:09:49.02,0:09:51.76,1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且 这种情况我不走左边的话
Dialogue: 0,0:09:51.87,0:09:53.61,1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,总觉得不对劲
Dialogue: 0,0:09:55.67,0:09:57.60,1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,的确 从人类行动学来说
Dialogue: 0,0:09:58.47,0:10:01.19,1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,人在不知道都那条路的时候
Dialogue: 0,0:10:01.31,0:10:04.46,1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大多数会下意识的选择左边的路
Dialogue: 0,0:10:05.16,0:10:06.52,1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也听过这个理论
Dialogue: 0,0:10:07.23,0:10:09.54,1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不对啊 这样的话结果就不对了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:09.79,0:10:11.05,1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们选的哪条路
Dialogue: 0,0:10:11.98,0:10:13.16,1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,右边 右边
Dialogue: 0,0:10:13.68,0:10:15.04,1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们两个啊
Dialogue: 0,0:10:15.65,0:10:18.37,1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是因为大多数人选左边  才会选右边的
Dialogue: 0,0:10:18.79,0:10:21.23,1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,考官一定知道这个法则
Dialogue: 0,0:10:21.50,0:10:24.71,1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,左边的题目可能会很难
Dialogue: 0,0:10:25.05,0:10:25.93,1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是这样
Dialogue: 0,0:10:26.29,0:10:29.64,1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,反正我们就比较单纯 是吧 小杰
Dialogue: 0,0:10:31.27,0:10:34.62,1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,原来的真的是和雷欧力同等级的人
Dialogue: 0,0:10:47.23,0:10:49.12,1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,天啊 这是什么
Dialogue: 0,0:11:04.84,0:11:05.63,1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们看那边
Dialogue: 0,0:11:09.72,0:11:12.39,1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,理伯监狱长 考生来了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:12.86,0:11:14.22,1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,帮我把手铐拿掉吧
Dialogue: 0,0:11:22.86,0:11:27.26,1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们是为了测试你们而来的人
Dialogue: 0,0:11:27.60,0:11:31.43,1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们想要过关 就一定要和我们战斗
Dialogue: 0,0:11:32.62,0:11:34.01,1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个人好像很强
Dialogue: 0,0:11:34.66,0:11:36.87,1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以我才说应该选左边的路
Dialogue: 0,0:11:37.42,0:11:39.67,1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说不定左边的更难
Dialogue: 0,0:11:40.23,0:11:43.51,1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,比试是一对一的方式 一局定胜负
Dialogue: 0,0:11:44.07,0:11:47.66,1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,顺序自由决定 你们要按照多数决的原则
Dialogue: 0,0:11:48.18,0:11:51.26,1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以 只要赢过三场就可以通关
Dialogue: 0,0:11:51.82,0:11:54.89,1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,自己决定打斗方式 没有平手
Dialogue: 0,0:11:55.41,0:11:57.83,1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只要其中一方已经认输了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:58.12,0:12:00.29,1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么另一方就赢得那一局
Dialogue: 0,0:12:02.30,0:12:05.10,1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在请决定是否要接受这场比赛
Dialogue: 0,0:12:05.48,0:12:08.84,1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,接受就按圈  不接受就按叉
Dialogue: 0,0:12:09.10,0:12:12.57,1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,又要表决 简直是浪费时间
Dialogue: 0,0:12:13.07,0:12:16.69,1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,反正为了合格 我们非得接受这场对决
Dialogue: 0,0:12:17.12,0:12:18.81,1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,每个人肯定都会按圈了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:19.95,0:12:23.24,1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只要没有那个蠢货来搅局
Dialogue: 0,0:12:25.15,0:12:27.43,1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了好了 我知道了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:29.77,0:12:31.43,1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么样 所有人都一致了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:31.77,0:12:34.80,1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很好 我们这边我第一个上
Dialogue: 0,0:12:35.31,0:12:36.53,1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们那边谁来
Dialogue: 0,0:12:37.51,0:12:39.36,1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么办  由谁上
Dialogue: 0,0:12:41.45,0:12:44.80,1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,已经完成设定了 还有69个小时
Dialogue: 0,0:12:45.26,0:12:48.14,1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们已经确定免去3年的刑期了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:48.70,0:12:50.77,1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了 那我们来欣赏一下他们的比赛吧
Dialogue: 0,0:12:51.44,0:12:52.46,1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那就我去好了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:53.19,0:12:54.43,1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行 我去吧
Dialogue: 0,0:12:55.59,0:12:58.50,1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看起来 那个家伙是想靠臂力来打赢这一局
Dialogue: 0,0:12:58.93,0:13:01.01,1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要是硬碰硬的话 对小杰你不利
Dialogue: 0,0:13:01.41,0:13:04.67,1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等等 小杰不行的话 你也很勉强吧
Dialogue: 0,0:13:05.23,0:13:07.01,1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是我有武器
Dialogue: 0,0:13:07.40,0:13:09.78,1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要是被对方抢去了 你不就输了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:10.23,0:13:11.47,1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么 你去吗
Dialogue: 0,0:13:15.62,0:13:17.72,1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那家伙的肌肉像钢筋一样
Dialogue: 0,0:13:18.46,0:13:19.98,1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你要是害怕的话 我上好了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:20.42,0:13:21.05,1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,奇犽
Dialogue: 0,0:13:21.41,0:13:23.24,1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就这样吧 等等
Dialogue: 0,0:13:24.94,0:13:25.75,1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让我去吧
Dialogue: 0,0:13:28.87,0:13:29.37,1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别瞎说了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:30.10,0:13:32.73,1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,像你这种只会玩阴的的人根本不是他的对手
Dialogue: 0,0:13:33.76,0:13:34.92,1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那可不一定
Dialogue: 0,0:13:35.99,0:13:39.57,1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,既然搏斗方式自由 那我就有自己的办法
Dialogue: 0,0:13:40.34,0:13:42.70,1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们也不知道对方会出什么花招
Dialogue: 0,0:13:43.27,0:13:44.77,1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然他看起来很强壮
Dialogue: 0,0:13:44.88,0:13:47.20,1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也不能肯定他就是一个靠力气取胜的人
Dialogue: 0,0:13:47.90,0:13:51.06,1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也就是说 现在最重要的  不是臂力
Dialogue: 0,0:13:51.54,0:13:54.69,1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而是不管遇到什么都能够应对的经验和直觉
Dialogue: 0,0:13:55.23,0:13:58.23,1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让我来试一试 探一探对方的底细
Dialogue: 0,0:14:01.27,0:14:04.93,1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也算是 我对过去的事情的弥补 就是这样
Dialogue: 0,0:14:05.32,0:14:07.11,1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在还有谁相信你
Dialogue: 0,0:14:08.39,0:14:09.41,1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我觉得也是
Dialogue: 0,0:14:09.70,0:14:12.15,1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,其实我自愿的前锋最大的原因是
Dialogue: 0,0:14:13.07,0:14:16.47,1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们到现在还是完全不相信我的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:14:16.85,0:14:18.40,1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不只是现在
Dialogue: 0,0:14:18.89,0:14:19.76,1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那我就问你们了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:20.16,0:14:21.46,1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说不定到最后
Dialogue: 0,0:14:21.67,0:14:24.10,1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就变成两胜两负的局面
Dialogue: 0,0:14:24.64,0:14:26.77,1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那时候 你们会把希望寄托在
Dialogue: 0,0:14:26.90,0:14:29.16,1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,完全不被信任的我的身上吗
Dialogue: 0,0:14:33.92,0:14:35.06,1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那就让他试试吧
Dialogue: 0,0:14:35.51,0:14:38.11,1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大叔说的也有道理
Dialogue: 0,0:14:39.35,0:14:41.33,1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那就这样决定吧
Dialogue: 0,0:14:47.41,0:14:50.40,1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,既然做了前锋 那就不许失败
Dialogue: 0,0:14:50.83,0:14:54.06,1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那就等着瞧吧 第一个上场的是我
Dialogue: 0,0:14:54.86,0:14:55.73,1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好
Dialogue: 0,0:15:14.06,0:15:16.74,1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么 我们就先决定如何定输赢
Dialogue: 0,0:15:17.32,0:15:20.02,1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我提议使用生死决斗
Dialogue: 0,0:15:23.21,0:15:25.88,1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这下惨了 酷拉皮卡 怎么办啊
Dialogue: 0,0:15:26.18,0:15:28.39,1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,遭了  被他看出了我们的企图
Dialogue: 0,0:15:28.94,0:15:31.48,1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可是东巴先生好像很有自信的样子
Dialogue: 0,0:15:32.05,0:15:34.14,1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一定有很好的作战计划
Dialogue: 0,0:15:34.44,0:15:35.45,1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看了就知道了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:37.86,0:15:41.63,1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,知道一方认输 或者死亡的时候比赛才结束
Dialogue: 0,0:15:42.55,0:15:43.54,1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如何
Dialogue: 0,0:15:47.27,0:15:49.64,1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这家伙好像不敢回答
Dialogue: 0,0:15:50.44,0:15:52.55,1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对于囚犯来说这是最好的方式
Dialogue: 0,0:15:54.25,0:15:58.26,1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一点没错 那些家伙的刑期都在一百年以上
Dialogue: 0,0:15:59.15,0:16:01.62,1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊 全是重刑犯
Dialogue: 0,0:16:02.10,0:16:04.96,1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不这样做来拖延时间的话 怎么能减刑呢
Dialogue: 0,0:16:05.30,0:16:09.30,1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,蝙都特犯下的是强盗杀人  刑期是199年
Dialogue: 0,0:16:09.98,0:16:12.18,1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他一定会好好利用这个机会
Dialogue: 0,0:16:13.09,0:16:16.84,1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可以公然杀人泄愤 而且 还能够减刑
Dialogue: 0,0:16:17.71,0:16:21.02,1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了 你到底要不要接受这个生死决斗
Dialogue: 0,0:16:21.56,0:16:23.36,1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你再慢吞吞的犹豫下去
Dialogue: 0,0:16:23.82,0:16:26.56,1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,同伴的时间也会消耗掉哦
Dialogue: 0,0:16:28.20,0:16:31.31,1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过相对的我们的刑期就会减少
Dialogue: 0,0:16:31.59,0:16:32.98,1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我可求之不得
Dialogue: 0,0:16:34.54,0:16:37.14,1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧  我接受你的挑战
Dialogue: 0,0:16:37.60,0:16:38.25,1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,东巴
Dialogue: 0,0:16:40.07,0:16:41.02,1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,东巴先生
Dialogue: 0,0:16:42.16,0:16:44.24,1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,做这个决定  算你爽快
Dialogue: 0,0:16:46.95,0:16:49.33,1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么 接招吧
Dialogue: 0,0:16:51.97,0:16:53.46,1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快逃啊 东巴先生
Dialogue: 0,0:16:59.66,0:17:00.94,1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我认输
Dialogue: 0,0:17:12.10,0:17:14.23,1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,呐  刚刚是在说认输了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:17:15.14,0:17:16.01,1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不会吧
Dialogue: 0,0:17:16.25,0:17:17.94,1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他是想说【慢着】吧
Dialogue: 0,0:17:18.50,0:17:21.71,1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你  刚刚  说啥
Dialogue: 0,0:17:23.38,0:17:24.34,1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我投降
Dialogue: 0,0:17:26.46,0:17:28.90,1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不好意思 我输了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:33.27,0:17:37.06,1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是想不到的攻击啊
Dialogue: 0,0:17:37.44,0:17:40.54,1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,前锋就这样了 后面的估计好不到哪去
Dialogue: 0,0:17:43.04,0:17:44.61,1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊  真不好意思
Dialogue: 0,0:17:45.33,0:17:52.93,1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你什么人啊 我总算更了解你这混蛋了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:53.33,0:17:55.34,1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你这个家伙 只会拖人后腿
Dialogue: 0,0:17:55.55,0:17:57.10,1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,无可救药的混蛋
Dialogue: 0,0:17:58.40,0:18:00.98,1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只要我们再赢两场 你们就输了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:01.83,0:18:06.48,1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,会陷入进退不得的困境 眼看着时间结束
Dialogue: 0,0:18:07.23,0:18:10.50,1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们想要赢的话 需要我们四人赢三场才行
Dialogue: 0,0:18:11.62,0:18:13.57,1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,做的不错啊 大叔
Dialogue: 0,0:18:22.50,0:18:24.69,1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我就是个卑鄙小人
Dialogue: 0,0:18:25.14,0:18:26.86,1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我一直就是这样
Dialogue: 0,0:18:27.56,0:18:28.83,1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且  以后也不会变
Dialogue: 0,0:18:29.87,0:18:30.63,1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你说什么
Dialogue: 0,0:18:31.36,0:18:34.03,1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是因为这样我才能活到现在
Dialogue: 0,0:18:34.91,0:18:36.34,1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们给我听清楚了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:36.97,0:18:39.67,1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我和你们不一样
Dialogue: 0,0:18:40.36,0:18:41.99,1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,压根就不想当什么猎人
Dialogue: 0,0:18:42.30,0:18:44.82,1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一点都不想
Dialogue: 0,0:18:47.02,0:18:49.22,1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我之所以来参加猎人考试
Dialogue: 0,0:18:49.63,0:18:52.65,1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是想要合格 而是想要追求前所未有的刺激
Dialogue: 0,0:18:53.60,0:18:57.40,1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在全是高手环绕的环境下 观察他们的举动
Dialogue: 0,0:18:57.77,0:19:01.98,1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后练就察觉危险的本领 好确保自己的安全
Dialogue: 0,0:19:03.20,0:19:05.97,1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样一方面可以保护自己的生命
Dialogue: 0,0:19:06.34,0:19:09.55,1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还可以欣赏死亡瞬间
Dialogue: 0,0:19:12.00,0:19:16.73,1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有梦有前途的年轻人一个个被毁灭
Dialogue: 0,0:19:18.47,0:19:22.34,1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,野心和希望永远的破灭的那一瞬间的表情
Dialogue: 0,0:19:23.10,0:19:26.40,1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,渐渐的欣赏这些就变成了我人生最大的乐趣
Dialogue: 0,0:19:26.88,0:19:31.19,1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也开始积极参与 亲手摧毁新人的梦想
Dialogue: 0,0:19:31.79,0:19:35.52,1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,比起当上猎人我找到了更有意义的人生目标
Dialogue: 0,0:19:43.09,0:19:47.18,1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这次的猎人考试对于我来说也该完结了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:48.11,0:19:52.73,1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,从第三次考试开始人数减少 危险增大
Dialogue: 0,0:19:53.52,0:19:54.96,1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这也难怪
Dialogue: 0,0:19:55.69,0:19:59.16,1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也就是说 我随便什么时候退出都没问题
Dialogue: 0,0:20:00.24,0:20:02.28,1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可是 这是多数表决之路
Dialogue: 0,0:20:03.02,0:20:06.92,1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们4个人努力的话 就能以4对1继续前进
Dialogue: 0,0:20:08.49,0:20:10.35,1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还是可能成功的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:20:10.86,0:20:11.99,1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你真是太过分了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:12.49,0:20:17.03,1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,混蛋 你给我记住 我一定要拉你走到塔底
Dialogue: 0,0:20:17.45,0:20:19.38,1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让你最后死的很惨
Dialogue: 0,0:20:19.90,0:20:22.26,1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大叔 你真是害群之马啊
Dialogue: 0,0:20:24.30,0:20:26.12,1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我最不喜欢玩抽鬼牌的游戏
Dialogue: 0,0:20:27.44,0:20:31.33,1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,杀了我的话 立刻就会失去考试资格的
Dialogue: 0,0:20:31.77,0:20:32.55,1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,无所谓
Dialogue: 0,0:20:32.83,0:20:33.58,1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:34.27,0:20:36.77,1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说的也是 东巴先生说的没错
Dialogue: 0,0:20:37.28,0:20:39.22,1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们4胜对1败的话还是有机会赢的
Dialogue: 0,0:20:39.60,0:20:43.34,1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们内部不打架也会赢 对吧 酷拉皮卡
Dialogue: 0,0:20:43.71,0:20:44.87,1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,话是这么说
Dialogue: 0,0:20:45.69,0:20:47.76,1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你比我还单纯啊
Dialogue: 0,0:20:49.58,0:20:51.66,1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要感谢小杰啊 大叔
Dialogue: 0,0:20:53.67,0:20:56.98,1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,时间用去不少了 赛托 你第二个出场
Dialogue: 0,0:20:57.44,0:20:58.57,1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,监狱长 把手铐打开
Dialogue: 0,0:21:07.89,0:21:10.56,1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对方已经确定了第二个了 我们这边咋办
Dialogue: 0,0:21:12.34,0:21:14.55,1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我来
Dialogue: 0,0:21:14.75,0:21:15.93,1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的没问题吗
Dialogue: 0,0:21:16.19,0:21:17.58,1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没事的 交给我吧
Dialogue: 0,0:21:19.98,0:21:22.61,1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们一定会赢得 别担心
Dialogue: 0,0:21:25.12,0:21:27.92,1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了 第二战 开始
Dialogue: 0,0:21:33.43,0:21:34.57,1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这次就是我了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:34.90,0:21:37.92,1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对方好像很弱 不用担心
Dialogue: 0,0:21:38.84,0:21:40.08,1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,下回  HunterXHunter
Dialogue: 0,0:21:40.28,0:21:42.10,1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,蜡烛  原则  分道扬镳
Dialogue: 0,0:21:42.40,0:21:44.16,1,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,用蜡烛定输赢时有风吹过


