[Script Info]
; // 此字幕由PopSub生成  2011-10-29 21:15:59
; // MESSAGE ERROR 0.75
; // popgo_fansub@yahoo.co.jp
; // 欢迎访问漫游天下 http://bbs.popgo.net
Title:漫游字幕
Original Script:漫游字幕组
Synch Point:0
ScriptType:v4.00+
Collisions:Normal
PlayResX:640
PlayResY:480
Timer:100.0000

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,MS Gothic,17,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&HF0000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,1,0,2,30,30,10,134
Style: china,方正卡通简体,31,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H01A600A6,&HF0000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,1,0,2,30,30,10,134
Style: staff,方正卡通简体,20,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&HF0000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,0,8,30,30,10,134

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Name, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:02:01.00,0:02:06.00,staff,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(1000,1000)}本字幕由天空树双语字幕组出品
Dialogue: 0,0:02:07.00,0:02:12.00,staff,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(1000,1000)}片源：小宁  中翻&日翻：小四 
Dialogue: 0,0:02:13.00,0:02:18.00,staff,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(1000,1000)}校对&间轴：可乐  压制：小四

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Actor, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:01:11.90,0:01:15.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,よっ　オレはトンパ　今年は１６番だ
Dialogue: 0,0:01:16.59,0:01:17.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ニコルと言います
Dialogue: 0,0:01:17.80,0:01:20.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ここだけの話　オレ忍者なんだよ
Dialogue: 0,0:01:22.89,0:01:23.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,気をつけようね
Dialogue: 0,0:01:24.18,0:01:26.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,人にぶつかったら　謝らなくちゃ
Dialogue: 0,0:01:27.61,0:01:30.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,では　これよりハンター試験を開始いたします
Dialogue: 0,0:01:34.73,0:01:36.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ね　君　名前なんって言うの
Dialogue: 0,0:01:41.97,0:01:42.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,レオリオ　おい
Dialogue: 0,0:01:44.10,0:01:45.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,おまえら　バカか
Dialogue: 0,0:01:45.86,0:01:47.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,そいつはもう終わりだ
Dialogue: 0,0:01:50.00,0:01:51.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,レオリオを　頼むよ
Dialogue: 0,0:01:55.83,0:01:57.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今助ける　一緒に来い
Dialogue: 0,0:01:57.83,0:01:59.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,オレ　様子見てくる
Dialogue: 0,0:01:59.10,0:01:59.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一緒に行こう
Dialogue: 0,0:02:00.23,0:02:00.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,戻ってくるよ
Dialogue: 0,0:02:01.28,0:02:04.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,そうしたら　名前を教えてくれると嬉しいな
Dialogue: 0,0:02:05.12,0:02:06.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ここでしばらく休め
Dialogue: 0,0:02:06.55,0:02:09.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,そうすれば　おまえ達は確実に脱落するぜ
Dialogue: 0,0:02:09.93,0:02:10.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,なんだと
Dialogue: 0,0:02:10.67,0:02:11.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,じゃあな
Dialogue: 0,0:02:20.61,0:02:23.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,次に潰れるのは誰かな
Dialogue: 0,0:02:23.52,0:02:27.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,トラウア　限界　甘いワナ
Dialogue: 0,0:02:42.70,0:02:45.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,それでさ　その時オレは言ってやったのよ
Dialogue: 0,0:02:45.94,0:02:49.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,それぐらいで諦めるようじゃ　おまえも大した事ないなってさ
Dialogue: 0,0:02:50.79,0:02:52.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,まだかな　腹減ってきたよ
Dialogue: 0,0:02:53.11,0:02:53.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘘
Dialogue: 0,0:02:58.61,0:02:59.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,あれ
Dialogue: 0,0:03:02.09,0:03:03.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,トンパさん　どうしたの
Dialogue: 0,0:03:06.66,0:03:08.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,た　大変だ
Dialogue: 0,0:03:08.73,0:03:10.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,速く　２人を速く
Dialogue: 0,0:03:11.13,0:03:12.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,中で何あった
Dialogue: 0,0:03:12.53,0:03:16.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,こ　こんなワナは初めてだ　急げ
Dialogue: 0,0:03:35.04,0:03:39.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,言うな　オレは落後者なんかじゃない　やめてくれ
Dialogue: 0,0:03:41.10,0:03:43.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,こんなところでへばる奴　初めて見たぜ
Dialogue: 0,0:03:44.53,0:03:46.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,恥ずかしいヤローな
Dialogue: 0,0:03:46.84,0:03:47.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,言うな
Dialogue: 0,0:03:48.60,0:03:51.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,落第生よ　脱落者だな
Dialogue: 0,0:03:51.79,0:03:52.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,やめてくれ
Dialogue: 0,0:03:53.23,0:03:56.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,負け犬　落後者　不適格者
Dialogue: 0,0:03:57.39,0:04:00.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,表彰モンの能なしだぜ　テメーはよ
Dialogue: 0,0:04:00.31,0:04:00.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,脳なしよ
Dialogue: 0,0:04:01.43,0:04:02.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能なしだな
Dialogue: 0,0:04:02.85,0:04:06.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ハンター試験始まって以来の落ちこぼれだよ　おめぇは
Dialogue: 0,0:04:06.52,0:04:08.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,才能ねぇーんだよ　バーカ
Dialogue: 0,0:04:08.78,0:04:11.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,二度と来るな　人クズヤロー
Dialogue: 0,0:04:11.53,0:04:17.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,クズ　落第生　クズ　不適格者　脳なしだな
Dialogue: 0,0:04:27.31,0:04:28.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一体　どうなってる
Dialogue: 0,0:04:29.13,0:04:29.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,レオリオ
Dialogue: 0,0:04:38.64,0:04:41.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,助けてくれ　レオリオ
Dialogue: 0,0:04:41.62,0:04:43.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ピ　ピエトロ
Dialogue: 0,0:05:01.27,0:05:02.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ピ　ピエトロ
Dialogue: 0,0:05:07.71,0:05:10.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ニコル　どうしたの　何があったの
Dialogue: 0,0:05:21.16,0:05:22.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ニコルさん
Dialogue: 0,0:05:36.42,0:05:38.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,急ごう　レオリオを探すんだ
Dialogue: 0,0:05:42.71,0:05:44.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,おい　どこへ行くんだよ
Dialogue: 0,0:05:44.86,0:05:47.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,待って　待ってくれよ
Dialogue: 0,0:05:49.09,0:05:50.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,おい
Dialogue: 0,0:05:58.23,0:05:58.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ピエトロ
Dialogue: 0,0:06:10.40,0:06:12.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ピエ　トロ
Dialogue: 0,0:06:14.15,0:06:17.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,レオリオ　来てくれたのか
Dialogue: 0,0:06:20.33,0:06:22.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,だが　遅かったよ
Dialogue: 0,0:06:23.28,0:06:26.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,オレはこの通り不様に死んじまった
Dialogue: 0,0:06:27.62,0:06:30.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,オレの心臓はもう脈打つ事はない
Dialogue: 0,0:06:31.88,0:06:34.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,この体はただの冷えた骸だ
Dialogue: 0,0:06:36.52,0:06:39.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,レオリオ　おまえは医者の賜だろ
Dialogue: 0,0:06:41.00,0:06:45.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,助けてくれよ　治してくれよ　レオリオ
Dialogue: 0,0:06:52.57,0:06:55.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,レオリオ　返事して　リオリオ
Dialogue: 0,0:06:57.71,0:06:58.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,どうしたの
Dialogue: 0,0:07:10.73,0:07:12.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,幻影旅団
Dialogue: 0,0:07:14.54,0:07:15.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,クラピカ
Dialogue: 0,0:07:17.13,0:07:17.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,やめろ
Dialogue: 0,0:07:19.21,0:07:20.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,やめてくれ
Dialogue: 0,0:07:23.36,0:07:26.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,クラピカ　ね　クラピカっては
Dialogue: 0,0:07:38.44,0:07:39.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,クラピカ
Dialogue: 0,0:07:41.89,0:07:43.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ね　どうしちゃったの
Dialogue: 0,0:07:45.27,0:07:49.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,や―めろ　や―め
Dialogue: 0,0:07:51.12,0:07:51.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,クラピカ
Dialogue: 0,0:08:12.96,0:08:14.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,クラピカ　しっかりして
Dialogue: 0,0:08:17.84,0:08:20.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,レオリオ　今行くからね
Dialogue: 0,0:08:32.82,0:08:34.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,何怯えてんだよ
Dialogue: 0,0:08:34.59,0:08:36.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,い　いや　別に
Dialogue: 0,0:08:37.38,0:08:40.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,おまえ　引っ掛けたな
Dialogue: 0,0:08:40.47,0:08:41.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,な　何を　バカな
Dialogue: 0,0:08:43.45,0:08:44.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,いい事を教えてやるよ
Dialogue: 0,0:08:48.20,0:08:49.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,薄汚い手を使う奴に
Dialogue: 0,0:08:50.29,0:08:53.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,いつか必ず薄汚い死に方をするってさ
Dialogue: 0,0:08:54.42,0:08:57.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘘じゃないぜ　なんなら試してみようか
Dialogue: 0,0:08:57.95,0:09:01.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今　ここで
Dialogue: 0,0:09:14.33,0:09:15.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ガキな
Dialogue: 0,0:09:19.58,0:09:21.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,起きたか　レオリオ
Dialogue: 0,0:09:22.02,0:09:24.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ああ　ピエトロ　すまん
Dialogue: 0,0:09:25.40,0:09:26.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,オレは治したかったんけど
Dialogue: 0,0:09:27.30,0:09:31.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,おまえを手術してやれる金がなかったんだ
Dialogue: 0,0:09:32.09,0:09:33.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ああ　わかってる
Dialogue: 0,0:09:34.50,0:09:38.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,それに　手術するには本物の医者にならなくちゃならねぇ
Dialogue: 0,0:09:39.77,0:09:42.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,それにやもっともっと金が必要だったんだ
Dialogue: 0,0:09:42.98,0:09:45.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,チクショウ　金さえあれや
Dialogue: 0,0:09:45.62,0:09:47.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,あん時　金さえあれや
Dialogue: 0,0:09:48.74,0:09:51.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,オレ　ハンターになって　金を稼いで
Dialogue: 0,0:09:51.60,0:09:53.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,その金で医者になるつもりだ
Dialogue: 0,0:09:54.68,0:09:57.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,そして　おまえみてぇな病気にかかった奴を
Dialogue: 0,0:09:57.70,0:09:59.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,片っ端から治してやりてぇー
Dialogue: 0,0:10:00.08,0:10:00.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,だから
Dialogue: 0,0:10:12.01,0:10:12.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,クラピカ
Dialogue: 0,0:10:14.92,0:10:17.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,クラピカ　クラピカ
Dialogue: 0,0:10:35.00,0:10:35.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,クラピカ
Dialogue: 0,0:10:36.80,0:10:37.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ゴン
Dialogue: 0,0:10:37.71,0:10:39.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,よかった　気がついたんだね
Dialogue: 0,0:10:40.29,0:10:40.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,えーと
Dialogue: 0,0:10:41.76,0:10:43.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,癒し杉なんて木はない
Dialogue: 0,0:10:45.20,0:10:49.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,こいつは昔から暗殺者がよく使う惑わす杉の樹液だ
Dialogue: 0,0:10:50.22,0:10:53.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,相手の一番触れられたくない過去の幻を見せて
Dialogue: 0,0:10:53.36,0:10:54.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,精神を破壊するんだ
Dialogue: 0,0:10:55.37,0:10:56.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,詳しんだね
Dialogue: 0,0:10:56.89,0:10:58.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,じゃ　トンパは
Dialogue: 0,0:10:59.16,0:11:01.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,おまえ達を引っ掛けたんだ
Dialogue: 0,0:11:02.97,0:11:03.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,行かなきゃ
Dialogue: 0,0:11:04.03,0:11:06.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,あえるぜ　あのおっさんを助けて
Dialogue: 0,0:11:06.35,0:11:09.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,しかも　一発逆転で先頭集団に追いつく方法
Dialogue: 0,0:11:10.76,0:11:12.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ゲームは単純じゃつまんないだろう
Dialogue: 0,0:11:13.32,0:11:16.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,もう一度会えたね　名前　教えてくれる
Dialogue: 0,0:11:18.62,0:11:19.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,キルア
Dialogue: 0,0:11:39.37,0:11:40.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,もうダメだ
Dialogue: 0,0:11:43.47,0:11:46.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,アレマン　お気の毒に　バイバイ
Dialogue: 0,0:11:51.28,0:11:52.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,キルア
Dialogue: 0,0:11:53.96,0:11:56.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ね　キルア　どうすればいいの
Dialogue: 0,0:11:58.77,0:12:00.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爆弾　けっこうすごい奴
Dialogue: 0,0:12:01.16,0:12:02.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爆弾
Dialogue: 0,0:12:02.46,0:12:06.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,打っ飛ばすのさ　この樹液べったりの気持ち悪い壁を
Dialogue: 0,0:12:19.46,0:12:24.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,オレは一体どうすればいい　どうすれば
Dialogue: 0,0:12:28.84,0:12:31.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,教えてくれ　ピエトロ
Dialogue: 0,0:12:36.72,0:12:37.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,死ねばいい
Dialogue: 0,0:12:38.17,0:12:41.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,死んで　オレと同じこっちの世界に来ればいい
Dialogue: 0,0:12:42.21,0:12:44.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,生きている者はいずれ死ぬ
Dialogue: 0,0:12:44.75,0:12:47.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,早いか遅いか　それだけの違いさ
Dialogue: 0,0:12:48.18,0:12:49.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,そんなに気に病む事はない
Dialogue: 0,0:12:50.93,0:12:52.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,おまえは医者なんて柄じゃない
Dialogue: 0,0:12:53.35,0:12:57.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,二人で楽しくやろう　昔みたいにな　レオリオ
Dialogue: 0,0:12:58.90,0:13:00.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,おまえとオレは友達だろう
Dialogue: 0,0:13:01.35,0:13:03.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,オレを一人にしないでくれ
Dialogue: 0,0:13:03.78,0:13:05.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,寂しい思いをさせないでくれよ
Dialogue: 0,0:13:06.59,0:13:09.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,こっちに来いよ　レオリオ
Dialogue: 0,0:13:18.07,0:13:19.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ピエトロ
Dialogue: 0,0:13:45.94,0:13:48.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,退けー　退け言ってんだよ
Dialogue: 0,0:13:50.43,0:13:51.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,落ちこぼれ共め
Dialogue: 0,0:14:07.99,0:14:09.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,どうした　レオリオ
Dialogue: 0,0:14:14.76,0:14:16.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,すまんねぇ　ピエトロ
Dialogue: 0,0:14:17.59,0:14:20.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,オレ　やっぱりおまえの元には行けねぇ
Dialogue: 0,0:14:22.34,0:14:23.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,なぜだ
Dialogue: 0,0:14:24.68,0:14:26.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,悪あがきかもしれねぇ
Dialogue: 0,0:14:27.35,0:14:29.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,立派な医者になる自信があるわけでもねぇ
Dialogue: 0,0:14:31.80,0:14:32.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,でも
Dialogue: 0,0:14:33.15,0:14:36.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,オレはこのまま何もせずに終わりたくねぇんだ
Dialogue: 0,0:14:37.16,0:14:39.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,おまえと同じ病気の子供を治してやりてぇ
Dialogue: 0,0:14:40.59,0:14:41.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,そして　その子の親に
Dialogue: 0,0:14:42.03,0:14:43.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,金なんていらねぇって言ってやりてぇ
Dialogue: 0,0:14:47.89,0:14:51.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,そのために　オレは　生きて医者になりてぇんだ
Dialogue: 0,0:14:53.06,0:14:57.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,すまんねぇ　許してくれ　ピエトロ
Dialogue: 0,0:15:04.46,0:15:08.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,レオリオ　なれよ　レオリオ
Dialogue: 0,0:15:11.25,0:15:12.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,立派な医者にな
Dialogue: 0,0:15:32.83,0:15:36.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,確かに手取り速やい方法だがなんとも荒っぽい
Dialogue: 0,0:15:36.93,0:15:38.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,もう引き返す事はできないな
Dialogue: 0,0:15:39.97,0:15:43.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,えっつー　いっててててー
Dialogue: 0,0:15:44.80,0:15:46.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ゴン　クラピカ
Dialogue: 0,0:15:48.62,0:15:49.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ピエトロ
Dialogue: 0,0:15:50.34,0:15:52.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,壁の樹液の匂いが幻覚を見せてたんだ
Dialogue: 0,0:15:53.33,0:15:54.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,トンパに騙された
Dialogue: 0,0:15:54.60,0:15:55.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,幻覚
Dialogue: 0,0:15:56.68,0:16:01.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,そうか　どうやら危ない所助けられたようだな
Dialogue: 0,0:16:01.61,0:16:03.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,でも　おまえ達はなんともなかったのか
Dialogue: 0,0:16:03.89,0:16:05.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,わたしも危うく
Dialogue: 0,0:16:05.40,0:16:07.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,オレ　なんともなかったよ
Dialogue: 0,0:16:07.68,0:16:10.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,確かに　ゴンには効きそうもねぇワナだな
Dialogue: 0,0:16:10.42,0:16:11.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,悩みなんてなさそうだし
Dialogue: 0,0:16:12.45,0:16:14.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,おっさん　ムダ話してる時間はないぜ
Dialogue: 0,0:16:15.15,0:16:17.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,おっさん　あっ　おまえ
Dialogue: 0,0:16:17.73,0:16:20.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,キルアって言うんだ　次行くぜ
Dialogue: 0,0:16:22.50,0:16:26.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,カチって　それは　もしかして　爆弾
Dialogue: 0,0:16:32.64,0:16:35.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,新人潰しのトンパさんよ　またやってきたのか
Dialogue: 0,0:16:35.98,0:16:38.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,へっ　オレの生き甲斐でね
Dialogue: 0,0:16:38.20,0:16:39.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怖い怖い
Dialogue: 0,0:16:47.43,0:16:49.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,トンネル工事でもしてるのか
Dialogue: 0,0:16:58.48,0:16:59.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,やった
Dialogue: 0,0:17:04.38,0:17:05.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一体　何をどうです
Dialogue: 0,0:17:09.55,0:17:12.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ごめんなさい　ちょっと壁壊しちゃった
Dialogue: 0,0:17:12.72,0:17:15.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,壊していけないとは一言も言っておりませんよ
Dialogue: 0,0:17:16.30,0:17:20.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,惑わしの道に迷い込んでよく生還できましたね
Dialogue: 0,0:17:20.55,0:17:22.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大した者ですよ
Dialogue: 0,0:17:22.50,0:17:23.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,そ　そんな
Dialogue: 0,0:17:24.55,0:17:27.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今年のルーキーは一体どんなってるんだ
Dialogue: 0,0:17:28.97,0:17:30.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,このヤロォー
Dialogue: 0,0:17:30.62,0:17:31.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,テメーだけは許さねぇ
Dialogue: 0,0:17:33.45,0:17:34.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,止めよな　レオリオ
Dialogue: 0,0:17:34.86,0:17:37.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,うるせぇー　ゴンは頭に来ねぇのかよ
Dialogue: 0,0:17:38.38,0:17:39.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,テストに障害は付き物だ
Dialogue: 0,0:17:52.62,0:17:54.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ありがとう　キルア
Dialogue: 0,0:17:54.57,0:17:55.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,助けたわけじゃない
Dialogue: 0,0:17:57.26,0:17:59.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,言ったろう　これはゲームだって
Dialogue: 0,0:17:59.96,0:18:02.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,さて　皆さん　そろそろラストスパートです
Dialogue: 0,0:18:03.08,0:18:05.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ちょっとペースをあげますよ
Dialogue: 0,0:18:08.28,0:18:10.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,なーにー
Dialogue: 0,0:18:16.88,0:18:18.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,そうだったのか　この嘘つきめ
Dialogue: 0,0:18:19.21,0:18:22.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘘なもんか　オレの目的はやっぱり金さ
Dialogue: 0,0:18:22.44,0:18:24.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,過去は過去　金は金よ
Dialogue: 0,0:18:24.48,0:18:26.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一文の得にもなんねぇもんは
Dialogue: 0,0:18:26.16,0:18:27.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,すっぱり捨ててくたちでね
Dialogue: 0,0:18:28.21,0:18:29.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,なれるといいな
Dialogue: 0,0:18:29.65,0:18:31.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,おまえに言われるまでもねぇよ
Dialogue: 0,0:18:31.41,0:18:33.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,死んでもハンターになったる
Dialogue: 0,0:18:33.67,0:18:35.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,いや　医者にだよ
Dialogue: 0,0:18:35.44,0:18:39.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,えっ　そういう事を済んだ人みてぇ言うんじゃねぇ
Dialogue: 0,0:18:40.08,0:18:41.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,誤解されたら　どうするんだよ
Dialogue: 0,0:18:42.04,0:18:43.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,よーし　行くぜ
Dialogue: 0,0:18:43.73,0:18:44.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大丈夫か　レオリオ
Dialogue: 0,0:18:45.20,0:18:47.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,おおー　見ての通りだぜ
Dialogue: 0,0:18:47.61,0:18:50.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,形振り構わなきゃまだまだいける事がわかったからな
Dialogue: 0,0:18:51.00,0:18:53.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,フリチンになっても走るのさ
Dialogue: 0,0:18:57.63,0:18:59.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,わたしも少しは奴を見習おうか
Dialogue: 0,0:19:00.34,0:19:01.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ああ　出口だ
Dialogue: 0,0:19:02.14,0:19:03.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嬉しそうだな
Dialogue: 0,0:19:03.97,0:19:05.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,キルア　嬉しくないの
Dialogue: 0,0:19:05.63,0:19:09.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,別に　ただの出口だ　つまんねぇ試験だな
Dialogue: 0,0:19:09.98,0:19:11.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,これじゃゲームにもならない
Dialogue: 0,0:19:14.73,0:19:17.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,でも合格すれば　ハンターになれるんだよ
Dialogue: 0,0:19:17.87,0:19:19.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,なんでそんなにハンターになりたいんだ
Dialogue: 0,0:19:20.20,0:19:21.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,オレの父さん　ハンターなんだ
Dialogue: 0,0:19:22.19,0:19:24.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,きっとすごいハンターに違いないんだ
Dialogue: 0,0:19:24.44,0:19:25.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,きっと
Dialogue: 0,0:19:25.92,0:19:28.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,うん　オレ　おばさんの家で育てられたから
Dialogue: 0,0:19:29.00,0:19:30.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,父さんは写真でしか知らないんだ
Dialogue: 0,0:19:33.26,0:19:34.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,でも　それでいいんだ
Dialogue: 0,0:19:34.72,0:19:36.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,オレ　父さんみたいなハンターになりたい
Dialogue: 0,0:19:45.58,0:19:48.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ね　それ　そのうち貸してくんないかな
Dialogue: 0,0:19:49.75,0:19:50.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ダメ
Dialogue: 0,0:19:51.99,0:19:55.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,その釣竿を貸してくれたらな　ゴン
Dialogue: 0,0:19:59.41,0:20:01.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,驚くほど太刀なお子様達です
Dialogue: 0,0:20:02.36,0:20:04.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,まだまだ楽しめそうですね
Dialogue: 0,0:20:15.80,0:20:19.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,ヌメーレ湿原　総称詐欺師の塒
Dialogue: 0,0:20:19.87,0:20:23.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,二次試験会場へはここ通って行かなければなりません
Dialogue: 0,0:20:28.26,0:20:31.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,この湿原にしかいない珍奇な動物達
Dialogue: 0,0:20:31.72,0:20:35.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,その多くが人間をあざむいて食料にしようとする
Dialogue: 0,0:20:35.73,0:20:38.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,狡猾で貪欲な生き物です
Dialogue: 0,0:20:45.84,0:20:46.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,待って
Dialogue: 0,0:20:49.04,0:20:51.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,十分注意してついて来てください
Dialogue: 0,0:20:51.80,0:20:53.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,騙されると死にますよ
Dialogue: 0,0:20:54.01,0:20:55.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,おかしいな事言うぜ
Dialogue: 0,0:20:55.42,0:20:58.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,騙されるとわかってたら　引っかるわけねぇだろ
Dialogue: 0,0:20:59.10,0:21:01.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘘だ　そいつは嘘をついてる
Dialogue: 0,0:21:10.67,0:21:11.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,そいつは偽物だ
Dialogue: 0,0:21:12.20,0:21:14.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,試験官じゃない　オレが本当の試験官だ
Dialogue: 0,0:21:17.47,0:21:19.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,偽者　どういうことだ
Dialogue: 0,0:21:19.67,0:21:21.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,じゃそこにいるのは　一体
Dialogue: 0,0:21:32.42,0:21:35.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,うわ　すごい霧　前が見えないよ
Dialogue: 0,0:21:35.58,0:21:38.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,霧の向こうで　ヒソカにより惨劇が始まっていたんだ
Dialogue: 0,0:21:39.24,0:21:40.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,次回　ハンターハンター
Dialogue: 0,0:21:40.95,0:21:42.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,奇術士　ほほえみ　猛獣注意
Dialogue: 0,0:21:43.17,0:21:44.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,君は見るよね
Dialogue: 0,0:01:11.90,0:01:15.44,china,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我叫顿巴 今年是16号
Dialogue: 0,0:01:16.59,0:01:17.58,china,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我叫尼克鲁
Dialogue: 0,0:01:17.80,0:01:20.21,china,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我只告诉你一个人 我可是个忍者哦
Dialogue: 0,0:01:22.89,0:01:23.94,china,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小心点
Dialogue: 0,0:01:24.18,0:01:26.22,china,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,撞到别人要记得道歉啊
Dialogue: 0,0:01:27.61,0:01:30.35,china,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在猎人考试正式开始
Dialogue: 0,0:01:34.73,0:01:36.49,china,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂 你叫什么名字
Dialogue: 0,0:01:41.97,0:01:42.98,china,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,雷欧力 喂
Dialogue: 0,0:01:44.10,0:01:45.08,china,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们是笨蛋吗
Dialogue: 0,0:01:45.86,0:01:47.06,china,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那家伙已经完了
Dialogue: 0,0:01:50.00,0:01:51.22,china,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,雷欧力就拜托你了
Dialogue: 0,0:01:55.83,0:01:57.30,china,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我来帮你 和我们一起走吧
Dialogue: 0,0:01:57.83,0:01:59.00,china,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我还是去看一下吧
Dialogue: 0,0:01:59.10,0:01:59.87,china,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也去
Dialogue: 0,0:02:00.23,0:02:00.95,china,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们一定会回来的
Dialogue: 0,0:02:01.28,0:02:04.11,china,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那时希望你能告诉我们你的名字
Dialogue: 0,0:02:05.12,0:02:06.26,china,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在这里休息下吧
Dialogue: 0,0:02:06.55,0:02:09.73,china,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样一来 你们一定会被淘汰
Dialogue: 0,0:02:09.93,0:02:10.46,china,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么
Dialogue: 0,0:02:10.67,0:02:11.49,china,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再见了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:20.61,0:02:23.25,china,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,下一个被毁掉的会是谁呢
Dialogue: 0,0:02:23.52,0:02:27.88,china,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,身心创伤 极限 陷阱
Dialogue: 0,0:02:42.70,0:02:45.30,china,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以 那个时候我已经说过了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:45.94,0:02:49.56,china,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样就放弃的话 你没资格当猎人
Dialogue: 0,0:02:50.79,0:02:52.77,china,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还没到吗 我肚子都饿了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:53.11,0:02:53.80,china,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不会吧
Dialogue: 0,0:02:58.61,0:02:59.18,china,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,奇怪
Dialogue: 0,0:03:02.09,0:03:03.51,china,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,顿巴先生 怎么了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:06.66,0:03:08.12,china,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不 不好了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:08.73,0:03:10.68,china,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快 你们俩快去帮帮他们
Dialogue: 0,0:03:11.13,0:03:12.11,china,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,里面怎么了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:12.53,0:03:16.71,china,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这种陷阱我还是第一次见 快
Dialogue: 0,0:03:35.04,0:03:39.96,china,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别说了 我怎么可能被淘汰 住嘴
Dialogue: 0,0:03:41.10,0:03:43.79,china,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,才到这里就被淘汰 真是闻所未闻
Dialogue: 0,0:03:44.53,0:03:46.08,china,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是丢人啊
Dialogue: 0,0:03:46.84,0:03:47.62,china,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要说了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:48.60,0:03:51.51,china,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,留级生 淘汰者
Dialogue: 0,0:03:51.79,0:03:52.85,china,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要说了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:53.23,0:03:56.61,china,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,落水狗 落后的人 失败者
Dialogue: 0,0:03:57.39,0:04:00.14,china,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最无能奖非你莫属
Dialogue: 0,0:04:00.31,0:04:00.96,china,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没大脑
Dialogue: 0,0:04:01.43,0:04:02.56,china,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,无能的人
Dialogue: 0,0:04:02.85,0:04:06.25,china,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,自从有猎人考试以来最弱的人
Dialogue: 0,0:04:06.52,0:04:08.19,china,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一点本事都没有 笨蛋
Dialogue: 0,0:04:08.78,0:04:11.01,china,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,以后可别再来了 废物
Dialogue: 0,0:04:11.53,0:04:17.50,china,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,废物 落选者 废物 没大脑 淘汰者
Dialogue: 0,0:04:27.31,0:04:28.80,china,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,到底 怎么回事
Dialogue: 0,0:04:29.13,0:04:29.74,china,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,雷欧力
Dialogue: 0,0:04:38.64,0:04:41.14,china,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,救救我 雷欧力
Dialogue: 0,0:04:41.62,0:04:43.05,china,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,皮 皮耶多
Dialogue: 0,0:05:01.27,0:05:02.65,china,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,皮耶多
Dialogue: 0,0:05:07.71,0:05:10.01,china,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,尼克鲁 怎么了 发生什么了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:21.16,0:05:22.26,china,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,尼克鲁
Dialogue: 0,0:05:36.42,0:05:38.14,china,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快 我们去找雷欧力
Dialogue: 0,0:05:42.71,0:05:44.66,china,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂 你去哪
Dialogue: 0,0:05:44.86,0:05:47.94,china,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等我 等我一下
Dialogue: 0,0:05:49.09,0:05:50.02,china,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂
Dialogue: 0,0:05:58.23,0:05:58.96,china,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,皮耶多
Dialogue: 0,0:06:10.40,0:06:12.16,china,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,皮耶多
Dialogue: 0,0:06:14.15,0:06:17.53,china,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,雷欧力 你终于来了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:06:20.33,0:06:22.69,china,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过 已经迟了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:23.28,0:06:26.66,china,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如你所见 我已经挂掉了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:27.62,0:06:30.91,china,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的心脏再也不会跳动了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:31.88,0:06:34.88,china,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个身体只是一具冰冷的尸体而已
Dialogue: 0,0:06:36.52,0:06:39.92,china,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,雷欧力 你不是想当医生吗
Dialogue: 0,0:06:41.00,0:06:45.54,china,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,救救我啊 治好我 雷欧力
Dialogue: 0,0:06:52.57,0:06:55.64,china,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,雷欧力 快回答 雷欧力
Dialogue: 0,0:06:57.71,0:06:58.41,china,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:10.73,0:07:12.07,china,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,幻影旅团
Dialogue: 0,0:07:14.54,0:07:15.29,china,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,酷拉皮卡
Dialogue: 0,0:07:17.13,0:07:17.93,china,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,住手
Dialogue: 0,0:07:19.21,0:07:20.28,china,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,住手
Dialogue: 0,0:07:23.36,0:07:26.57,china,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,酷拉皮卡 喂 酷拉皮卡
Dialogue: 0,0:07:38.44,0:07:39.22,china,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,酷拉皮卡
Dialogue: 0,0:07:41.89,0:07:43.42,china,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你怎么了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:45.27,0:07:49.36,china,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,住 住手
Dialogue: 0,0:07:51.12,0:07:51.88,china,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,酷拉皮卡
Dialogue: 0,0:08:12.96,0:08:14.83,china,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,酷拉皮卡 振作一点啊
Dialogue: 0,0:08:17.84,0:08:20.37,china,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,雷欧力 我现在就去救你
Dialogue: 0,0:08:32.82,0:08:34.26,china,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你害怕什么
Dialogue: 0,0:08:34.59,0:08:36.05,china,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没啊 没啥
Dialogue: 0,0:08:37.38,0:08:40.10,china,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是你设下的陷阱吧
Dialogue: 0,0:08:40.47,0:08:41.97,china,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,胡说什么
Dialogue: 0,0:08:43.45,0:08:44.93,china,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要好好教教你
Dialogue: 0,0:08:48.20,0:08:49.97,china,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,使用卑鄙手段的家伙
Dialogue: 0,0:08:50.29,0:08:53.81,china,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,早晚会死的很惨的
Dialogue: 0,0:08:54.42,0:08:57.31,china,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我可没有骗你 不信的话试试看吧
Dialogue: 0,0:08:57.95,0:09:01.29,china,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在 在这里
Dialogue: 0,0:09:14.33,0:09:15.15,china,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,臭小鬼
Dialogue: 0,0:09:19.58,0:09:21.08,china,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,醒了吗 雷欧力
Dialogue: 0,0:09:22.02,0:09:24.69,china,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 皮耶多 对不起
Dialogue: 0,0:09:25.40,0:09:26.69,china,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我很想治好你的
Dialogue: 0,0:09:27.30,0:09:31.27,china,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可是没有给你做手术的钱
Dialogue: 0,0:09:32.09,0:09:33.73,china,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 我知道
Dialogue: 0,0:09:34.50,0:09:38.99,china,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且 做手术得有医师执照
Dialogue: 0,0:09:39.77,0:09:42.58,china,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那样需要更多更多的钱
Dialogue: 0,0:09:42.98,0:09:45.27,china,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可恶 要是有钱就好了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:45.62,0:09:47.28,china,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个时候要是有钱的话
Dialogue: 0,0:09:48.74,0:09:51.28,china,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要成为猎人 挣很多的钱
Dialogue: 0,0:09:51.60,0:09:53.80,china,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后用这些钱去做医生
Dialogue: 0,0:09:54.68,0:09:57.56,china,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后把你这样的病人
Dialogue: 0,0:09:57.70,0:09:59.32,china,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一个个全部治好
Dialogue: 0,0:10:00.08,0:10:00.82,china,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以
Dialogue: 0,0:10:12.01,0:10:12.62,china,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,酷拉皮卡
Dialogue: 0,0:10:14.92,0:10:17.76,china,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,酷拉皮卡
Dialogue: 0,0:10:35.00,0:10:35.71,china,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,酷拉皮卡
Dialogue: 0,0:10:36.80,0:10:37.42,china,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小杰
Dialogue: 0,0:10:37.71,0:10:39.32,china,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太好了 你清醒了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:40.29,0:10:40.90,china,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:10:41.76,0:10:43.46,china,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这根本不是什么治愈之树
Dialogue: 0,0:10:45.20,0:10:49.20,china,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这些是以前的暗杀者常用的迷魂树脂
Dialogue: 0,0:10:50.22,0:10:53.18,china,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,它让人看到记忆中最痛苦的回忆
Dialogue: 0,0:10:53.36,0:10:54.82,china,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,从而摧毁人的精神
Dialogue: 0,0:10:55.37,0:10:56.43,china,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你好了解
Dialogue: 0,0:10:56.89,0:10:58.31,china,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那 顿巴呢
Dialogue: 0,0:10:59.16,0:11:01.02,china,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们中了他设下的陷阱了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:02.97,0:11:03.63,china,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们快走吧
Dialogue: 0,0:11:04.03,0:11:06.24,china,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我有办法救那个大叔
Dialogue: 0,0:11:06.35,0:11:09.37,china,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,并且 还能一口气住追上领先的家伙们
Dialogue: 0,0:11:10.76,0:11:12.81,china,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,游戏太简单的话也就没意思了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:13.32,0:11:16.40,china,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在我们又见面了 告诉我你的名字吧
Dialogue: 0,0:11:18.62,0:11:19.39,china,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,奇犽
Dialogue: 0,0:11:39.37,0:11:40.01,china,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不行了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:43.47,0:11:46.97,china,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎哟喂 真可怜 拜拜
Dialogue: 0,0:11:51.28,0:11:52.05,china,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,奇犽
Dialogue: 0,0:11:53.96,0:11:56.24,china,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,奇犽 我们该怎么办
Dialogue: 0,0:11:58.77,0:12:00.87,china,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,炸弹 威力很强的
Dialogue: 0,0:12:01.16,0:12:02.02,china,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,炸弹
Dialogue: 0,0:12:02.46,0:12:06.03,china,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要炸掉它 这个沾满树液的恶心墙壁
Dialogue: 0,0:12:19.46,0:12:24.19,china,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我到底该怎么办 怎么办
Dialogue: 0,0:12:28.84,0:12:31.42,china,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,告诉我 皮耶多
Dialogue: 0,0:12:36.72,0:12:37.47,china,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你最好也死了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:38.17,0:12:41.39,china,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,死了 就可以来到我的世界
Dialogue: 0,0:12:42.21,0:12:44.19,china,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,活着的人总是要死的
Dialogue: 0,0:12:44.75,0:12:47.41,china,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只是早点晚点的不同而已
Dialogue: 0,0:12:48.18,0:12:49.89,china,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不需要纠结了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:50.93,0:12:52.69,china,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你又没有当医生的天分
Dialogue: 0,0:12:53.35,0:12:57.80,china,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,到我这里来吧 就像以前一样 雷欧力
Dialogue: 0,0:12:58.90,0:13:00.56,china,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们可是朋友啊
Dialogue: 0,0:13:01.35,0:13:03.10,china,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要丢下我一个人
Dialogue: 0,0:13:03.78,0:13:05.94,china,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要让我一个人孤孤单单的
Dialogue: 0,0:13:06.59,0:13:09.09,china,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来吧 雷欧力
Dialogue: 0,0:13:18.07,0:13:19.04,china,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,皮耶多
Dialogue: 0,0:13:45.94,0:13:48.30,china,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让开 给我让开
Dialogue: 0,0:13:50.43,0:13:51.70,china,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一群没用的家伙
Dialogue: 0,0:14:07.99,0:14:09.88,china,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了 雷欧力
Dialogue: 0,0:14:14.76,0:14:16.54,china,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉 皮耶多
Dialogue: 0,0:14:17.59,0:14:20.17,china,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我 我还是不能跟你走
Dialogue: 0,0:14:22.34,0:14:23.07,china,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么
Dialogue: 0,0:14:24.68,0:14:26.05,china,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,或许我只是在做梦
Dialogue: 0,0:14:27.35,0:14:29.55,china,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也没有信心成为了不起的医生
Dialogue: 0,0:14:31.80,0:14:32.42,china,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是
Dialogue: 0,0:14:33.15,0:14:36.03,china,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不想还没开始就放弃
Dialogue: 0,0:14:37.16,0:14:39.85,china,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想治好那些像你一样生病的孩子
Dialogue: 0,0:14:40.59,0:14:41.72,china,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后 对他们的父母说
Dialogue: 0,0:14:42.03,0:14:43.87,china,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我治病不要钱
Dialogue: 0,0:14:47.89,0:14:51.86,china,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以 我才想成为医生的
Dialogue: 0,0:14:53.06,0:14:57.43,china,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不起 请你原谅我 皮耶多
Dialogue: 0,0:15:04.46,0:15:08.14,china,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,雷欧力 你做得到的 雷欧力
Dialogue: 0,0:15:11.25,0:15:12.56,china,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,成为了不起的医生
Dialogue: 0,0:15:32.83,0:15:36.43,china,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,确实是很有效的办法 不过有点太粗暴了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:36.93,0:15:38.78,china,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,已经没法恢复了原样了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:39.97,0:15:43.63,china,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 疼 哎哎
Dialogue: 0,0:15:44.80,0:15:46.43,china,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小杰 酷拉皮卡
Dialogue: 0,0:15:48.62,0:15:49.70,china,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,皮耶多
Dialogue: 0,0:15:50.34,0:15:52.59,china,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是墙上的树液让你产生了幻觉
Dialogue: 0,0:15:53.33,0:15:54.51,china,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们被顿巴骗了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:54.60,0:15:55.53,china,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,幻觉
Dialogue: 0,0:15:56.68,0:16:01.05,china,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吗 还好你们在最危险的时候救了我
Dialogue: 0,0:16:01.61,0:16:03.28,china,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过 你们什么也没看到吗
Dialogue: 0,0:16:03.89,0:16:05.10,china,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也中计了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:05.40,0:16:07.19,china,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我 什么都没看到
Dialogue: 0,0:16:07.68,0:16:10.21,china,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我觉得也是 那陷阱对小杰无效
Dialogue: 0,0:16:10.42,0:16:11.87,china,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为他根本就没有烦恼嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:16:12.45,0:16:14.86,china,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大叔 我们可没时间在这里闲聊了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:15.15,0:16:17.21,china,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大叔 喂 你
Dialogue: 0,0:16:17.73,0:16:20.31,china,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他叫奇犽 我们走
Dialogue: 0,0:16:22.50,0:16:26.80,china,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咔叽 那不会是炸弹吧
Dialogue: 0,0:16:32.64,0:16:35.58,china,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,新人杀手顿巴 你又害了几个人啊
Dialogue: 0,0:16:35.98,0:16:38.00,china,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哼 这可是我人生的意义所在啊
Dialogue: 0,0:16:38.20,0:16:39.56,china,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真可怕
Dialogue: 0,0:16:47.43,0:16:49.03,china,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,隧道在施工吗
Dialogue: 0,0:16:58.48,0:16:59.45,china,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,成功了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:04.38,0:17:05.98,china,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,到底 是怎么回事
Dialogue: 0,0:17:09.55,0:17:12.44,china,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不起 我们把墙壁炸坏了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:12.72,0:17:15.97,china,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我没说你们不能炸坏墙壁
Dialogue: 0,0:17:16.30,0:17:20.27,china,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,误闯鬼迷心窍杉树林居然还能活着出来
Dialogue: 0,0:17:20.55,0:17:22.27,china,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是了不起
Dialogue: 0,0:17:22.50,0:17:23.94,china,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什 什么
Dialogue: 0,0:17:24.55,0:17:27.22,china,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今年的新人到底是何方神圣啊
Dialogue: 0,0:17:28.97,0:17:30.13,china,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,混蛋
Dialogue: 0,0:17:30.62,0:17:31.98,china,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我绝不会原谅你
Dialogue: 0,0:17:33.45,0:17:34.63,china,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,住手 雷欧力
Dialogue: 0,0:17:34.86,0:17:37.79,china,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,闭嘴 小杰你不生气吗
Dialogue: 0,0:17:38.38,0:17:39.99,china,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,任何考试中总有妨碍别人的人
Dialogue: 0,0:17:52.62,0:17:54.09,china,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢你 奇犽
Dialogue: 0,0:17:54.57,0:17:55.93,china,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不是想要帮你们
Dialogue: 0,0:17:57.26,0:17:59.45,china,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我说过了 这只是个游戏
Dialogue: 0,0:17:59.96,0:18:02.86,china,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,各位 马上就是最后冲刺了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:03.08,0:18:05.35,china,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要加快速度了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:08.28,0:18:10.64,china,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么
Dialogue: 0,0:18:16.88,0:18:18.70,china,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的是那样的吗 你这个骗子
Dialogue: 0,0:18:19.21,0:18:22.18,china,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我才没说骗人 我的目的就是钱
Dialogue: 0,0:18:22.44,0:18:24.08,china,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,过去是过去 钱是钱
Dialogue: 0,0:18:24.48,0:18:26.03,china,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为了赚钱
Dialogue: 0,0:18:26.16,0:18:27.71,china,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我可是什么都能丢下
Dialogue: 0,0:18:28.21,0:18:29.18,china,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,希望你能成功
Dialogue: 0,0:18:29.65,0:18:31.15,china,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我还用不着你这个小鬼来鼓励
Dialogue: 0,0:18:31.41,0:18:33.21,china,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我死也要成为猎人
Dialogue: 0,0:18:33.67,0:18:35.10,china,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不 我是说当医生
Dialogue: 0,0:18:35.44,0:18:39.85,china,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要说的好像你已经办到了似的
Dialogue: 0,0:18:40.08,0:18:41.50,china,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,被人误会了 怎么办
Dialogue: 0,0:18:42.04,0:18:43.34,china,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了 我要出发了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:43.73,0:18:44.96,china,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你还好吧 雷欧力
Dialogue: 0,0:18:45.20,0:18:47.39,china,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你也看到了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:47.61,0:18:50.51,china,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我这个人只要拼命去做就一定能成
Dialogue: 0,0:18:51.00,0:18:53.55,china,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,半裸着我也要跑下去
Dialogue: 0,0:18:57.63,0:18:59.69,china,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也要像雷欧力学习一下啊
Dialogue: 0,0:19:00.34,0:19:01.75,china,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啊 到出口了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:02.14,0:19:03.38,china,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你好像很高兴
Dialogue: 0,0:19:03.97,0:19:05.36,china,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,奇犽你不觉得高兴吗
Dialogue: 0,0:19:05.63,0:19:09.59,china,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没什么 只是出口而已 这考试真无聊
Dialogue: 0,0:19:09.98,0:19:11.58,china,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样下去游戏就不好玩了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:14.73,0:19:17.51,china,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是通过了就能成为猎人
Dialogue: 0,0:19:17.87,0:19:19.82,china,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么那么想当猎人呢
Dialogue: 0,0:19:20.20,0:19:21.93,china,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我父亲就是猎人
Dialogue: 0,0:19:22.19,0:19:24.26,china,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他一定是个了不起的猎人
Dialogue: 0,0:19:24.44,0:19:25.43,china,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一定
Dialogue: 0,0:19:25.92,0:19:28.79,china,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 我是阿姨养大的
Dialogue: 0,0:19:29.00,0:19:30.76,china,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我只在相片中见过父亲
Dialogue: 0,0:19:33.26,0:19:34.38,china,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是没有关系
Dialogue: 0,0:19:34.72,0:19:36.96,china,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也要成为他那样的猎人
Dialogue: 0,0:19:45.58,0:19:48.80,china,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂 那个 你的滑板 借我玩玩好不好
Dialogue: 0,0:19:49.75,0:19:50.30,china,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行吗
Dialogue: 0,0:19:51.99,0:19:55.25,china,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,除非你先借给我你的钓竿 小杰
Dialogue: 0,0:19:59.41,0:20:01.92,china,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没想到今年的小鬼都很厉害
Dialogue: 0,0:20:02.36,0:20:04.72,china,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好像越来越有趣了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:15.80,0:20:19.25,china,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,失美乐湿原 通常称为欺诈师的巢穴
Dialogue: 0,0:20:19.87,0:20:23.76,china,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是去二次考试考场的必经之路
Dialogue: 0,0:20:28.26,0:20:31.19,china,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这里有很多特有的珍奇动物
Dialogue: 0,0:20:31.72,0:20:35.40,china,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,其中很多以人肉为食
Dialogue: 0,0:20:35.73,0:20:38.23,china,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是生性狡猾又贪婪的生物
Dialogue: 0,0:20:45.84,0:20:46.66,china,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等等我
Dialogue: 0,0:20:49.04,0:20:51.61,china,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请一定注意跟紧我的脚步
Dialogue: 0,0:20:51.80,0:20:53.64,china,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,落入陷阱的话只有死路一条
Dialogue: 0,0:20:54.01,0:20:55.16,china,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真搞笑
Dialogue: 0,0:20:55.42,0:20:58.41,china,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,既然知道是陷阱 谁还会上当啊
Dialogue: 0,0:20:59.10,0:21:01.68,china,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,骗子 那家伙在说谎
Dialogue: 0,0:21:10.67,0:21:11.89,china,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他是冒牌货
Dialogue: 0,0:21:12.20,0:21:14.98,china,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他不是考官 我才是考官
Dialogue: 0,0:21:17.47,0:21:19.14,china,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,冒牌货 到底怎么回事
Dialogue: 0,0:21:19.67,0:21:21.52,china,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么 那个人到底是谁
Dialogue: 0,0:21:32.42,0:21:35.05,china,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哇 好大的雾啊 根本看不清前面的路
Dialogue: 0,0:21:35.58,0:21:38.38,china,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,雾的前方 西索开始大开杀戒
Dialogue: 0,0:21:39.24,0:21:40.64,china,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,下集 全职猎人
Dialogue: 0,0:21:40.95,0:21:42.97,china,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,魔术师 微笑 注意魔兽
Dialogue: 0,0:21:43.17,0:21:44.18,china,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你一定要看哟


